when women are empowered to make their
当女性被赋予权力做出她们的决定时
own sexual decisions they target the top
他们自己的性决定，他们的目标是顶层
10% of men but why does any of that
10%的男性，但为什么会这样呢？
matter well that creates a lot of
物质很好，这造成了很多
problems both for men and women so it
男女都会遇到这些问题。
creates problems for women because Dr
这会给女性带来问题，因为医生
Orion taban is a clinical psychologist
Orion Taban 是一位临床心理学家
who specializes in modern dating and
专门研究现代约会和
relationships by delving into the
通过深入探究人际关系
psychological aspects of Attraction
吸引力的心理层面
communication and emotional intimacy the
沟通和情感亲密
meteoric rise of dating apps has seen a
约会软件的迅猛发展已经见证了
catastrophic decline in all forms of
各种形式的灾难性衰退
relationships fewer people are entering
越来越少的人开始建立恋爱关系。
into relationships fewer people are even
更少的人会进入恋爱关系，甚至更少的人会进入恋爱关系。
hooking up anymore and it is a crisis
不再约会，这简直是一场危机
and a lot of the traditional strategies
以及许多传统策略
are no longer relevant so why'd you stop
已经不再相关了，那你为什么停止呢？
first of all date like it's your job
首先，约会要像对待工作一样认真。
lots of people just want a loving secure
很多人只是想要一个充满爱和安全感的家庭。
peaceful relationship that's like
就像和平的关系一样
wanting a job that's high paying low
想要一份高薪低收入的工作
stress and you're passionate about if
压力，以及你对……的热情
you want one of those jobs they're the
你想找一份这样的工作吗？他们就是
needle in the Hast stack you might have
你可能在疾速堆叠中遇到的针
to send out 200 resumes and you have to
你需要发送200份简历。
get over that rejection another thing
克服被拒绝的阴影，还有一件事
you get more opportunities for selection
你将获得更多选择机会。
the more attractive you present yourself
你越能展现自己的吸引力。
then everyone can be more attractive
这样一来，每个人都能更有魅力。
than you currently are and also the less
比你现在所拥有的更少
conventionally attractive you are the
你拥有传统意义上的吸引力。
more you have to learn seduction and if
你越需要学习如何诱惑别人，如果
you can do both you'll be able to have
你可以两者兼顾，你将能够拥有
all kinds of relationships so how do I
各种各样的关系，那我该如何？
become more attractive and also learn
变得更有吸引力，并且还能学习
The Art of Seduction so first of all you
诱惑的艺术，首先，你
need
需要
to what role has pornography played in
色情作品在其中扮演了什么角色？
all this it has completely changed the
这一切已经彻底改变了
game of mating and dating if you give
如果你参与交配和约会游戏，那就尽情享受吧！
men the opportunity to exist in a
男人有机会生活在一个
sexually satisfied state which is what
性满足状态，也就是什么
pornography does then they aren't going
如果色情作品确实能做到这一点，那么他们就不会去了。
to be having sex with real women so the
和真正的女人发生性关系，所以
man that comes to you with this problem
带着这个问题来找你的人
what you say to those men the advice I
你对那些男人说的话是什么？我的建议
would give is
会给的是
this is a sentence I never thought I'd
这是我从未想过我会说出的一句话。
say in my life um we've just hit 7
比如说，在我的人生中，我们刚刚到了7岁。
million subscribers on YouTube and I
我在YouTube上有数百万订阅者，而且我
want to say a huge thank you to all of
我要对所有人表示衷心的感谢。
you that show up here every Monday and
你们这些每周一都来这里的人
Thursday to watch our conversations um
周四观看我们的对话
from the bottom of my heart but also on
发自内心，但也……
behalf of my team who you don't always
代表我的团队，你并不总是……
get to meet there's almost 50 people now
见面的时候，现在差不多有50个人了。
behind the D of a CEO that work to put
首席执行官背后的D，致力于……
this together so from all of us thank
我们大家一起感谢大家。
you so much um we did a raffle last
非常感谢你，我们上次搞了个抽奖活动。
month and we gave away prizes for people
本月我们还向人们赠送了奖品。
that subscribed to the show up until 7
截至7点，一直订阅该节目的用户
million subscribers and you guys love
百万订阅者，你们都喜欢我！
that raffle so much that we're going to
那次抽奖活动如此成功，以至于我们将要……
continue it so every single month we're
继续这样做，这样我们每个月都能
giving away money can't buy prizes
花钱买不到奖品
including meetings with me invites to
包括与我会面的邀请
our events and ,000 gift vouchers to
我们的活动和价值 0000 美元的礼品券
anyone that subscribes to the DI CE
任何订阅DI CE的人
there's now more than 7 million of you
现在你们的人数已经超过700万了。
so if you make the decision to subscribe
所以，如果您决定订阅的话。
today you can be one of those lucky
今天，你也可以成为这些幸运儿之一。
people thank you from the bottom of my
人们由衷地感谢我
heart let's get to the
心脏，让我们进入正题
[Music]
[音乐]
conversation Dr Orion terban
与奥赖恩·特班博士的对话
can you give me the macro picture as it
你能给我一张微距照片吗？
relates to the work that you do when I
这与你做的工作有关，当我……
say the macro picture I mean like what
我说的是宏观画面，我的意思是，比如什么
is going on in the world now that is so
现在世界上正在发生的事情真是如此
interesting and important for us to
有趣且对我们来说很重要
understand before we start talking about
在我们开始讨论之前，请先了解一下
the relationship dynamics that we're
我们之间的关系动态
going going to talk about what is that
我们要谈谈那是什么。
sort of macro picture at the moment and
目前来看，这有点像是一幅宏观图景。
how is that changed and
这种变化是如何发生的？
changing I think probably big picture
我认为改变可能是从大局来看的。
the most Salient thing in the world is
世界上最显著的事物是
the relation ship crisis that we're
我们正经历着一场关系危机。
working through and it is a crisis in
正在努力克服，这是一场危机。
the last 10
最后10
years all kinds of relationships are
多年来，各种各样的关系
being transacted less frequently fewer
交易频率较低
people are getting married at this
人们正在这里结婚
country I think in the most recent year
我认为该国在最近一年
in which statistics are available it's
哪些地方有统计数据？
at historic lows it has never been this
处于历史低位，从未如此。
low before in the history of America
美国历史上最低点
fewer people are entering into
进入这个行业的人越来越少。
relationships half the world's
世界上一半的人的人际关系
population lives in countries below
人口居住在以下国家
reproductive rates replacement rates
生育率更替率
America would also be one of those
美国也将是其中之一。
countries if it weren't for its
如果不是因为……国家
immigration
移民
like actual citizenry isn't reproducing
就像真正的公民没有繁衍后代一样。
enough to replace its own population but
足以取代其自身人口，但
that's obscured by immigration really
移民问题确实掩盖了这一点。
yeah fewer people are even hooking up
是的，现在连约会的人都越来越少了。
anymore like there's fewer even casual
现在就连普通人也越来越少了。
sexual relationships being transacted
性关系交易
which is somewhat
这在某种程度上
surprising when you say fewer people are
令人惊讶的是，你说的人越来越少
hooking up and there's fewer um
约会越来越频繁，嗯……
transactional sexual relationships
交易性性关系
versus when versus like the 1950s or
与 20 世纪 50 年代相比，或者
versus certainly 1970 okay so when the
与1970年相比，当然可以，所以当
pill became widely available there was
药丸开始广泛普及。
predictably an explosion in casual sex
不出所料，随意性行为激增
relationships we know that for both men
我们知道，对于男性和女性来说，这种关系至关重要。
and women the number of Lifetime sexual
女性一生中性行为的数量
partners went up
合伙人上
significantly and we see that that's
非常明显，我们看到这一点是
much lower these days and that's kind of
如今价格低得多，这有点……
a problem because regardless of how you
这是一个问题，因为无论你如何……
feel about casual sex we live in a
对我们生活在其中的这种随意性行为的看法
culture in which sex precedes commitment
在性行为先于承诺的文化中
so the way to get to commitment and to
所以，获得承诺和……的方法
long-term relation relationships and
长期关系和
engagement in marriage if that's what
如果这就是订婚的话
you're looking for is kind of through
你想要的有点像通过
sex
性别
it's the first step of a process that
这是整个过程的第一步，
can potentially end in children and
可能导致儿童死亡
family so there are important Downstream
家庭，所以下游很重要
consequences in a culture where sex
在性行为会带来后果的文化中
precedes commitment when there is less
承诺之前，当较少
casual sex being transacted all of those
随意性行为被交易的所有这些
things you've described in the macro
你在宏观层面上描述的事情
those macro factors why do any of them
这些宏观因素为什么会对它们中的任何一个产生影响？
matter why do any of them matter hm
重要吗？为什么它们都重要？嗯？
what's the downstream consequence of all
这一切的后续后果是什么？
those things that you know you described
你知道你描述的那些东西
less people hooking up but marriage and
约会的人少了，但结婚的人却多了。
all these other factors relationships
所有这些其他因素之间的关系
why why does any of that matter to
为什么这一切对……重要？
society I guess on a macro scale it
我想，从宏观层面来说，社会就是这样。
could be population collapse I mean we
可能是人口崩溃，我的意思是，我们
know that some countries like Japan are
要知道，有些国家，比如日本，
already on the other side of their curve
他们已经走到了曲线的另一边
and are going to have a very topheavy
将会有一个非常重的顶部
generation for the next 10 to 15 years
未来10到15年这一代人
where one worker might be supporting
其中一名工人可能正在提供支持
over two citizens which might be an
超过两名公民，这可能是一个
economic burden that few workers
经济负担给少数劳动者带来了沉重的负担。
can bear because there's a young there's
能忍受，因为有个孩子
young people in the workforce and then
年轻人进入职场，然后
there's too many old people effectively
老年人太多了，而且他们的工作效率也太低了。
yeah and there's not enough babies to
是啊，而且婴儿数量也不够。
kind of rise up and replace even those
某种程度上，它们会崛起并取代那些
that are passing away so that's why
那些正在去世的人，所以才会这样。
there's all these advances in robotics
机器人技术取得了所有这些进步
and AI because they're trying to kind of
以及人工智能，因为他们试图……
make one person two people to keep
让一个人变成两个人来保持
Society stable and The
社会稳定且
Economic Consequences of population
人口的经济后果
collapse would be dire like they would
崩溃的后果将如同他们那样严重。
have to be navigated with a great deal
必须谨慎行事
of nuance and vision because the more
细致入微的洞察力和远见卓识，因为越多
accelerated the decline the more
加速衰退
unstable Society becomes so that
社会不稳定，以至于
probably is on a macro level the most
从宏观层面来看，这或许是最主要的。
dangerous thing about this kind of
这种类型的危险之处在于
situation but for the individual it just
情况就是这样，但对个人而言，这只是
makes mating and dating so much more
让交配和约会变得更加……
confusing than it ever has been like the
比以往任何时候都更加令人困惑。
individual probably isn't worried about
个人可能并不担心
the collapse of civilization and
文明的崩溃和
population decline they're worried about
他们担心人口下降
am I going to find somebody that I can
我能找到一个可以和我在一起的人吗？
have a satisfying relationship with and
与……建立令人满意的关系
that seems to be more difficult than it
这似乎比……更难
ever has been which is paradoxical
一直以来都是如此，这本身就是一个悖论。
because it also seems on some level that
因为在某种程度上，似乎也
it should never have been easier in the
事情本不应该这么容易。
history of humanity to get into a sexual
人类历史上，性行为的发生
or romantic relationship with all of our
或者与我们所有人建立浪漫关系
new
新的
technologies but it is it is isn't that
技术，但事实并非如此，不是吗？
interesting who who is suffering more or
有趣的是，谁遭受的痛苦更多？
are they just suffering differently men
他们只是遭受着不同的痛苦吗？
or women usually it's it's hard to be a
或者对女性来说，通常很难成为……
man and it's hard to be a woman it's
男人做人很难，女人做人也很难。
like hard to be a human being down here
在这里做人真难。
suffering is kind of standard like it's
苦难似乎成了一种常态，就像……
pain either way what other the types of
无论哪种方式都会感到疼痛，还有哪些其他类型？
problems that that start with men men
始于男性的问题
are having
有
well it's harder for men to meet women
男性结识女性确实更难。
and to get into relationships like in
并建立像……这样的关系
the last 10 years the number of
过去十年中，数量
relationships that were initiated online
通过网络建立的关系
increased by
增加
250% which is huge 10 years ago about
250%，这在10年前是一个巨大的增长。
20% of Americans met online now it's
现在有20%的美国人是通过网络认识的。
over
超过
50 the vast majority of couples are now
50 绝大多数夫妇现在
meeting through social media or online
通过社交媒体或网络相识
dating sites and across that same time
约会网站以及同一时期
period we've we've seen a radical
这段时期，我们已经看到了一个激进的
decrease in relationships that are being
关系减少
transacted so it's correlative but it's
已进行交易，因此具有相关性，但它是
very suggestive that the meteoric rise
这非常暗示了这种迅猛的崛起。
of dating apps has also seen a
约会软件也出现了这种情况
catastrophic decline in all forms of
各种形式的灾难性衰退
relationships do you think dating apps
你认为约会软件对人际关系有什么影响？
are a net positive or a net
是净正值还是净值
negative I think most people don't know
我觉得大多数人都不知道。
how to use dating apps correctly dating
如何正确使用约会应用程序
apps are tools and you have to adapt
应用程序是工具，你必须适应它们
strategy given what that technology is
鉴于该技术是什么，该策略是什么？
capable of doing if you try to use
如果你尝试使用，它就能做到
dating apps casually you're probably
随便用约会软件，你可能……
going to be
将会是
infuriated depressed and hopeless like
愤怒、沮丧和绝望
you need a strategy and that strategy
你需要一个策略，而这个策略
generally requires Massive Action so
通常需要采取大规模行动
especially for men interesting we'll get
尤其是对男性来说，这会很有趣，我们会得到
into that because I want to dig deeper
深入研究这个问题，是因为我想更深入地了解它。
there but just closing off on this point
就此打住，不再赘述。
about the other ways in which the
关于其他方面
changes in society have started to
社会变革已经开始
impact men yeah
冲击男人是的
um I think a lot about the mental health
嗯，我经常思考心理健康问题。
statistics and about suicidality I think
我认为，统计数据和自杀倾向方面的问题值得关注。
at least in the UK I know that the
至少在英国，我知道……
single biggest killer of men above the
男性最大的单一杀手
age of I think 40 45 is themselves and
我认为他们的年龄在40到45岁之间。
um I'm think trying to understand if
嗯，我想弄明白的是……
there's correlation there between a
两者之间存在相关性
changing world that has changed dating
世界变迁，约会方式也随之改变。
Dynamics but also gender Dynamics and
动态，以及性别动态和
the impact that that's had on men and
这对男性和女性都产生了影响
masculinity let's say well masculinity
男子气概，我们姑且称之为男子气概吧。
is in a crisis which creates an
正处于危机之中，这造成了
opportunity in the marketplace for lots
市场上有很多机会。
of people to come come in and say this
来的人会说这句话
is what it means to be a man like that
这就是做那样一个人的意义所在。
would be somewhat unheard of 100 years
这在一百年前是闻所未闻的。
ago because we all just more or less
很久以前，因为我们或多或少都差不多
knew what it meant to be a man but now
曾经知道做男人的意义，但现在
we need personalities to come into the
我们需要有个性的人加入。
milu and say this is what it means to be
milu 说这就是存在的意义
a man now in my opinion A lot of that is
在我看来，他现在很大程度上就是这样。
what I would call performative
我称之为表演性的
masculinity and is not at the core of
男性气质并非其核心所在
what it means to be a man but can make
身为男人意味着什么，但也能做到
you more visible in the sexual
你在性方面更显眼
Marketplace like one of the regardless
市场就像其中之一，无论如何
of your udes toward traditional
你对传统的看法
masculinity or
男性气质或
femininity it makes that person more
女性气质使那个人更
visible to the opposite sex it's like by
对异性来说，这就像……
emphasizing what you might call um
强调你可能称之为“嗯”的东西。
sexual dimorphic characteristics what's
性二态性特征是什么
that that is a biological phenomenon
那是一种生物学现象
that says that males and females look
也就是说，男性和女性看起来
very different but not in all ways like
非常不同，但并非所有方面都相同
for example the peacock the male is the
例如，孔雀，雄性是
one with the bright plumage right right
右边那个羽毛鲜艳的
and so whereas the the pen the female
因此，尽管笔是雌性的。
doesn't have that and so a lot of the
没有那种功能，所以很多
attraction between peacock and PE hens
孔雀和PE母鸡之间的吸引力
is based on that plumage because it's
是根据那种羽毛来判断的，因为它
one way in which the males and females
男性和女性之间的一种方式
really differentiate themselves from
真正将自己与……区分开来
each other so it makes sense to stress
彼此之间，所以强调这一点是有意义的。
the most visible obvious differences
最明显的区别
from a biological perspective between
从生物学的角度来看
men and women to make that contrast more
男女之间的这种对比会更加明显
visible so I might get really big bicep
很明显，所以我的二头肌可能会变得非常粗壮
muscles because that's one of the big
因为那是主要肌肉之一。
sort of differences and she might get a
存在一些差异，她可能会得到……
boob job sure I mean yeah absolutely
隆胸手术？当然可以，我的意思是，绝对没问题。
that's one of the on some level issues
这是某种程度上的问题之一。
with respect to some of the the gender
就某些性别而言
conversations these days which is that
如今的谈话内容是……
when you move further away from these
当你离这些地方越来越远的时候
really obvious sexual signals it's
这是非常明显的性暗示。
harder to kind of even see you it's like
感觉甚至都很难看清你，就像……
well what are you and what do you want
你是什​​么人？你想要什么？
and what are you putting yourself out
你给自己设定了什么目标？
there for like it becomes more
因此，它变得更
individualistic becomes more custom
个人主义变得更加普遍
tailored which is harder to see at a
定制的，在……处更难看清。
distance and it's it's really important
距离，而且这一点真的很重要。
on some level to be able to kind of see
在某种程度上能够看到
things at a distance because there's an
远处的事物，因为存在一个
opportunity cost to approaching if I'm
如果我接近对方，机会成本是
going up to you and talking to you and
走到你面前和你说话
learning more about you I'm not doing
我不想更多地了解你。
that with anybody else at least for this
至少对其他人来说是这样。
moment in time right and so I kind of
那一刻，对吧？所以我有点……
want to feel like there's a reasonable
想要感觉有合理的
hope that if I go here I might find
希望我去那里能找到
something that I want or what I like
我想要的东西或我喜欢的东西
versus this is just curious I don't know
这只是我的好奇心，我不知道。
what this is the vast majority of people
这就是绝大多数人的情况
don't have the time and the energy to
没有时间和精力
really explore and entertain their
真正地探索和娱乐他们
curiosity they go where they need to go
好奇心驱使它们去往它们需要去的地方。
or they want to go so going back to that
或者他们想回去，所以就回到那个话题。
that starting point then one of the
那个起点，然后是其中一个
things that's emerged as a solution to
已经出现的解决方案
men I guess feeling lost about what it
我想男人可能会感到迷茫，不知道自己到底在做什么。
is to be a man is this performative
成为男人是一种表演吗？
masculinity in there we we we put people
那里有男性气质，我们把人放在那里
like you know I've heard you talk about
就像你知道的，我听你说过……
Andrew Tate being I don't think I've
安德鲁·泰特，我觉得我还没……
ever talked about Andrew really I
我曾经真的谈论过安德鲁吗？
thought it was on one of your videos
我以为是在你的某个视频里看到的。
that I saw on Tik Tok or something would
我在抖音之类的平台上看到的
you fit him in the category of per of
你把他归类为每……
performative masculinity I would fit him
表演型男子气概，我觉得很适合他。
in the CATE of a personality who's come
在一位性格的人的CATE中
to the Forefront to help men who might
走到最前线去帮助那些可能
be lost and confused to find their way
迷路，不知所措，找不到路
in navigating the current sexual
在应对当前的性问题时
Marketplace absolutely so he's he's
市场绝对如此，他就是这样。
offering a solution to navigating the
提供导航解决方案
current sexal Marketplace yeah and what
当前的性交易市场，是的，还有什么？
um what do you think of that solution I
嗯，你觉得这个方案怎么样？
don't follow I haven't followed Andrew
我没有关注安德鲁。
Tate very closely I've watched just a
我一直非常仔细地观察泰特。
few of his Clips I think he talked about
我记得他谈到过他的一些片段
acting in a way in such that your
以某种方式行事，以至于你的
ancestors would be proud if they were
如果他们是祖先，他们会感到自豪的。
watching you and I was like that's a
看着你，我就想，这真是……
pretty good piece of advice
很好的建议
mhm uh I actually follow very
嗯，我其实很关注。
few uh content creators online because
因为网上的内容创作者很少。
I'm trying to keep my content as um
我尽量保持我的内容……
original as possible I don't want to
尽量保持原样，我不想
necessarily just do reactions to other
不一定只是对其他事物做出反应
folks he's clearly a problematic
各位，他显然是个问题人物。
character like I think that he was
我觉得他就是这样的人。
indicted for sex trafficking in Europe
因在欧洲进行性交易而被起诉
correct yeah so I don't know the full
没错，所以我不清楚全部内容。
story but clearly people had he was both
故事，但显然人们都认为他既是……
loved and hated that's for sure just I
爱恨交织，这的确如此，我就是这样。
really want to just close from the point
真想就此结束。
of that the world that men find
那是人类所发现的世界。
themselves in before we move to the
在我们搬家之前，他们自己先……
world that women find themselves in and
女性所处的世界
then try and tackle some of those
然后尝试解决其中的一些问题。
problems so um they're lost in terms of
问题在于，嗯，他们在哪些方面迷失了方向？
understanding what masculinity is we
理解什么是男子气概
know that there's been they're finding
知道他们一直在寻找
it harder to find
更难找到
dates um they're finding it harder to
约会，嗯，他们发现越来越难了
have sort of sexual relationships is
有某种性关系是
there anything else that I need to
还有其他需要我注意的吗？
understand about the the man in the
了解这个男人。
current social climate well I think the
当前的社会氛围，嗯，我认为
the problem for the vast majority of men
绝大多数男性面临的问题是
as especially young men is their
尤其是年轻男性
invisibility most men are
大多数男人都隐形了
wallpaper and the world does not treat
壁纸和世界并不对待
men very well when they want nothing
男人如果什么都不想要，那就很好了。
from them I talk about that in the very
我从他们那里谈到这一点，非常
first pages of the book that to
这本书的前几页是……
understand why some people are rich in
了解为什么有些人富有
relationship opportunities whether
建立关系的机会
they're romantic professional friendship
他们之间既有浪漫的感情，也有专业的友谊。
Etc and other people are not it's not
等等，其他人不是这样，不是这样的
correct to say that it's the good people
没错，正是好人。
who have relationship opportunities or
有建立人脉机会的人或
The Virtuous people it's the people that
有德之人，就是那些……
other people want things from that have
其他人想要从那些拥有……的东西。
relationship opportunities if you have
如果你有关系机会的话
more of what other people want more you
更多别人想要的东西，更多你
are going to have relationship
将会建立关系
opportunities throughout your lifespan
一生中的机会
and that's very difficult because
这非常困难，因为
imagine being an 18-year-old man you
想象一下你是一个18岁的男人
have no money and you've never had money
你没钱，而且你从来就没有钱。
you may not have a job you may never
你可能没有工作，你可能永远
have had a job so you have no skills
你曾经有过工作，所以你没有任何技能
you're kind of invisible to women
你对女人来说几乎是隐形的。
because you don't have yet anything that
因为你还没有拥有任何东西。
women might find conducive for a
女性可能会发现这有利于……
long-term relationship if you're cute
如果你长得可爱，就能谈一场长期的恋爱。
they might hook up with you but if
他们可能会和你发生关系，但如果
you're not even that I mean why waste
你甚至都算不上，我的意思是，为什么要浪费时间？
their opportunity why waste their time
他们的机会，为什么要浪费时间？
when there are other more attractive
当有其他更具吸引力的选择时
options
选项
available and you're also kind of
有空，而且你也挺……
useless to most men because you don't
对大多数男人来说没用，因为你没有
yet have the skills and the experience
但具备相应的技能和经验
to be a good team player like I wouldn't
要像我一样成为一个优秀的团队成员，我不会
want you on my squad if you've never
如果你从未……我希望你加入我的团队。
been out in the field you're going to be
如果你已经在实地考察过了，你将会……
a liability you know what I'm saying I
你明白我的意思吗？我是个累赘。
don't have to carry your ass off the
你不用自己扛着屁股离开
field so you can't be here either and
所以你也不能在这里，因为这里是空的。
that creates a obviously the Catch 22
这显然造成了一种进退两难的困境。
which is well where am I going to get
那我该从哪里得到呢？
the experience if no one gives me a shot
如果没人给我机会，那我的经历会是怎样的？
it's actually very difficult to be a
实际上，成为一名……非常困难。
young man you don't have
年轻人，你没有
what either women or more experienced
无论是女性还是更有经验的人
men want or need and you're generally
男人想要或需要的，而你通常是
very disposable and unfortunately we've
非常容易被丢弃，不幸的是，我们已经
seen that I mean
明白我的意思
young men have a very
年轻男性非常
high mortality rate in all kinds of ways
各种方面的死亡率都很高。
they were shipped off to Wars you talked
他们被运往你所说的战争地区。
about the suicide epidemic among older
关于老年人自杀率上升的问题
men well it's also very high among
男性中，这个比例也很高。
adolescent boys as
青春期男孩
well it's hard to be a young man I
做个年轻人真不容易。
remember one of my guests telling me
记得我的一位客人跟我说过
that they about a study where they
他们正在进行一项研究，其中他们
analyzed the suicide letters of men and
分析了男性的遗书
they looked at the words used versus the
他们对比了所用词语和……
words used in female suicide letters and
女性遗书中使用的词语和
the T the most sort of fre sentiment
T 是最常见的自由情感
amongst those letters was about feeling
其中一封信是关于感受的。
worthless feeling like you weren't
觉得自己毫无价值，好像自己什么都不是
needed and the the guest on the podcast
需要嘉宾参与播客节目
concluded that really what we needed to
最终得出结论，我们真正需要的是
find a way is to send a message to men
找到方法就是向男人传递信息。
that you're needed and it's a strange
你需要被需要，这很奇怪
thing to say but it but it correlates
想说的是，但它与此相关。
perfectly to what you were saying the
完全同意你刚才说的话
message sounds good but it would be
信息听起来不错，但会是
better to actually have opportunities to
最好是能有机会
be needed yeah than to be told that you
比起被告知，你更需要。
are needed and that you are valued and
你需要被需要，你也很重要。
that you are cared for that's a nice
有人照顾你，这真是一件好事。
emotional sentiment that doesn't really
并非真正意义上的情感
keep the demons away at night people
人们，晚上要驱赶恶魔。
need to feel connected to other people
需要感受到与他人的联系
they need to feel like they have a place
他们需要感到自己有归属感。
in the world and it can take quite some
在世界上，这可能需要相当长的时间。
time to discover that what I've one of
是时候发现我拥有的其中之一了
the traps that I fell into when I was a
我小时候掉进的那些陷阱
young man is I thought that I could
年轻人，我以为我可以
figure that out by just sort of like
想办法弄明白，就像……
noodling it out alone in my room like I
我一个人在房间里琢磨着，就像……
I was trying to figure out what I wanted
我当时在努力弄清楚自己想要什么。
my life to be about what the purpose of
我的人生意义在于……
my life was going to be before I even
我的生命在我出生之前就已经注定了。
left the house and I wasted a lot of
离开家后，我浪费了很多时间
time in fruitless rumination that way
那样浪费时间进行徒劳的思考
it's much better to discover your
最好是自己去发现你的
purpose in life by moving through the
通过经历以下过程找到人生目标
world and examining your choices in
探索世界并审视你的选择
retrospect it's like you only really get
回想起来，就好像你只有真正得到
to discover Who You Are by examining and
通过审视和发现你是谁
understanding your revealed
理解你所揭示的
preferences based on your behavior As
基于你的行为的偏好
you move through the world it's very
你穿梭于世界各地，这非常
easy to think of yourself in all kinds
很容易把自己想象成各种各样的人
of ways when you're untested when you're
当你未经考验时，有很多方法可以做到。
untried when you're in the morally
当你处于道德困境时，未经尝试
ambiguous situations in which human
人类所处的模糊情境
beings find themselves as they navigate
众生在航行中逐渐发现自己
reality
现实
are you saying that the evidence you're
你是说你提供的证据……
looking for or the answers you're
你正在寻找的答案
looking for come from taking action
寻求通过行动获得回报
absolutely they don't come from thinking
它们绝对不是来自思考。
it
它
out they often don't come from therapy
它们通常并非来自治疗
and that might sound weird coming from a
这话从某人嘴里说出来可能有点奇怪
therapist but I do think that we live in
但我确实认为我们生活在治疗师的掌控之中
a very overly therapized culture with
过度依赖心理治疗的文化
the understanding that therapy is
对治疗的理解是
somewhat of a Panacea in that it should
它在某种程度上是一种万灵药，因为它应该
be able to cure all that ails you and I
能够治愈你我所有的疾病
don't think that that's true therapy is
不要认为那是真正的治疗。
very good for certain problems and it's
非常适合解决某些问题，而且它
useless for others what about women what
对别人没用，那女人呢？
are the challenges that a woman faces in
是女性在以下方面面临的挑战
the modern world because of all these
现代世界正是因为所有这些原因。
sort of macro changes that have taken
已经发生的一些宏观变化
place well the main problem that I see
很好地解决了我看到的主要问题。
women encountering at least in my
至少在我的生活中，女性遇到的情况是这样的。
consultative practice is they have
咨询实践是他们拥有的
trouble finding the men that they want
找不到自己想要的男人
to have long-term relationships
建立长期关系
with uh almost every consultation I've
几乎每次咨询我都
done with a woman has been around how do
和一个女人在一起已经很久了，该怎么做？
I get a man to marry
我找了个男人结婚
me and that's also kind of strange
我也觉得这有点奇怪。
because I would think 80 100 years ago
因为我觉得80到100年前
that was something that that girl was
那是那个女孩的特质。
being prepared for since she was a very
因为她从小就为此做好准备，所以她非常
young person by her mother and her
这位年轻女孩由她的母亲和她抚养长大
grandmother and her aunts and her female
祖母、她的姑姑和她的女性
relatives with whom she probably lived
她可能和亲戚们住在一起
in close
近距离
consultation and she never would have
咨询，她永远不会有
gotten to the age of 30 where this would
到了30岁，这种情况就会发生。
be an open question still and who are
这仍然是一个悬而未决的问题，以及他们是谁
you what's your sort of I if I looked at
你是哪种类型的我？如果我看着你
your you know you talked about your
你知道你谈到了你的
consultative practice what is the
什么是咨询实践？
experiences you've had and the education
你的经历和教育
you've had that have brought you to this
你所经历的一切把你带到了这里。
point where you've written this book
你写这本书的起点
about relationships and those Dynamics
关于人际关系和这些动态
what is your sort of professional
你从事哪方面的专业工作？
personal experience well professionally
个人经验和专业能力
I'm a psychologist I'm licensed in the
我是一名心理学家，持有执照。
state of California so I went to grad
所以我去了加利福尼亚州读大学
school and got a doctorate in Psychology
在学校获得心理学博士学位
I had all kinds of training experiences
我有过各种各样的培训经历。
while I was moving through that I worked
在我经历那段时期的时候，我工作了
at a chemical dependency clinic for two
在一家化学依赖诊所接受两人治疗
years I worked with cancer patients in
多年来，我一直与癌症患者一起工作
their caregivers in a health psychology
他们的照护者在健康心理学中
setting for a couple years I worked with
我曾在一家公司工作过几年。
significant dysfunction in a Community
社区中存在严重的功能障碍
Mental Health Center in San Francisco
旧金山心理健康中心
for a while I worked in outpatient with
我曾在门诊部工作过一段时间。
severe personality
性格严厉
disorders so that was all part of my
所以，这些都是我疾病的一部分。
training and then when I started my
训练，然后当我开始我的
private practice I began to focus on
我开始专注于私人执业
men's mental health and for a long time
男性心理健康，而且长期以来
when I was a therapist I worked
我当心理治疗师的时候工作过
exclusively with men that's changed a
仅限男性，这改变了
little bit now that uh I have a kind of
现在我有点……
a larger platform on which to reach
一个更大的平台，以便达成目标
reach people
接触人们
um but that's sort of been my
嗯，但那算是我的
professional experience so in your
专业经验，所以你的
private practice when people come to you
私人执业，人们会来找你。
what what are men most frequently coming
男人最常说的是什么
to you with in terms of the problem they
就他们遇到的问题而言，他们
come with versus what women come to you
与女人主动接近你相比，主动接近你的女人是什么样的呢？
with a problem with well in general it's
总的来说，存在一个问题。
either money or women for men oh really
对男人来说，要么是钱，要么是女人，真的吗？
yeah and this is nothing new like Sigman
是的，这没什么新鲜的，就像西格曼一样。
Freud said a long time ago that the
弗洛伊德很久以前就说过，
purpose of
目的
psychoanalysis was to teach people how
精神分析的目的是教人们如何
to work and how to love that's it if you
工作和如何去爱，仅此而已，如果你
can learn how to work and love you can
可以学会如何工作和爱你
be a fairly functional human being in
成为一个相当能干的人
society and have a satisfying life and
社会化并拥有令人满意的生活
he also said that the goal of therapy
他还说，治疗的目标是
was not to cure suffering per se which
并非为了治愈痛苦本身，
might be Inseparable from The Human
或许与人类密不可分
Experience but to free human beings from
经验，但是为了将人类从……中解放出来
neurotic unnecessary suffering so that
神经质的、不必要的痛苦，以至于
they are better equipped to meet the
他们更有能力应对这种情况
necessary suffering and pain of being
存在的必要苦难和痛苦
alive so he had I think a more
他还活着，所以我认为他还有更多
attenuated vision for what therapy could
视力减弱，需要进行哪些治疗？
do so it's either money work or women
这样做要么是为了钱，要么是为了工作，要么是为了女人。
love and what I found is that it's
爱，以及我发现的，是
either one or the other I often did
我经常做其中之一。
consultations with guys who were super
和一些非常棒的人咨询
successful professionally they were
他们在事业上取得了成功
making millions but they were in failed
他们赚了数百万美元，但却失败了。
marriage after failed marriage or they
失败婚姻后的再婚，或者他们
couldn't for the life of them get laid
他们无论如何都无法和人发生性关系
even if they were having parties with
即使他们当时正在举办派对
models on their super Yachts you know
你知道，模特们在他们的超级游艇上。
what I'm saying MH by the same token
我的意思是，MH 也同样如此。
there are there are fewer of them
它们的数量比较少。
because they couldn't afford my out-of
因为他们负担不起我的外出费用
pocket rate but it's like there were
口袋价，但感觉就像有
some men who were just absolutely
有些男人简直太……
cleaning up like I've done some
像我一样打扫干净
consultations I had some some patients
我曾为一些病人提供咨询。
young men who were just
那些刚出生不久的年轻人
like plowing through San Francisco I
就像在旧金山横冲直撞一样
mean they had sexual success in a way
这意味着他们在某种程度上获得了性方面的成功。
that most men would just fantasize about
大多数男人只会幻想这件事。
but they had a really hard time getting
但他们获取信息的过程非常艰难。
their money straight their career um
他们的钱直接用于他们的事业
they were super stressed out they had
他们压力非常大，他们
anxiety disorders things like that which
焦虑症之类的疾病
is actually fairly ironic because what I
这其实相当讽刺，因为我
found is if it works in one domain It
发现它是否在一个领域有效。
generally works in the other interesting
通常在其他有趣的方面也有效。
so if I get my work right then I'll get
所以如果我把工作做好，我就能得到
my love right if it works in business it
我的爱，如果它在商业上行得通的话。
often works with women what do you mean
经常与女性合作，你的意思是？
sorry well think about it this way men
抱歉，伙计们，你们换个角度想想。
want sex and they want relationships
他们想要性，也想要恋爱关系。
from women women don't go around giving
女性不会到处送礼物
those things out to men just because
那些东西是给男人的，仅仅因为
they want them okay so what's the anal
他们想要它们，好吧，那么肛门是什么？
problem in the professional Arena which
专业领域中的问题
is I want money let's say you're a
我想要钱，假设你是一个
Salesman I want money I have this
推销员，我想要钱，我有这个
product or I have this service I want
我想要的产品或服务
people to hire me I want people to buy
人们想雇佣我，我想让人们购买
it well people aren't just going around
人们并非只是四处走动。
with their wallets out saying who's
他们掏出钱包，说着谁是……
going to take my money you know what I'm
你要拿走我的钱，你知道我的意思吗？
saying so you have to find a way to get
所以，你必须想办法获得
what you want from the people that you
你想要从你身边的人那里得到什么
want it from and a lot of the strategies
想要从很多方面获得它以及许多策略
that work in business to do that will
在商业领域从事这项工作将会
work in the sexual Marketplace as well
在性交易市场工作
interesting that's um that's that's very
很有意思，嗯，这很……
very true because I I think I told you
确实如此，因为我想我已经跟你说过。
before we started recording When I Was I
在我们开始录制《当我还是我的时候》之前
don't know 18 there was this pickup
不知道18号那里有没有这辆皮卡
Artistry book sent to my house that I
我收到了一本寄到家里的艺术画册。
think my brother my older brother had
我想我哥哥，我哥哥曾经
ordered but he ordered it to the wrong
他点了单，但却点错了。
address because he had moved out to
因为他已经搬出去了，所以需要改地址。
University so he said just keep it lucky
所以他说，大学就祝你好运吧
accident for you yeah and I sat there
对你来说，这是一场意外，而我当时就坐在那里。
and I read it cover to cover without
我一口气读完了它。
moving and actually much of the
搬家，实际上大部分
principles I learned about pickup
我从搭讪中学到的原则
Artistry about attraction about being a
关于吸引力的艺术性
high value male are actually things that
高价值男性实际上是以下特质：
I took into business when it comes to
我进入商业领域时，谈到了
negotiation sales persuasion and all
谈判、销售、说服等等
those things so I do see that
那些事情我确实看到了。
translation well another thing is that
翻译方面还有一点需要说明。
often when I say
经常当我说
because people have all kinds of
因为人们有各种各样的
associations with pickup they think it's
他们认为搭讪是……
kind of sleazy and it's especially for
有点低俗，尤其如此
guys who couldn't get laid otherwise and
那些否则就无法获得性满足的男人们
so they have to use manipulative tactics
所以他们不得不使用操纵手段。
to get what they want it's like okay
为了得到他们想要的东西，就好像……好吧
well yeah welcome to advertising right
没错，欢迎来到广告界。
yeah so that's one side of it they think
是的，这是他们认为的其中一方面。
that those strategies just work to get
这些策略确实有效，可以达到
laate or to have casual sexual
迟到或发生随意性行为
relationships no they often also work in
关系中，他们也经常在工作。
longterm relationships not only because
长期关系不仅仅是因为
generally the pathway to a long-term
通常是通往长期的途径
relationship is through a more casual
这种关系是通过一种更随意的方式建立起来的。
arrangement
安排
usually people date and hang out and
通常人们会约会、出去玩，
sleep together for some weeks some
他们一起睡了几个星期
months before they Define the
几个月前，他们定义了
relationship right so they kind of for
关系对，所以他们有点为了
better for worse have to go through that
无论好坏，都必须经历这一切。
Proving Ground before they get to here
在他们到达这里之前，这里是试验场。
right but like it's really important for
对，但这真的很重要
long-term relationships it's one of the
长期关系是其中之一
principles for long-term success is
长期成功的原则是
complimentarity of skill sets it's like
技能互补就像
if you're a startup founder you want
如果你是一名创业公司创始人，你肯定希望
somebody who can do very well the things
能够把这些事情做得非常好的人
that you cannot do
你不能这样做
like having two CEOs is just a recipe
拥有两位CEO就像是一种配方
for competition struggle and strife
为了竞争、斗争和冲突
right yeah so you need people with
对，所以你需要一些有……的人
complimentary skill sets in order to go
互补的技能组合以便出行
the distance in my experience 90% of
根据我的经验，90% 的距离
successful relationships are based on
成功的关系建立在……之上
selection if you can understand
如果你能理解的话，请选择
yourself accurate self- knowledge and
准确的自我认知和
you get better at Discerning other
你会越来越擅长辨别他人
people you can have satisfying
你可以和那些让你感到满足的人相处
relationships with lots of different
与许多不同事物建立关系
human beings we're going to get into
我们将要进入​​的人类世界
figuring out how you do that but but on
弄清楚你是怎么做到的，但是……
the point I asked you there I said what
我当时问你，我说的是什么？
do men come to you with in terms of
男人会就此和你交谈吗？
problem sets and you said money and
问题集，你提到了金钱和
women ideally sort of work in work in
女性理想情况下应该从事某种工作。
women work in love so what do women come
女人在爱情中工作，那么女人会做什么呢？
to you they want to get married so they
他们想和你结婚，所以他们
just come to you with the love problems
我只是带着爱情问题来找你。
yeah I mean they do that now because I I
是的，我的意思是他们现在这样做是因为我
talk about lots of things on my channel
我的频道会聊很多事情
but by far the most successful videos
但迄今为止最成功的视频
are the ones about intersexual Dynamics
是关于两性关系动态的那些
and so that's kind of what I'm known for
所以，这就是我为人所知的原因。
and so there is a bit of a selection
所以，这里还是有一些选择的。
bias there is the most popular videos
偏见在于最热门的视频
are me talking about men and women and
我是在谈论男人和女人吗？
so increasingly men and women come to me
所以越来越多的男人和女人来找我。
about their relationship issues right so
关于他们的关系问题，没错。
that makes sense but women use therapy
这很有道理，但女性也会接受治疗。
for all kinds of different reasons right
出于各种不同的原因，对吧？
we know that women are by far bigger
我们知道女性的体型远大于男性。
consumers of therapeutic services in
治疗服务消费者
particular like actually going to
特别喜欢真的去
therapy and also more generally like
治疗，以及更广泛意义上的治疗
they make up the line share of consumers
它们构成了消费者的市场份额。
for just self-help material in general
一般而言，仅指自助类材料。
like a big market for that kind
就像一个巨大的市场
of self- betterment and self-improvement
自我提升和自我完善
in the female
在女性中
Marketplace and we also know that about
市场，我们也知道这一点
85% of mental health practitioners are
85%的心理健康从业者是
women like when I was in my training I
像我训练时那样的女性
think I was one of three people in my
我想我是那三个人之一
cohort that were
该队列
men uh I would interview at some
呃，我会去面试一些男士职位。
placements where there weren't any men
那些没有男性的安置地点
at all on the staff
全体员工
whatsoever and just like I can
无论如何，就像我可以一样
appreciate that women might not feel
要理解女性可能没有这种感觉
entirely comfortable going to a man with
完全可以放心地去找一个男人
certain of their issues I know for sure
我确信他们存在某些问题。
that there's plenty of men who wouldn't
有很多男人不会
feel comfortable going to a woman about
觉得和一位女士谈论这件事很自在
some of their
他们中的一些人
concerns so when they talk about why you
所以当他们谈到你的原因时，你会感到担忧。
often hear it's usually women they're
经常听到，通常是女性。
dissatisfied with
对……不满意
men's lack of interest in going to
男性对去……缺乏兴趣
therapy men would literally want to
接受治疗的男士们真的会想要
refurbish a train then go to therapy and
翻新一列火车，然后去做心理治疗。
talk about their feelings well it's
好好谈谈他们的感受
partly it's because there aren't a lot
部分原因是数量不多。
of male practitioners and I think what's
男性从业者，我认为是什么？
good for men isn't always what's good
对男人好的东西，未必就是对所有人都好的东西。
for women and vice versa what's good for
对女性而言，反之亦然，什么对……有利？
the goose isn't always what's good for
鹅并不总是最好的选择
the gander what I found is that women
我发现，女性
generally talk to process their emotions
他们通常会通过交谈来处理自己的情绪
and they're
他们是
more keen on emotionally focused
更倾向于情感方面的
strategies right whereas men they try to
正确的策略，而男人则试图……
resolve things through action and
通过行动解决问题
through
通过
solution and they often see that just
解决方案，他们经常看到，只需
talking about their problems and paying
谈论他们的问题并付费
for the opportunity to do so to be a
有机会这样做
complete waste of time and money and I
完全是浪费时间和金钱，而且我
can understand why now it does have its
现在我明白了为什么它确实有它
place like it's very important for some
这个地方对某些人来说非常重要。
men to be able to have a safe space to
让男性能够拥有一个安全的空间
really share their experience and talk
他们真正分享了自己的经历并进行了交流。
about this stuff because man they can be
关于这些事，因为它们确实可能
judged harshly if they open up to the
如果他们向别人敞开心扉，就会受到严厉的评判。
wrong people so there's a time and a
错的人，所以会有时机和……
place for that for men as well but it's
这里也适合男性，但是……
generally not every week for several
通常不是每周都这样，持续好几周。
years so let's go into those two those
几年了，所以我们来谈谈那两个方面。
three different problems then so if a
三个不同的问题，那么如果
man comes to you and they are expressing
男人来到你面前，他们表达着
an issue with love they're trying to get
他们试图解决的爱情问题
laid they're trying to find someone um
他们躺着，正在努力寻找某人。
where does where do you start what are
从哪里开始？有哪些内容？
the sort of foundational things you need
你需要的那些基础知识
them to understand for you to all get
让他们明白，这样你们所有人都能明白
focused in the right direction well
朝着正确的方向努力
usually start with what they've tried in
通常从他们尝试过的事情开始
the past and where in the funnel they
过去以及它们在漏斗中的位置
tend to be experiencing their
往往正在经历他们的
difficulties like there's a the advice
困难之处包括建议
is very different if you're not getting
如果你没有得到，情况就大不相同了。
any matches on a dating app or you
在约会软件上的任何匹配对象，或者你
haven't been able to get a date in
一直没能约到会。
months versus I can get with women but
几个月后我就可以和女人交往了，但是
after 3 months everything kind of seems
三个月后，一切似乎都好多了。
to fall apart or I'm able everyone just
崩溃或者我能做到每个人都只是
wants me for these long-term
希望我长期从事这些工作
relationships and I just want to be able
人际关系，我只是想能够
to play the field so it's really
为了多方涉猎，所以这真的
depending on the goals of the man in
这取决于该男子的目标
question and where he's experiencing the
问题以及他正在经历什么
difficulties so if he's at the top of
困难重重，所以如果他处于顶峰……
the funnel so when we talk about funnels
漏斗，所以当我们谈论漏斗时
um if we have the top of the funnel is
嗯，如果我们有漏斗的顶部是
you know you're meeting people maybe a
你知道你可能会遇到一些人
little bit further down the funnel is
漏斗再往下一点是
you're you know having some kind of
你知道，你好像有点……
relationship with them short term and
与他们建立短期关系
then at the very bottom of the funnel
然后，在漏斗的最底部
might be like marriage and kids sure um
可能就像结婚生子一样，嗯……
so at the very top so if they come in at
所以，在最顶端，如果他们进来的话
the top of the funnel and they've got
漏斗顶部，他们有
problems just like meeting
问题就像会议一样
people where where did you start that's
人们，你们是从哪里开始的？
a tough one I think it's a good idea in
我觉得这是个难题，但我认为是个好主意。
today's day and age to have kind of a
如今这个时代，有一种……
dual strategy I think that you can use
我认为你可以使用双重策略。
the apps for what the apps are good for
这些应用程序的用途
but overly relying on them as a solution
但过度依赖它们作为解决方案
for your dating wos is probably not
你的约会对象可能不是
correct you're going to have to get out
没错，你必须离开。
there and get better at your people's
在那里，努力提升自己，更好地服务于你的人民。
skills because even if you do match with
技能，因为即使你与……匹配
somebody if you're more of an introvert
如果你比较内向，可以找个人聊聊。
if you have a lot of social anxiety even
即使你患有严重的社交焦虑症
if you manage to get someone off the app
如果你设法让某人卸载了该应用程序。
into the real world you might be able to
进入现实世界，你或许能够
blow it because you're going to be
搞砸了，因为你将会……
nervous you're going to be uncharismatic
担心自己缺乏魅力
you're not going to know how to lead the
你不会知道如何领导
encounter in the direction of a sexual
朝着性方向的遭遇
experience if that's what you're looking
如果您正在寻找经验，那就来这里吧。
for so it's generally a good idea to get
因此，通常来说，获取这些信息是个好主意。
out out there um there's really no
外面，嗯，真的没有
antidote there's no there's no better
没有解药，没有更好的办法。
solution than doing it it's just like
与其这样做，不如试试其他方法，就像……
learning a language you have to speak it
学习一门语言，你必须会说它。
you're going to make a lot of mistakes
你会犯很多错误
you're going to be embarrassed it's
你会感到尴尬的。
going to feel frustrating and impossible
会感到沮丧和不可能
until it doesn't so unfortunately
直到它不再如此，真是太可惜了。
everything that you can say or read or
你能说的、能读的或
listen to is just Prelude to going out
听着只是外出前的序曲
there and doing it and failing enough
在那里，去做，并且失败得足够多次。
times and learning from your mistakes
时间以及从错误中吸取教训
until you have a reasonable hit rate but
直到你拥有合理的命中率为止，但是
how do I increase my probability that a
如何提高我的概率
woman will give me that chance and then
女人会给我这个机会，然后
stick with me like how do I increase my
跟我一起努力，比如我该如何增加我的
chance of being
成为
attractive all things I can do do I need
所有我能做的事情都很有吸引力，我需要
to go hit the gym sure like what I talk
去健身房？当然可以，就像我说话一样。
about in the book is that everyone can
书中提到的一点是，每个人都可以
be more attractive than they currently
比他们现在更有吸引力
are and if you're having a problem in
如果您遇到问题，请联系我们。
that initial funnel it's generally a
最初的那个漏斗通常是一个
marketing issue because think about it
营销问题，想想看
on an app it's six pictures and three
在应用程序上，有六张图片和三个
responses in a meat market it's hey how
肉市上的回应是：嘿，怎么样？
you doing it's like she's going to give
你这样做就像她要给
me a once over she already gave me the
她已经上下打量了我一番，给了我……
side eye and she's going to kind of make
她斜眼看了看，然后她就要……
a snap judgment based on the vibe that
根据感觉做出的仓促判断
I'm giving out right neither one of
我不会给任何人任何机会
those has anything to do with really who
这些跟谁真的有关系？
I am as a person that's one of the
我个人就是其中之一
things is that they can't really reject
问题在于他们无法真正拒绝
you because they haven't spent any time
你，因为他们没有花任何时间
getting to know you For Better or For
更好地了解你
Worse if they like you or not they like
更糟糕的是，不管他们喜不喜欢你，他们都喜欢
the idea of you they like the
他们喜欢你的想法
presentation of you and it's really
你的展示真的很棒
important not to disabuse people of that
重要的是不要使人们对这一点失去信心。
presentation too quickly okay so to
演示速度太快了，好吧。
think about your exterior marketing
考虑一下你的外部营销
absolutely okay because that's what men
完全没问题，因为男人就是这样。
do I mean they don't go up to women
我的意思是，他们不会主动接近女性。
randomly they think oh man she's pretty
他们突然觉得，哇，她真漂亮。
cute right they're paying attention to
很可爱，他们正在关注
the surface marketing as well what can I
表面营销以及我能做什么
do with my Surface marketing to make me
利用我的 Surface 营销来让我
more
更多的
attractive well you got to focus on what
有吸引力？那你得专注于什么？
you can control because generally when
你可以控制，因为通常情况下
we go down this road what I hear from
我们沿着这条路走下去，我听到的
men online is well that's all well and
男人在网上……嗯，一切都很好。
good Orion but I'm 56 you know I'm
奥赖恩不错，但我已经56岁了，你知道的。
balding women aren't going to like me
秃顶的女人不会喜欢我
and it's like yeah if you don't have
就像，如果你没有……
some of the genetic markers it is more
有些基因标记更是如此。
difficult but everyone can get
虽然很难，但人人都能做到。
better at what they do and on some level
他们更擅长自己所做的事情，并且在某种程度上
the less conventionally attractive that
不太传统意义上的吸引力
you are the more you have to learn
你学得越多，你就越优秀。
seduction the more you have to learn
诱惑之道，你需要学习的越多。
game you have to think about the fact
玩游戏时你必须考虑到这一点
that attractiveness is not normally
这种吸引力通常并非如此。
distributed across any population right
分布于任何人口权利
there's going to be a small subset of
将会有一小部分
men and women who are just absolutely
那些绝对的男男女女
gorgeous some of that are wow that's
有些太美了，哇！
interesting and most people are kind of
有趣，而且大多数人都是这样。
in the middle right
在中间偏右的位置
and seduction is the process of being
而诱惑的过程就是如此
able to direct
能够指导
attention to your purposes and the more
关注您的目标，以及更多
that you can learn how to direct
你可以学习如何执导。
attention for your purposes the more
越关注你的目的越好
that you can overcome some of the
你可以克服一些
liabilities associated with being let's
与“让我们”相关的责任
say in the fat part of the curve when it
比如说在曲线的较厚部分，当
comes to attractiveness okay so how do I
说到吸引力，好吧，那我该怎么做呢？
do that well you have to kind of learn
要想做好这一点，你必须学习。
what works I think one of the things
我认为有效的方法之一是……
that all men can learn from the pickup
所有男人都能从搭讪中学到东西
Community is that they were basically
社区基本上就是他们
behavioral scientists some of them went
行为科学家们，其中一些人去了
to the field and said okay if I knew
到场边，我说如果我知道的话，那就好。
what I was doing I'd be laid by now you
我当时在做什么，我现在应该已经躺下了。
know I'd have I'd be a washing
我知道我会洗干净。
optionality so maybe I don't know what
可选性，所以也许我不知道什么
women want maybe I don't know what works
女人想要什么？也许我不知道什么方法有效。
let's let the outcome teach me what I
让结果来告诉我我该怎么做
should believe as opposed to going to
应该相信而不是去
women with a preconceived notion about
对女性抱有先入为主观念
what should work or what they should
什么应该有效，或者他们应该
want and that's why on some level you
想要，所以在某种程度上你
got what on the surface seems like some
表面上看似乎是一些
ridiculous strategies like peacocking
像孔雀开屏这样的荒谬策略
you know it's like some men look at that
你知道，有些男人就是这么看那个的。
and I would never do that that's just so
我绝不会那样做，那太荒谬了。
ostentatious and extravagant but it can
炫耀和铺张浪费，但它可以
attract attention that's a very let's
吸引注意力，这真是太好了
say uh heavy-handed way to do so for
呃，这是一种过于强硬的做法。
someone that doesn't know what
不知道什么的人
peacocking is how you describe you know
炫耀就是你形容你知道的方式。
dressing a little bit more flamboyantly
穿着打扮稍微张扬一些
to attract attention or like a
吸引注意力或喜欢
flamboyant feature or like it could be a
华丽的特征，或者就像它可能是一个
crazy hat you have could be a crazy hat
你戴的那顶怪异的帽子可能是一顶怪异的帽子
flavor flave had the big clock around
风味风味有一个大钟
his NE I I don't know if I just dated
他的东北部，我不知道我是否刚刚约会过
myself with that reference but um
我自己也参考了这个例子，但是……
there's and sometimes it's just looking
有时只是看看而已。
sharp I mean by far one of the best
锋利无比，我的意思是，绝对是最好的之一。
things that men can do is just spend one
男人能做的事情之一就是花一个小时
or two thousand bucks to get like two or
或者花两千美元买两个或
three really good outfits you can just
三套非常好的服装，你可以直接穿。
cycle through them when you're dating
约会时轮流使用它们
especially in some marketplaces La is
尤其是一些市场 La 是
tough New York is tough but it is so
纽约很艰难，但它也如此
easy to be the Best Dressed Man in San
成为旧金山最佳着装男士轻而易举
Francisco I swear to God it does not
弗朗西斯科，我向上帝发誓，这绝不可能。
take that much effort and if you're the
付出这么多努力，如果你是……
best dressed man in the room you get
房间里最会穿衣的男人
like one free point can you imagine some
就像一个免费积分，你能想象吗？
women have to spend tens of thousands of
女性不得不花费数万
dollars on cosmetic surgery to get one
花几美元做整容手术，就能拥有一个
extra point some men just need to put
额外加分，有些男人只需要加分。
some clothes on and get a better haircut
穿上衣服，剪个更好的发型。
you know what I'm saying and they refuse
你知道我的意思，但他们拒绝
to do that for whatever reason what
无论出于何种原因，这样做是什么
other things should I be thinking about
我还应该考虑哪些其他事情？
in terms of Seduction if I want to be
就诱惑而言，如果我想成为
because one of the central things I need
因为我最需要的一件事就是
to understand as you said that the
正如你所说，要理解这一点
pickup artist Community learned is is
搭讪艺术家社区了解到是
what actually leads to the outcome
究竟是什么导致了最终结果
because if I was to ask a woman hey how
因为如果我问一个女人“嘿，你好吗？”
can I become more attractive to a woman
我怎样才能更吸引女人
I I guess what she might say to me is
我猜她可能会对我说的是
being nice be you know what I don't know
友善就是我不知道的事
I've asked that question to so many
我问过很多人这个问题。
women in my life and I've never gotten a
我生命中有很多女性，但我从未得到过
good answer because that's almost always
很好的答案，因为这几乎总是如此。
the response is I want a kind man I want
回应是：我想要一个善良的男人。
a man who is I feel safe with I want a
我想要一个让我感到安全的男人。
man who is loving and usually the guy in
一个温柔体贴的男人，通常是那个男人
question is listening to that and be
问题是听着，并且
like what the the problems like
到底他妈的有什么问题？
I'm I'm kind as like I don't get it
我心地善良得像个傻瓜，好像我根本不明白似的。
like I need to be kinder and they they
好像我需要对他们更友善一些，而他们……
start to into that even more and I don't
我开始更加沉迷其中，但我并不
think that these women are necessarily
认为这些女性必然是
lying to these men but they're leaving
我对这些人撒谎，但他们还是要离开。
out the most important part one of my
找出我最重要的部分之一
most popular YouTube videos is the part
最受欢迎的 YouTube 视频是其中一部分
that women always leave out that speaks
女人总是忽略这一点。
exactly to this problem which is that
正是针对这个问题，那就是
women do want those things that they
女人确实想要那些她们想要的东西。
list off when men ask them that question
列举男性问她们这个问题时的情况
they just want them from the men that
他们只是想从那些男人那里得到这些东西。
they're attracted
他们被吸引
to they want the men they're attracted
她们想要的是她们所吸引的男人。
to to be kind and to be loving and to be
要善良、要有爱心、要……
generous and to make them feel safe but
慷慨大方，让他们感到安全，但
it's not like being kind and generous
这跟善良慷慨不一样。
and making women feel safe is going to
让女性感到安全至关重要
lead them to feeling attracted to you
引导他们对你产生好感
and that's the part that women leave out
而这正是女性常常忽略的部分。
and men in their let's say naive but
而男人们，我们姑且称他们天真吧，但是
good-hearted intention to give women
出于好意，想给女性
what they want and to be a better mate
他们想要什么，以及如何成为更好的伴侣
for them they just totally lose out on
对他们来说，他们完全失去了机会。
so it's better to be attractive like if
所以最好长得漂亮些，比如
you want to be good at the game of
你想擅长玩……
mating and dating you have an easier
交配和约会更容易
time the more attractive that you
时间越长，你就越有吸引力。
present yourself you have an you get
展现你自己，你拥有并得到
more opportunities for selection you get
你将获得更多的选择机会
more beneficial Arrangements in the
更有利的安排
negotiation process and it's easier to
谈判过程更容易
maintain your relationship in the long
长期维持你们的关系
run against your intersexual competition
与你的异性竞争对手竞争
as well so there's all kinds of
所以还有各种各样的
Privileges and benefits to being
成为特权和好处
attractive and everyone can be more
更有吸引力，每个人都可以更……
attractive than they currently are what
比现在更有吸引力
do men need to do to be more attractive
男人需要做些什么才能更有吸引力
I think can learn to dress better I
我认为我可以学习如何穿衣打扮得更好。
think that they can take care of their
他们认为他们可以照顾好自己
physical fitness for some men it's as
对某些男性来说，体能状况是……
basic as hygiene you know what I'm
像卫生习惯一样基本的东西，你知道我的意思吗？
saying uh I think it's also really
我觉得这也真的
important to learn how to talk the
学习如何交谈很重要
most the most vulnerable organ in a
最脆弱的器官
woman to sedu seduction is her mind is
女人诱惑的手段是她内心的想法。
her brain like you that is her biggest
她的大脑就像你一样，那是她最大的优势。
ayous Zone and if you can learn to talk
ayous Zone，如果你能学会说话的话
to a woman in a way that women will
以女性会喜欢的方式对待女性
listen listen and respond to you'll be
听，听，并回应，你就会……
able to do all kinds of things and have
能够做各种各样的事情并且拥有
all kinds of
各种各样的
relationships what do I need to say well
人际关系，我需要说什么？
it's not a script right so one of the
这不是剧本，对吧？所以其中一个
it's a it's a lot about vibing like
这很大程度上是关于感觉的。
female feminine communication let's put
女性之间的沟通方式，我们来谈谈这个。
it that way feminine communication is
女性沟通的方式就是这样
very different from mask in
与面具截然不同
communication I'm not saying I'm I'm
沟通 我不是说我是我是
staying away from men and women because
远离男人和女人，因为
obviously men and women can do both but
显然，男人和女人都可以做这两件事，但是
mask and communication is about the
口罩和沟通是关于
conveyance of information using semantic
利用语义传递信息
words I know that the message has been
我知道这信息已经传达了。
received if you can more or less
收到，如果你能或多或少地收到的话
summarize that message back to me it's
请把那条信息总结一下。
like I understood the content of what
就像我理解了什么内容一样
you said transmission complete
你说传输完成
right feminine communication is very
正确的女性沟通方式非常重要
different it's more like emotional
不同，它更像是情感上的。
resonance and communication has been
共鸣和沟通一直是
received when I can succeed in provoking
当我成功激怒对方时，就会收到。
in you a comparable or analogous
在你身上有一个类似或相近的
emotional experience the one that I went
我经历的那次情感体验
through or I'm currently in you can
通过或者我目前在你可以
think of it like tuning Forks one of
把它想象成音叉之一
them is vibrating bring another one up
它们在震动，再带一个上来
to it it will start vibrating at the
它会开始振动。
same frequency as well and that's when
频率也相同，那时
you know that the communication has been
你知道沟通已经……
received and that's really important for
收到了，这真的很重要。
men to understand because that leads to
男人需要理解这一点，因为这会导致
a lot of disagreements and arguments
很多分歧和争论
between men and women in their long-term
男女之间的长期关系
relationships where Sometimes women are
有时女性在恋爱关系中
attempting to get men to feel the way
试图让男人产生这种感觉
that they currently feel but men are
他们目前感受到的，但男人是
paying attention to what they're
关注他们正在做什么
actually saying and they're saying why
他们实际上是这么说的，而且他们还在解释原因。
are you bringing this up now or that's
你现在要提起这件事吗？还是以后再说？
not factually accurate
不符合事实
I don't understand and it's because of
我不明白，这是因为……
this failure of intersexual
这种性发育失败
understanding the woman is trying to
理解这位女士试图
provoke in the man the emotional state
激起男人的情绪状态
so that he can understand like in his
这样他就能像在他自己那里一样理解了。
bones what it feels like to have been
骨头，感觉就像曾经是
her in that moment but the men are just
那一刻她很在意，但男人们却只是
paying some men are just so literal
付钱给某些男人，他们就太较真了。
they're so functionally fixed on the
它们在功能上是如此固定。
semantic content of language and the
语言的语义内容及其
truth is that words are both words
事实是，词语本身就是词语。
always have this defined semantic
始终具有这种定义的语义
meaning but they also are in different
意思是，但它们也处于不同的状态。
containers of emotion like every word
每一个词都承载着情感。
can be said with any different emotional
可以用任何不同的情感来表达
content
内容
possible you can say the word please
或许你可以说“请”这个词。
seductively you can say the word please
你可以用诱惑的语气说“请”。
threateningly you can say the word
你可以威胁地说出这个词
please pathetically I mean that's What
拜托，可悲的是，我的意思是，那是什么？
actors do right they invest this script
演员们尽职尽责，他们投入到这个剧本中。
which are just words on a page with
这只是纸上的一些文字而已。
emotional content and that's what makes
情感内容，而这正是它的意义所在。
their performance
他们的表演
enchanting if you can do both if you can
如果你能两者兼顾，那就太好了。
be very particular with your words and
说话要非常谨慎。
you can invest it with some degree of
你可以进行一定程度的投资
emotional content you can be a very
情感内容，你可以非常
charismatic
魅力四射
communicator and I guess some you're
沟通者，我想你也是。
saying that some men maybe lean one way
也就是说，有些男人可能倾向于某一方面
more than the other absolutely they lean
绝对比其他方式更倾向于
more towards the semantic information
更偏向语义信息
just like logic just absolutely like a
就像逻辑一样，简直就像……
robot yeah well sometimes there's
机器人？嗯，有时候会有。
definitely some robotic men out there
确实有一些机器人存在。
and what women want is more of the
而女性想要的是更多
emotional resonance yes in how you're
是的，你的情感共鸣方式是……
talking yeah they want a Vibe you know
是啊，他们想要那种氛围，你知道的。
it's that Shakira stong it's starting to
是夏奇拉的实力开始显现了
feel right her hips don't lie so it's
感觉对了，她的臀部不会说谎，所以就是这样。
like it's this mood that's being
就像是这种情绪正在发生
generated where the two people the two
生成的两个人
dancers the two players begin to occupy
两位玩家开始占据舞者。
a shared private world and within that
一个共享的私人世界，以及在这个世界中
world the the rules don't always apply
世界规则并非总是适用。
we've created a different bounded
我们创建了一个不同的有界
universe and that's actually the goal of
宇宙，而这实际上就是目标。
seduction is the just the two of us here
这里只有我们两个人，只有我们两个人。
and we're creating this separate
我们正在创建这个独立的
universe that's different from
与宇宙不同的宇宙
everything else that's going on it's
其他所有事情都是
just you and me here and we can then
只有你和我，然后我们就可以
play according to the rules that we've
按照我们制定的规则来玩。
developed inside of this little
在这个小地方发展起来
microcosmic universe so I'm G to get my
微观宇宙，所以我很荣幸能得到我的
hygiene right I'm GNA hit the gym I'm G
注重个人卫生，我是GNA，去健身房，我是G
to get a new outfit sounds like you're
想买套新衣服听起来像是你在……
doing pretty good I'm going to learn how
做得还不错，我要学习如何
to talk is there anything else that in
还有其他什么要说的吗？
that sort of initial top of the funnel
那种漏斗顶部的初始状态
attraction phase I should be really
恋爱阶段我应该真的
focusing on to make sure that I increase
专注于确保我增加
my probability of just inviting someone
我邀请某人的概率
in to the house those things are the
那些东西被带进了房子里
most important a lot of guys get too
最重要的是，很多男人都太容易得罪人了。
focused on money at this stage and the
现阶段的重点是资金。
fact of the matter is is that money is
事实是，金钱是
what I call an attraction
我称之为吸引力
proxy you don't need money to get laid
代理，你不需要钱就能上床
you don't need money to attract
你不需要花钱就能吸引别人
attention it's one way like it will
注意，这是一种方式，就像它会……
absolutely attract attention if you go
如果你去的话，绝对会引人注目。
to the VIP section in order bottle
前往贵宾区订购酒水
service and you're throwing around tens
服务周到，你却挥霍无度。
of thousands of dollars that was my
那是我损失的几千美元。
whole strategy when I was 21 wow you had
我21岁时就有了整套策略，哇，你当时就有了。
tens of thousands thrown around good for
数万块钱随意挥霍，这对……有好处
you it was just a pre25 strategy that
对你来说，这只是一个25岁之前的策略而已。
converted well for shallow relationships
对于浅层关系，转换效果良好
and stuff but other than that it can
还有其他一些东西，但除此之外，它还可以
work but at the same token I guarantee
工作，但同时我保证
that there is an unemployed man living
那里住着一个失业男子。
in his parents basement who's getting
在他父母家的地下室里，谁会得到
laid tonight because he's a musician and
今晚和他睡了，因为他是个音乐家。
he's playing at the
他正在演出
local open mic on Tuesday you know what
你知道的，周二的本地开放麦克风之夜
I'm saying and he's up on stage so if if
我说，他现在在台上，所以如果如果
you're young and broke
你年轻又穷。
and you're not cute then you have to
如果你长得不好看，那你就得……
find some way to be to Stand
找到某种方式来站立
Out by far the
远远领先
most useful thing to attracting women is
吸引女性最有效的方法是
not money per se because it's not always
并非指金钱本身，因为金钱并非总是如此。
easy to tell who has money especially in
很容易看出谁有钱，尤其是在……
places like San Francisco the
像旧金山这样的地方
billionaires dress like homeless people
亿万富翁的穿着打扮像无家可归的人
sometimes and um it's not necessarily
有时候，嗯，也不一定。
power because sometimes the most
权力，因为有时最
powerful individuals are actually hidden
真正有权势的人往往隐藏起来。
from the Limelight and that's what
从聚光灯下走出来，就是这样
allows them to to exercise their power
使他们能够行使权力
with some degree of
在某种程度上
immunity the most powerful people you
免疫力最强大的人
know are probably not the most powerful
知道他们可能不是最强大的
people the thing that works is Fame is
人们认为真正有效的方法是名气。
Renown and Renown can work at many
Renown 和 Renown 可以在很多方面发挥作用
different levels you can be and I
你可以达到不同的水平，而我
learned this as an actor which is how I
这是我作为演员学到的，也是我如何学会的。
got my start in New York City is like I
我在纽约市的起步就像……
performed on some very small stages um
在一些非常小的舞台上表演
throughout my career to sometimes just a
在我的整个职业生涯中，有时甚至只是一个
few people in the audience
观众席上只有寥寥几人。
but the fact of the matter is for those
但事实是，对于那些
two hours if I was the lead and my name
如果我是主角，两个小时，我的名字
was on the Marquee and the spotlight was
当时正在大堂里，聚光灯照耀着……
on me on some level what I call as I was
对我而言，在某种程度上，我称之为“我曾经的样子”。
the contextual Alpha and within that
上下文 Alpha 以及其中
tiny almost insignificant world I was at
我身处一个渺小得几乎微不足道的世界。
the top of that status hierarchy and
该地位等级体系的顶端和
that's what gets you laid now those same
这就是现在让你和别人上床的秘诀，那些人
women had no interest in having a
女性对生育没有兴趣
long-term relationship with me and
与我建立长期关系
that's what kind of motivated me to take
正是这一点促使我采取了行动。
a hard look at the guy in the mirror and
认真地审视镜子里的自己
think well why would a woman want
想想，妈的，女人为什么会想要
to marry me it's like I'm living in this
嫁给我就像我生活在这样的世界里
one room studio with roaches everywhere
一间单间公寓，到处都是蟑螂。
it's like I'm broke I'm living month to
我感觉自己像个穷光蛋，每月都得勉强糊口。
month my lifestyle sucks I don't really
这个月我的生活方式糟透了，我真的不太喜欢。
have much ambition except for this let's
除了这件事以外，我还有很多抱负。
say very vague Vision about becoming a
谈到成为一个……的非常模糊的愿景
successful actor whatever that meant I I
无论“成功演员”意味着什么，我
wasn't really I didn't really have a
其实我并没有真的……
plan and I didn't really have much to
计划，但我其实没什么可做的。
offer in terms of a long-term
提供长期的报价
relationship and so I said okay well if
关系，所以我说好吧，如果
this is something that I want I
这是我想要的。
gotta I mean the cavalary isn't coming
我的意思是，援军不会来了。
I got to do it because no one else will
我得做这件事，因为没人愿意做。
and I took kind of radical
我采取了一种激进的做法。
responsibility for my life and you know
对我的生命负责，你知道的
started down a different path we talked
我们开始走上一条不同的道路，我们聊了起来。
about attraction um as you move down
关于吸引力，嗯，当你向下移动时
through that funnel the next challenge
通过这个漏斗，下一个挑战即将到来。
becomes actually keeping someone yeah
实际上，留住某人是的
and I funny enough because in my early
说来也巧，因为在我早期
20s although I could seemingly attract
虽然我似乎能吸引到20多岁的人
women at this point I couldn't get any
这时我一个女人都找不到。
of them to want to be in a relationship
他们中有人想要谈恋爱
with me especially the ones I wanted
尤其是那些我想要的。
yeah what is useful to get a man or a
是的，什么对找个男人有用？
woman is not the same thing as what
女人和……不是一回事。
works to keep a man or a woman those are
那些用来维系男人或女人关系的手段是
two different problems some people
有些人遇到的两个不同的问题
actually make great long-term Partners
实际上，他们是优秀的长期合作伙伴。
but they're terrible at attracting
但它们在吸引人方面很糟糕
they're terrible at the marketing other
他们在市场营销方面很糟糕。
people they get the marketing down but
人们都明白营销的要点，但是
they lack the substance or they can't
他们缺乏实质内容，或者他们做不到。
really go the distance from one way or
真正从一条路上走到底
the other and so it's harder them to
另一个，所以他们更难……
keep their Partners around they're two
他们俩都让伴侣待在身边。
different problems the solution for one
不同的问题，其中一个问题的解决方案
does not apply to the other in
不适用于其他情况
particular the vast majority of
尤其是绝大多数
Attraction is based on Pro
吸引力基于专业性
fantasy I don't know who you
幻想 我不知道你是谁
are I just see the
我难道只看到……
outside and I'm going to approach you
我会到外面去，然后接近你。
because I like that outside and my
因为我喜欢户外，而且我的
attraction is going to fill in the gaps
吸引力将填补空白
of my knowledge base with what I want to
将我的知识库与我想要的东西结合起来
see
看
there that's why I talk about I'm in an
这就是为什么我说我身处……
episode about how most men blow the
一集讲的是大多数男人如何吹箫
first date they blow the first date by
第一次约会他们就搞砸了。
talking too much they talk too much out
他们话太多，说得太多。
of the misguided desire to prove their
出于一种错误的渴望，想要证明自己
value to women
对女性的价值
they usually do it in a very
他们通常以一种非常……的方式做这件事。
heavy-handed hamfisted way and generally
笨拙生硬的方式，而且通常
all they do is succeed in disabusing
他们所做的只是成功地使人产生错觉。
that woman of the fantasy that she had
她幻想中的那个女人
of that man which is why she was sitting
就是因为那个男人，所以她才坐在那里。
there on that date tonight because the
今晚那天你会在那里，因为
likelihood that anything I say is going
我说的任何话都有可能发生
to match up with what you want to see in
为了与你想看到的内容相匹配
the privacy of your own mind is
你个人思想的隐私是
functionally zero so I need to tread
功能上为零，所以我需要踩踏
very carefully because you're not on
务必小心，因为你不在线上。
this date because you like me because
这个日期是因为你喜欢我，因为
you don't know who I am yet
你他妈的还不知道我是谁
you're here because of what you hope I
你来到这里是因为你希望我
might be and so I need to be very
有可能，所以我需要非常谨慎。
careful not to disabuse you of that hope
小心别让你的希望落空。
too
也
quickly right it's actually the the key
很快，没错，这才是关键。
to to transitioning from one phase to
从一个阶段过渡到
the other it's going to sound real bad
另一个听起来会很糟糕。
but it's a slow and gradual
但这是一个缓慢而渐进的过程
disappointment right and you have to do
失望是必然的，你必须这样做。
this because if you you don't do it then
这是因为如果你不这样做的话……
what do you end up with end up in a
你最终会得到什么？最终会得到什么？
relationship where you're not truly
在一段你并不真正投入的关系中
known and you're just performing all the
众所周知，你只是在执行所有操作
time and that's probably not sustainable
时间紧迫，而且这种情况可能不可持续。
but it's certainly not very satisfying
但这确实不太令人满意。
and there'll be a sudden disappointment
然后会突然感到失望。
probably there generally is I talk about
可能一般情况下我会谈到
that in the book The Crisis of
在《危机》一书中
disappointment is one of the first
失望是首要的感受之一。
crises that all nent relationships must
所有人际关系都必须面对的危机
pass through and on some level the
穿过，并在某种程度上
relationship doesn't even begin in
关系甚至还没有开始
Earnest until couples go through the
认真对待，直到情侣们经历
Cris of
克里斯
disappointment where I e through one
失望，我通过一个
significant betrayal or the accumulation
重大背叛或积累
of small inconsistencies the fantasy on
幻想中一些细微的矛盾之处
which the relationship has been based up
这种关系正是建立在……之上的。
until that point
直到那时
shatters and the person is really no
破碎，而那个人真的不是
different from who he or she was the day
与他/她当天的样子截然不同
before but he or she's going to feel
之前，但他或她将会感到
completely different because it's almost
完全不同，因为它几乎
like you're the scales have dropped from
就像你的天平已经从……下降了
your eyes and you're seeing this person
你睁开眼睛，看到了这个人。
and maybe what sound what seemed cute
也许是什么声音听起来很可爱
and lovable and adorable just a week ago
就在一周前，她还那么可爱迷人。
now is completely infuriating and uh
现在真是令人无比恼火，呃……
difficult to live with sometimes the
有时难以相处
very things that most attracted to tend
最吸引人的事物往往
to be the things that we dislike most
成为我们最厌恶的事物
about our partners further down the road
关于我们未来的合作伙伴
It's a cruel irony so interesting when
这是一种残酷的讽刺，但却非常有趣。
you talk about this moment that some
你谈到这一刻，一些
relationships go through where they have
人际关系会经历他们所经历的一切。
that sudden disappointment where the
那种突如其来的失望
kind of honeymoon effect the halo effect
类似蜜月效应的光环效应
of this person kind of shatters and you
这个人有点崩溃了，而你
say that's when the relationship
就说，这就是关系开始的时候。
actually begins well yeah because it's
其实开头还不错，因为……
at that point where you have the
在那一刻，你拥有
opportunity at long last to see the
终于有机会看到
other person for who he or she is and
因为他/她本身的样子而尊重对方。
you couldn't see that before you just
你以前看不到这一点
saw what you wanted to see you were
你看到了你想看到的，你就是
distorted in your perception by your
你的感知因你的
attraction and you need some of that
吸引力，你需要一些这种东西。
Distortion because why else would you
失真，不然你为什么会这样？
have taken the risk and the expense and
已经承担了风险和费用，
the opportunity to pursue this
有机会追求这一点
relationship up until that point like
在那之前的关系就像
you need a little bit of Attraction too
你也需要一点吸引力。
much of Attraction is crazy I mean it's
《诱惑》这部电影很多地方都很疯狂，我的意思是，它……
completely distortive not enough
完全扭曲，还不够
attraction and you're not going to
吸引力，而且你不会……
overcome the behavioral inertia you're
克服你的行为惯性
just going to be SE in your head you're
你脑子里只会一直想着SE（可能是指某种游戏或软件）
be like this isn't worth it I'd rather
感觉这样不值得，我宁愿……
just do something with a higher
做点更有意义的事
likelihood of success where I can get
我能获得的成功可能性
one of my needs met in a more
我的一个需求得到了满足，而且更加……
predictable and consistent way because
以可预测和一致的方式，因为
relationships are really a role of the
人际关系实际上是……的角色
dice especially today more than yeah
骰子，尤其是今天，比以前更甚。
more than ever so in that first day can
第一天就比以往任何时候都更是如此
women also talk themselves out of it in
女性也会说服自己放弃这种想法。
terms of the women talking too much and
用女性话太多的术语来说
the man going Jesus Christ they can but
那个人要去见耶稣基督，他们可以，但是
most guys just they're trying to get
大多数人只是想得到
laid so it like the woman would have to
摆放得好像女人不得不这样做似的
be a total train wreck or that guy would
要么彻底完蛋，要么那家伙就会
have to have enough optionality that he
他必须有足够的自主权。
could be picky but most men are not
男人可能会挑剔，但大多数男人并非如此。
picky because most men are just really
挑剔是因为大多数男人真的非常挑剔。
hungry for anything that they're willing
他们渴望得到任何他们愿意得到的东西。
to get I know that sounds bad but it's
我知道这听起来很糟糕，但事实就是如此
kind of true well I mean it's supported
某种程度上来说确实如此，我的意思是，它得到了支持。
by data as well isn't it that you know
根据数据来看，你不是也知道吗？
I've heard repeatedly that the top 10%
我反复听说，前 10%
of men are having most of the sex they
大部分男性都拥有大部分的性生活。
are killing it it's like what a time to
太棒了，这真是个好时机！
be alive these days man and that seems
如今活着真不容易啊，这似乎……
to be kind of the end state of a
某种程度上是最终状态
disregulated sexual Marketplace and it's
不受监管的性交易市场，而且是
not unusual it's not uncommon like we
这并不罕见，也并不像我们这样不寻常。
see this in all kinds of animal species
在各种动物物种中都能看到这种现象
elephant seals wild Mustangs it's like
象海豹和野马就像
you see some alpha males dominate the
你会看到一些强势雄性占据主导地位。
females who congregate in Herms around
聚集在赫尔墨斯周围的雌性
those men and if that man is defeated by
那些人，如果那个人被打败了……
another Contender the women Aren't Loyal
另一位竞争者：女性并不忠诚
it's not like those females love that
并不是说那些女性喜欢那样。
individual and they'll stick with it
他们是独立的个体，而且会坚持下去。
even after it's defeated in combat they
即使在战斗中被击败之后，它们
just move on to the next one 85% of
直接跳到下一个，85%
cultures on this planet according to
根据地球上的文化
people who know more about this than I
比我更了解这方面的人
do have been polygamous and what we see
确实实行过一夫多妻制，而我们看到的也确实如此。
is that when
就是当
women are able and empowered to make
女性有能力且有权做出决定
their own sexual decisions in sexual
他们在性方面做出自己的性决定
Marketplace they target the top 10% of
他们瞄准的是市场中排名前 10% 的人群。
men that creates a lot of problems
制造很多问题的男人
though creates a lot of problems both
虽然这会造成很多问题，
for men and
男士和
women um it creates problems for women
这会给女性带来问题。
because the likelihood that any one of
因为任何一方发生这种情况的可能性都很小
those 10% men are going to give up their
那10%的男性将会放弃他们的
insane sexual optionality and enter into
疯狂的性选择权并进入
a monogamous exclusive arrangement with
与伴侣建立一夫一妻制的专属关系
them is very negligible like that guy
他们就像那个人一样，微不足道。
has to be so done with playing the field
必须彻底结束这种玩弄感情的行为。
and so ready to start a family and
所以他们已经准备好组建家庭了。
settle down so it's really about timing
冷静下来，所以关键在于时机。
as opposed to being the right woman you
而不是成为你的理想伴侣
kind of just have to be at be good
基本上只需要表现良好就行了。
enough at the right moment to kind of
在合适的时机，足以达到某种程度
capture that man's attention and for the
吸引那个男人的注意力，并且为了
vast majority of those women they're not
绝大多数女性都不是
going to be it but what's the
将会是，但那是什么？
alternative it's like how about this uh
或者，比如这样如何？
you know this guy he's he's completely
你知道这个人，他完全
average there's nothing bad about him
他性格普通，没什么缺点。
nothing that great about him either he'd
他也没啥了不起的地方。
make a great husband like that doesn't
那样做并不能造就一个好丈夫。
sound very attractive I can understand
听起来很有吸引力，我能理解
that do you still think that
你仍然这么认为吗？
relationships are a exchange of value
人际关系是价值交换。
between two people of course and what is
当然，这指的是两个人之间，而这又是什么呢？
that exchange of value because when I
这种价值交换是因为当我
when when you when I read that it kind
当我读到那篇文章时，它有点像
of sounds like gold digging or something
听起来像是拜金女之类的。
well that's because often people take
那是因为人们常常会……
value very literally and especially
非常字面意义上的价值，尤其
economics that word just is associated
经济学中这个词恰好与……相关
very strongly with money in the
资金实力非常雄厚。
collective imagination I think in one of
我认为集体想象力在其中扮演着重要角色。
the footnotes I use a definition from
我在脚注中使用的定义来自
Von misus from the Austrian School of
来自奥地利学派的冯·米苏斯
economics and he basically defines
经济学，他基本上是这样定义的。
economics as the study of human
经济学是对人类的研究
behavior in respect to means and with
就手段和行为而言
respect to ends and scarce means that
尊重目标和稀缺资源
could be applied in other
可以应用于其他领域
ways the easiest way to explain the
解释方法最简单的方式
value is that people don't move towards
价值在于人们不会趋向于
people they want nothing to do
人们什么都不想做
with they have better things to do
他们还有更重要的事要做。
especially when they have these scarce
尤其是当他们拥有这些稀缺资源的时候。
resources like time like energy like
时间等资源，就像能源一样。
attention and that they want things from
他们渴望得到关注，并希望从中获得一些东西。
other people if I at a distance can see
如果我远远地能看到其他人
there's it's like going shopping I can
就像去购物一样，我可以
look at a distance there's nothing in
远远地望去，什么也没有。
that store that I want I don't have to
我想要的那家店我不必非得去
go in and waste my time to figure out
进去浪费我的时间去弄清楚
whether that's absolutely true or not
无论这是否完全属实
because I have other things to do today
因为我今天还有其他事情要做。
so it's like if there's nothing that I
所以就好像如果没有什么东西……
want from that store I'm not going to
我不想从那家店里买东西。
walk through its
漫步其中
doors right people don't move towards
门右边的人不会朝那边走。
those they don't want anything from so
他们不想从那些人那里得到任何东西
what is value value can be all kinds of
什么是价值？价值可以有很多种形式。
things value is anything that can be
事物的价值在于任何可以……的东西。
bought or
买的或
earned okay not everything can be bought
挣来的钱是可以的，但不是所有东西都能买到。
and earned and I have a whole chapter
并且赚到了，我还有整整一章。
about that but a lot of things can be
关于这一点，但很多事情都可能……
bought and earned okay so give me some
买的，赚的，好吧，给我一些
examples of the most important types of
最重要的几种类型示例
values values that we exchange in a the
我们在……中交换的价值观
context of a
上下文
relationship sex yeah
是的，有性关系
security yeah excitement yeah emotional
安全感，是的，兴奋感，是的，情绪化
support yeah child
支持孩子
rearing okay
饲养情况良好
and do women and men value those types
女性和男性是否重视这类人
of value differently of course and what
价值当然因人而异，以及什么
do what do men value more and what do
做男人更看重的事，以及做什么
women value more that's a tough one
女性更看重这一点，这确实是个难题。
because not only do men and women value
因为不仅男性和女性都重视
those differently but men and women
那些不同的，但男人和女人
value them differently at different
不同情况下，它们的价值不同。
stages of their life okay like I'm sure
他们人生的各个阶段，好吧，我确信
when you were doing the bottle service
当你负责酒水服务的时候
you were not really thinking whether
你当时并没有真正考虑过这个问题。
these women had good maternal capacities
这些女性都具备良好的母性能力。
right you were you were trying to get
没错，你当时就是想得到
laid exactly you were approaching those
正好是你接近那些人时的样子
women with a different set of needs or
有不同需求的女性
desires there's nothing wrong with that
有欲望并没有错。
because it's actually very difficult for
因为实际上这非常困难
one person to meet this hyper conflated
一个人来满足这种高度混淆的
set of needs and wants that's one of the
一系列需求和愿望，这是其中之一
reasons why relationships tend to fail
导致人际关系失败的原因
these days is we want too many things
如今我们想要的东西太多了。
from one
一个
person and we expect one person to be
我们期望一个人是
all things across our entire lives which
我们一生中所有的事情
is very difficult if not impossible it's
这非常困难，甚至是不可能的。
like incredible that it even happens at
简直难以置信，这种事竟然会发生
all that didn't used to be the case did
所有这些以前都不是这样的。
it well didn't used to be the case
以前并非如此。
mostly because it was so difficult if
主要是因为如果这样做太难了
not impossible to divorce and there were
离婚并非不可能，而且
a lot of social tabos against separation
许多社会禁忌都反对分离
but Al I would have been living in like
但是，如果我住在Al，我就会像
a community where I could have got you
我本可以带你去的那个社区
know we're living much more isolated and
我知道我们现在的生活更加孤立，而且
lonely now so I would have been a you
现在我很孤独，所以我会成为你的。
know the village would have given me
我知道村子会给我
some of those things that I'm looking
我正在寻找的一些东西
for in terms of value I would have had a
就价值而言，我本可以拥有
big social structure around me
我周围有庞大的社会结构。
absolutely I talk about that in the book
当然，我在书中谈到了这一点。
is that we used to live in small
我们过去常常住在小房子里。
communities where we actually had lots
在一些我们确实有很多社区的社区里，我们有很多
of different kinds of relationships with
与不同类型关系
lots of different people and also an
很多不同的人，还有一个
Extended kin networks in
扩展亲属网络
intergenerational housing for instance
例如，代际住房。
and so with the Advent of the nuclear
因此，随着核武器的出现，情况发生了变化。
family and the dissolution of real
家庭与现实的解体
Community we expect our partner to be
我们期望合作伙伴成为社区的一份子。
all things to be an entire Village and
所有的一切，构成一个完整的村庄，
an extended family and that's just
一个大家庭，仅此而已。
really not possible I mean the love
真的不可能，我是说爱。
marriage in particular may even be a
婚姻尤其可能是一种
paradox in terms because you want kind
就你而言，这本身就是一个悖论，因为你想要的是善良
of let's say um an emotionally stable
比如说，一个情绪稳定的人
safe
安全的
companion who is also your passionate
你的伴侣，也是你热情似火的伴侣。
love
爱
and sexual partner spontaneous risky so
性伴侣自发且有风险
difficult if not impossible like you
像你这样，即使不是不可能，也很难。
certainly can't do both of those things
当然不可能同时做到这两件事。
at the same time the best you can hope
同时，这也是你所能期盼的最好结果
for is to kind of vacillate between the
这样做是为了在两者之间摇摆不定
two of them yeah to kind of create a
是的，他们俩要创造某种东西
proportion just enough passion or
恰到好处的热情或
spontaneity and risk to keep the kind of
自发性和冒险精神，以保持这种风格
bedroom alive but still maintaining the
卧室里还活着，但仍然保持着
stability and long-term security of the
稳定性和长期安全
relationship it's very difficult to
建立关系非常困难
manage I find this difficult I find this
管理我觉得这很难我觉得这
difficult I find it difficult to be in
我觉得很难……
I'm in a five-year relationship now I'm
我现在处于一段五年的恋爱关系中。
like how do you how do you go for
比如，你如何才能……
another 50 years because I I you know
再过50年，因为我知道
with the with the same person and
与同一个人
maintain the spontaneity and the
保持自发性和
excitement for 50 years you know and
你知道，这令人兴奋了50年。
being the kind of Novel sexually
是那种性小说
attractive
吸引人的
whatever while also being stable safe
无论如何，同时还要保持稳定安全。
predictable comfortable present at the
可预见的舒适礼物
same time like if they feel like
同时，就像他们感觉一样
paradoxes it's very hard and you have to
悖论很难，你必须
be creative yeah it's part of the reason
要有创意，没错，这也是原因之一。
why
为什么
there
那里
are that places like Victoria's Secret
像维多利亚的秘密这样的地方。
exist you know what I'm saying it's like
存在，你知道我的意思，就像
21y old girls aren't shopping there
21岁的女孩不会在那里购物。
really so if you're not willing to
真的，如果你不愿意的话
actually open up your relationship then
实际上，那就公开你们的关系吧。
you have to kind of make your partner
你必须想办法让你的伴侣
feel new which could mean different
感觉焕然一新，这可能意味着不同
outfits it could mean play and entering
服装可能意味着玩耍和进入
in experimenting with different roles
在尝试不同角色时
behind closed doors it can also just
在关起门来之后，它也可能只是
mean travel yeah I mean one thing that
我的意思是旅行，嗯，我的意思是一件事
really seems to spark sex life in
似乎真的能激发性生活。
couples is foreign bed sheets and I
情侣们用的是外国床单，而我
think that you've just sort of changed
我觉得你好像突然就变了。
the context and that's enough of a spark
有了这些背景信息，就足以引发讨论。
of novelty to bring some of the sexual
新颖性带来一些性
interest back for the
利息返还
man I think novelty is more important
我觉得新颖性更重要。
for men than for women one of the things
对男性而言，比对女性而言，这是其中一点。
that really works in my relationship
这在我的关系中真的行之有效
that I've observed is just being away
我观察到的只是远离。
absolutely so I come out here for you
当然，所以我才来这里为你服务。
know I'm out here for a couple of weeks
我知道我会在这里待上几个星期。
now I'm not going to see my and then I
现在我见不到我的，然后我
was doing Dragons Den before this in the
在此之前，我曾参加过《龙穴》节目。
UK so that was I was away for a while
所以，我当时在英国，所以就离开了一段时间。
there
那里
in total I wouldn't have seen my partner
总之，我本来就见不到我的伴侣了。
for about four weeks so when I come back
大约四个星期，等我回来的时候
it's kind of like they're a new person
感觉他们就像变了一个人似的。
it is I mean one of the things about
我的意思是，这是关于……的事情之一
what made relationships work back in the
过去维系人际关系的关键是什么？
day is men didn't really spend a lot of
白天，男人们其实并没有花很多时间。
time with women and vice versa James
与女性相处的时间以及女性与女性相处的时间，詹姆斯
ston the divorce lawyer he had this
离婚律师斯通，他有这个
great line on the softw underbelly
柔软的腹部线条很棒
interview when he was responding to the
他在接受采访时回应了
spike in divorces during Co when
疫情期间离婚率激增
everybody was shut down and forced into
所有人都被迫停工并进入
close company with each other for
彼此关系密切
periods of time he said that men and
他说，在某些时期，男人和
women signed up for Better or For Worse
女性报名参加了“更好或更糟”活动
but not for lunch it's really hard to
但午餐就很难了。
just be in each other space all the time
就一直待在彼此的空间里
and the fact of the matter is when we
事实是，当我们
lived in extended kid networks and
生活在庞大的儿童网络中
communities men had a bunch of men to do
社区里的男人们有很多事要做。
things with and women had a bunch of
与女人有关的事情有很多
women to talk to and even in the 50s
即使在 50 年代，也有女性可以交谈。
which is kind of romanticized as the the
这在某种程度上被浪漫化了，即
Paragon of conservative traditional
保守传统的典范
marriage that was the time when the man
婚姻，就是男人结婚的时期。
was a traveling salesman and he was on
他是一名旅行推销员，当时他正在……
the road for 200 days out of the Year
一年中有 200 天都在路上
having an office has kept more marriages
拥有办公室让更多婚姻得以维系
alive than probably any
比任何人都更活着
other toy or therapy or intervention on
其他玩具、疗法或干预措施
the planet like you need to
你需要像对待地球一样对待它
leave you need to leave and it's even
你必须离开，而且这甚至
harder to do that with the Advent of
随着……的出现，做到这一点变得更加困难。
cellular technology it's like being
蜂窝技术就像是
physically absent doesn't matter if the
即使人不在场，也无关紧要。
whole time you're there I know where you
只要你在那儿，我就知道你在哪里。
are at all times because I've put a
一直都是这样，因为我放了一个
tracking thing on your phone and I'm
你手机上的追踪器，而我……
constantly communicating with you
一直与您保持沟通
throughout the day like now there's no
一整天都像这样，没有
uncertainty there's no mystery there's
不确定性，没有谜团，就是这样。
no unknown so when we get back together
没有未知数，所以当我们再次聚在一起时
what do we have to talk
我们有什么可谈的
about I'm not interested in you because
我对你没兴趣，因为
I believe you're an entirely known
我相信你是一个完全知名的人
entity you need to have something that I
你需要拥有的实体，我
don't know yet to attract my interest
还不知道如何才能引起我的兴趣
and curiosity which is the spark that
好奇心，正是那份火花。
eventually potentially leads to passion
最终可能会发展成激情
and sexual
以及性
intimacy but what does this say about
亲密关系，但这又说明了什么呢？
the very nature of monogamy because if
一夫一妻制的本质就在于此，因为如果
you need to this doesn't feel like a
你需要这样做，这感觉不像是一个
natural thing if I go back you know we
如果我回去，你知道，这是很自然的事情。
once upon a time we couldn't just get on
从前，我们无法和平共处。
a plane or go to the office we would
我们会选择坐飞机或者去办公室。
presumably be around each other most of
想必大部分时间都会待在一起
the time I'm trying to understand if you
我正在努力理解你是否
think like monogamy is quote unquote
想想一夫一妻制是……
natural oh probably not like I think
自然的哦，可能不像我想的那样。
that humans are probably
人类很可能
monogamish but like strict
类似严格一夫一妻制但又很严格
monogamy which should be really rigidly
一夫一妻制应该非常严格
an explicit defined by the individuals
由个人明确定义的
in question because there's clearly
之所以有疑问，是因为显然存在……
behaviors that are in the gray Zone like
处于灰色地带的行为，例如
is harmless flirting cheating you know
你知道，无害的调情和出轨是一回事吗？
what I'm saying that some people might
我的意思是，有些人可能会
say no that's just part of the fun of
说“不”，这也是乐趣的一部分。
being a social human being and it it's
作为一个社会性的人，这是……
not going to lead anything and other
不会领导任何事情，还有其他
people might think no that's totally
人们可能会想，不，那完全不可能。
inappropriate and incorrect so these
不恰当且不正确，所以这些
things need to be discussed monogamy
需要讨论一夫一妻制的问题。
isn't just something that everybody
并非每个人都能理解的事情
agrees on and understands what that
同意并理解这一点
means but yeah I think that it's
意思是，嗯，我觉得是这样。
generally not something that
通常不是这样的
we do
我们这样做
naturally one way to think about this is
当然，思考这个问题的一种方式是：
um monogamy actually benefits men on a
嗯，一夫一妻制实际上对男性有利。
utilitarian perspective because there's
功利主义视角，因为存在……
generally more women than there are for
通常情况下，女性人数多于男性。
men if you maintain strict social
如果你保持严格的社交
monogamy we have this many men and this
一夫一妻制，我们有这么多男人，还有这个
many women what that means is that even
很多女性，这意味着即使
the worst men in society in that
社会上最坏的人
Community can be functionally guaranteed
社区功能可以得到保障
of a wife I want to really close off on
我想彻底和妻子断绝关系。
this point about um exchanging values
关于价值交换这一点
but that's really what a relationship is
但那才是真正意义上的关系。
when I spoke to James seon the divorce
当我与詹姆斯·西恩谈及离婚时
lawyer you referenced there we started
您提到的那位律师，我们就开始了。
talking about gold diggers and he you
谈论拜金女，还有你
know would reference divorce cases where
我知道会提及离婚案例，其中
there's a
有一个
70-year-old significantly overweight man
70岁，严重超重的男子
who's you know with a 30-year-old woman
你认识谁和一个30岁的女人在一起？
and I said to him is that not gold
我问他，那难道不是金子吗？
digging and I said is that love and his
挖掘，我说那就是爱和他的
response to me I'll always remember it
我会永远记住你的回复
was he
是他吗？
said well it's a transaction she's
她说，这是一笔交易。
getting something from him and in the
从他那里得到一些东西，并且在
words that you've described it might be
你描述的这些词可能是
safety it might be I don't know money or
安全问题可能是我不知道钱的问题，或者
whatever and he's also getting something
不管怎样，他还会得到一些东西。
from her mhm which
从她嗯嗯的
is I guess a feeling I guess it's an
我猜这是一种感觉，我猜这是一种
emotional feeling presumably he's
他大概是情绪激动吧。
getting sex sex yeah he's getting the
得到性爱，是的，他正在得到
opportunity to walk in the door with a
有机会带着……走进这扇门
beautiful 30-year-old on his arm which
他手臂上挽着一位漂亮的30岁女子。
is certainly a bump to his ego but is
这当然会打击他的自尊心，但
also good for the social game the fact
这也有利于社交游戏。
of the matter is is that most
问题的关键在于大多数
women most men would have sex with most
大多数男人都愿意和大多数女性发生性关系。
women but most women would not have sex
大多数女性不会发生性行为
with most men so we also know that men's
对于大多数男性来说，我们也知道男性的
threshold for selection is much lower
选择门槛要低得多
than
比
women's generally women have more
女性通常拥有更多
optionality than men do and so when we
我们比男性拥有更多的选择，所以当我们
see a woman with a man we more or less
看到一个女人和一个男人在一起，我们或多或少都会
assume that that's the best man that she
假设那是她心目中的最佳人选。
could get given her range of options
可以给她提供一系列选择
often times with the men it's the only
很多时候，对男人来说，这是唯一的选择。
woman that would have him not quite the
那个女人会让他……但并非完全如此
same thing so if a very attractive woman
同样的情况，如果一个非常有魅力的女人
is with a man then that's an automatic
如果是和男人在一起，那就是自动的
status boost in any Social Circle that
在任何社交圈中提升地位
he navigates in because everyone is
他之所以能融入其中，是因为每个人都……
going to assume that there must be
我假设一定存在
something really important or
非常重要的事情或
significant about that guy given the
考虑到那个人，这件事意义重大
fact that we assume that that attractive
我们假设有吸引力的事实
or beautiful woman could pretty much
或者，一位美丽的女士几乎可以做到。
have any man that she wanted and yet
她可以随心所欲地选择任何男人，然而
she's with him for Better or For Worse
她将与他同甘共苦。
it's more difficult to know a man's True
要了解一个男人的真心，更难。
Value given the the reasons why men and
考虑到男性和女性的价值原因
women transact in the sexual Marketplace
女性在性交易市场进行交易
like women's value in terms of sexual
比如女性在性方面的价值
Marketplace is just so much more
Marketplace 的功能远不止这些。
explicit like it's it's men's downfall
直白地说，这简直就是男人的堕落。
that we're too monom maniacally focused
我们过于单调，过于执着于某件事。
on the reproductive cues and the
关于生殖信号和
physical attractiveness for Better or
外貌吸引力对更好或
For Worse and that's hard for women
情况更糟，这对女性来说尤其艰难。
because some women have it and some
因为有些女性患有这种病，有些女性则没有。
women don't you know what I'm
女人们，你们难道不知道我是什么吗？
saying but for a man when it comes time
但对于一个男人来说，时机到了就另当别论了。
like is he it's difficult to even
就像他一样，甚至很难说清楚。
calculate a person's net worth if you
计算一个人的净资产，如果你
have all of their income documentation
他们拥有所有收入证明文件
like you have accountants to do that
就像你们有会计师来做这件事一样。
right Stephen you certainly can't do it
没错，斯蒂芬，你肯定做不到。
on site no like if I didn't know about
现场没有，就好像我不知道似的。
your podcast you were just walking down
你的播客里，你当时正走着呢
the street with your plain old black tea
街上，你正端着一杯普通的红茶
I'd be like you you might be
我可能会像你一样。
functionally invisible you know what I'm
实际上我隐形，你知道我是什么吗？
saying and that's that's actually kind
这么说其实挺好的。
of good it's nice to be able to be
能够成为好人真好
Incognito and invisible when you want to
想隐身就隐身。
be yeah to be so famous that you can't
是的，出名到无法自拔。
go anywhere without being recognized
去任何地方都不会被人认出来
would be a liability more than an
与其说是负担，不如说是负担
opportunity mhm but it takes it would
机会，嗯，但这需要时间。
take somebody to be curious about you to
带个对你感到好奇的人去
learn about all the
了解所有相关信息
interesting and valuable things about
有趣且有价值的事情
you and your
你和你的
lifestyle and unless you advertise that
生活方式，除非你宣传这一点。除非你宣传这种生活方式。
in some way most women would
在某种程度上，大多数女性都会
not go through the trouble of trying to
不费事尝试
figure that
考虑到
out and that's not the same for a woman
出去，这对女人来说就不一样了。
of course not it's really hard for women
当然不是，这对女性来说真的很难。
to just be alone oh yeah gosh like and
只想一个人待着，哦耶，天哪，就像……
that's I can and sometimes they complain
我能做到，但有时他们会抱怨。
about that and I get that there's been
关于这一点，我明白已经……
times when I've been approached and I
有时有人会接近我，而我
would rather just be left alone it's
宁愿一个人待着。
annoying to have to reject people it's
拒绝别人真让人恼火。
uncomfortable to be sexualized against
被性化会让人感到不舒服
your will when you don't want to be
当你不想这样做的时候，你的意志依然存在
right I was actually watching something
对，我当时其实在看什么东西。
yesterday in my green room over there
昨天我在那边的休息室里
just because it came up on my phone it
仅仅因为它出现在我的手机上
was an ITV documentary where they just
那是一部ITV纪录片，他们当时就在里面
basically followed a woman at night
基本上是晚上跟踪一个女人。
through a major city with a camera and
带着相机穿过一座大城市
it is pretty horrific the one man comes
真是太可怕了，那个人来了
up to her puts his arm around her in
他走上前，将手臂搭在她肩上。
she's alone at night in the middle of
她独自一人在夜里……
the street context puts his arm around
街头环境让他搂住了他
her and basically stops her hey please
她基本上阻止了她，说了句“嘿，拜托”。
what's your name please another a man
请问你叫什么名字？另一位男士
who's in his 60s or 70s comes up hey do
一个六七十岁的人走过来，嘿，你
you want some piano lessons I play piano
你想学钢琴吗？我会弹钢琴。
would you like some piano and she can't
你想听钢琴曲吗？但她不会。
move down this High Street without
沿着这条商业街走下去
someone making a sound a gesture some
有人发出声音，做出某种手势
kind of proposition like Jesus Christ
类似耶稣基督的那种提议
that's what it's like to be like Justin
这就是做贾斯汀的感觉
Bieber or something it'd be really
比伯或者其他什么人，那真的会很棒。
annoying yeah yeah it's interesting
真烦人，是啊，挺有意思的。
because that behavior is just point
因为那种行为仅仅是点
blank
空白的
unacceptable but what I saw in that
虽然令人无法接受，但我从中看到了什么。
video as well was just how desperate men
视频也展现了男人是多么绝望。
must
必须
be and especially in the the way that
是，尤其是以这种方式
the world has changed following the me
世界在我之后发生了改变。
tooo movement and we understand you know
太过激进，我们明白您知道
what consent really is and the the
同意的真正含义以及
experience that women have been through
女性的经历
I I go there's a subset of men now that
我去那里，现在有一部分男人是这样的
are going to be even more terrified to
他们会更加恐惧
walk up to someone and say hi my name is
走到某人面前说：“你好，我叫……”
Stephen um can we talk like I've done so
斯蒂芬，嗯，我们能像我之前那样谈谈吗？
many consultations with guys who are
多次咨询过一些男士
terrified of being Meed of being
害怕成为米德
cancelled of being like surreptitiously
取消了偷偷摸摸的行为
recorded and humiliated on the
被记录下来并遭受羞辱
internet especially in San Francisco
互联网，尤其是在旧金山
which is sort of like the epicenter for
这有点像是震中
Progressive feminism and politics in
进步女权主义和政治
general I have done cold approaches to
我通常都会进行冷接触式搭讪。
get over my own approach anxiety
克服我自己的焦虑
hundreds and hundreds of times in San
在圣路易斯，这样的事发生了数百次。
Francisco and I have never once been
弗朗西斯科和我从来没有过
slapped or had a drink thrown in my face
被人扇耳光或被人把饮料泼到脸上
or had an angry uncomfortable
或者感到愤怒和不舒服
interaction like the worst I got was I
最糟糕的互动经历就是我
went up to a girl I like hey how you
我走上前去跟我喜欢的女孩打招呼：嘿，你好吗？
doing and without even responding she
她做了，甚至没有回应。
just sort of looked at me and then like
他就看了我一眼，然后就好像……
looked away and I was like o okay all
我别过脸去，心想：哦，好吧，就这样吧。
right not interested understood that was
没错，我对此不感兴趣，我明白了。
the worst thing that happened to me I
我遇到的最糟糕的事情是
think if you approach women in the right
想想如果你用正确的方式接近女性
way you can leave them better than you
你可以用某种方式让他们比你更好。
found them even if they're not
即使他们不是，也要找到他们
interested in having a relationship with
对建立关系感兴趣
you which most women won't be by
你，大多数女性都不会这样。
definition so get used to striking out
所以要习惯被三振出局
so what' you say to those men then that
那么，你对那些人说些什么呢？
are scared of rolling up to someone in
害怕向某人驶近
you know saying
你知道这话
hello it's all about how you approach
你好，关键在于你的态度。
them and you approach them with first of
你首先要接近他们，
all don't ever try to surprise a woman
千万不要试图给女人制造惊喜。
okay because ex well a lot of guys do
好吧，因为很多男人都这样。
it's like they run up excuse me and they
就好像他们跑过来，对不起，然后他们
get really close and they get in their
他们靠得很近，然后就进入了他们的
face they're they're nervous themselves
他们面对着自己，他们自己也很紧张。
and you kind of it's like approaching an
感觉就像在接近一个
animal a deer in the wild you know it's
动物，比如野生的鹿，你知道它是
like here I am I'm making eye contact
就像我现在这样，我正在和对方进行眼神交流。
we've made eye contact for a while I'm
我们已经对视了一会儿了，我
getting up slowly I'm moving towards you
我缓缓起身，向你走来。
here are my hands sort of like
这是我的手，有点像
interacting with the cops sometimes it's
与警察打交道有时会是
like I got nothing at my my sleeve and
就像我袖子里什么都没有一样。
we're going to do this slow and I'm
我们会慢慢来，我是
going to smile I'm going to exude warmth
我要微笑，我要散发温暖。
I'm not going to get in too close I'm
我不会靠得太近。
certainly not going to touch her this
当然不会碰她
bodyy language matter of course it
肢体语言当然很重要。
matters so I have a whole chapter about
这件事很重要，所以我专门用一整章的篇幅来讨论。
the game of please no in the book say
书中“请不要”的游戏
that again okay the game of please no so
好吧，游戏还是不行。
this is a game that I played at Tish so
这是我在Tish玩过的一个游戏
I went to Tish School of the Arts at NYU
我曾就读于纽约大学蒂什艺术学院。
to train as an actor and in my first
接受演员训练，这是我的第一段经历。
semester of acting school we didn't do
我们没有参加表演学校的一个学期。
any acting really we didn't study scenes
我们根本没演戏，也没研究过场景。
we
我们
didn't do plays we played this one game
我们没打过任何战术，只打了这一场比赛。
and we played this game for I think
我们玩这个游戏好像玩了很久。
three or four months straight and the
连续三四个月，
game is called the game of please no and
这款游戏叫做“请不要”游戏。
I've since discovered that this game is
我后来发现这款游戏是
the fundamental game of Human
人类的基本游戏
Relationships it wasn't advertised to me
人际关系方面，他们并没有向我宣传过。
as such but I since understood that this
确实如此，但我后来明白了这一点。
is the core game at the heart of all
是所有游戏的核心。
human interaction which is I'm going to
人际互动，也就是我即将要做的事
you because I want something from you
你，因为我想要从你那里得到些什么。
whether it's a attension sex a dollar a
无论是性吸引力还是金钱
job a house a meal it's like I'm here
工作、房子、饭菜，感觉就像我在这里一样。
because I want something or else I'd be
因为我想要某样东西，否则我就会……
somewhere else right and the default
在其他地方，对吧，还有默认设置
answer is no can I have a dollar
答案是否定的，我可以要一美元吗？
no hey could I take you out for a drink
嘿，我可以请你出去喝一杯吗？
sometime oh no could I have this job no
有时，哦不，我能得到这份工作吗？不
no definitely not so and there's some
不，绝对不是这样，而且还有一些
wisdom to that like I say in the book
正如我在书中提到的那样，这其中蕴含着智慧。
The Universe lives closed if the default
如果默认设置，宇宙将处于封闭状态。
answer to the universe was yes if we
宇宙的答案是肯定的，如果我们
just lived in this like Genie bottle
就像住在阿拉丁神灯里一样
where if we just think it and we want it
如果我们只是想想，如果我们想要它，那会怎样呢？
our wishes are effortlessly satisfied
我们的愿望轻而易举地就实现了。
the world the universe would have been
宇宙本该是怎样的世界？
stripped of all of its resources by now
现在它的所有资源都已被剥夺殆尽。
like if human beings continued to exist
就像人类继续存在一样
it would be a very desolate and awful
那将是一个非常荒凉和可怕的地方
place for the survivors I would think so
我想，那应该是幸存者的归宿。
the default answer to every request is
所有请求的默认答案是
no why because it costs nothing to want
不，为什么？因为想要它不需要任何成本。
but it costs something to give and
但付出是要付出代价的。
there's that inherent asymmetry
存在那种固有的不对称性
so in general the way to overcome that
所以，克服这个问题的一般方法是……
asymmetry is if I want something I'll in
不对称性是指如果我想要什么东西，我会……
exchange for what I want to get from you
用我想从你那里得到的东西来交换
I might give you something of
我可能会给你一些东西
commensurate value that you want from me
您希望从我这里获得的相应价值
that's the pro-social solution that has
这是有利于社会的解决方案。
brought people into relationships and
将人们带入恋爱关系
Society of all
全社会
kinds is the the basis of relationship
种类是关系的基础
is the transaction of unequal Goods of
是交换不等价货物的交易
comparable
可比
value and when that doesn't happen for
价值，以及当这种情况没有发生时
whatever reason no relationship
无论出于何种原因，都没有关系
exists nor can exist in any case going
存在，也不可能存在，无论如何
back to the game of please no the game
回到“请不要玩这个游戏”的游戏
of please know as it was taught to me in
请记住，这是我在……中学到的。
this acting class always has two players
这个表演课总是有两​​个学生。
there's always let's say a wter and a
总会有，比如说，一个水和一个
giver M the wter can only say the word
给予者 M 只能说出这个词
please The Giver can only say the words
请赐予者只能说出这些话
no and yes and The Giver has to start
不，是，《赐予者》必须开始
from a no position and the game
从零开始，比赛
continues for as long as it needs to
持续进行，直到达到所需时间。
until the wter can change the no into a
直到水能将“否”变成“
yes using only the word please okay so
是的，只用“请”这个词，好的。
how would we do that
我们该如何做到这一点呢？
well what you learn like I was saying
就像我刚才说的，你学到的东西。
earlier is that a word is both a
前面提到的一个词既是……
semantic yeah message but it's also a
语义上的“是”消息，但它也是一个
container for emotion so you're really
情感的容器，所以你真的
leveraging the emotion of and the
利用情感和
non-verbal communication if you're
如果你是非语言沟通者
stripped of the ability to use your
被剥夺了使用你的能力
words you have to use facial expression
你必须用面部表情来表达。
you have to use tone of voice you have
你必须运用你拥有的语气。
to use gesture you have to use body
要使用手势，你必须使用身体
language and what you what you decide
语言以及你的决定
what you discover is that you can
你会发现你可以
communicate all kinds of different
沟通各种不同的
intentions without using words at all
无需言语，便可表达意图
okay so if I pick up this book and I go
好的，如果我拿起这本书，然后我
I I gesture to pass it towards you for
我示意把它递给你
people that can't see us right now and I
现在看不到我们的人和我
go
去
please sure yes thank you so you've just
当然可以，谢谢。所以你刚刚
said yes exactly one of the best ways to
答应了，这正是最好的方法之一
get what you want is polite request okay
礼貌地提出你的要求是可以的。
and there was nothing unusual about your
你的情况并没有什么不寻常之处。
request it seemed like it was a
请求似乎是
completely normal thing and here are we
完全正常的事情，我们就是这样。
have good rapport why wouldn't I take
关系融洽，我为什么不接受呢？
the book from you you know um so what
你送我的那本书，你知道，嗯，所以呢？
I've discovered by watching hundreds and
我通过观看数百个视频发现了这一点
hundreds of those playthroughs is that
数百次这样的游戏体验就是如此。
different strategies tend to emerge in
不同的策略往往会在以下情况下出现：
that game that are predictably
那场游戏是可以预见的
associated with success and you see
与成功相关，你看
these strategies in cocktail lounges in
这些策略在鸡尾酒吧中
corporate boardrooms in exotic bazaars
异国集市里的公司会议室
where you're actually trading spices and
你实际上是在交易香料，
whatnot it's like it's the fundamental
诸如此类，这就像是最基本的
strategies of negotiation right these
这些谈判策略是正确的。
are things like intimidation okay
恐吓之类的行为可以吗？
seduction
诱惑
victimization playfulness friendliness
受害的玩闹友好
straightforwardness
直率
quitting there's all kinds of strategies
戒烟有很多种策略。
that have developed that leaving aside
已经发展起来的，撇开其他因素不谈
the the moral or ethical implications of
道德或伦理方面的影响
those strategies work and they work by
这些策略有效，而且它们通过以下方式发挥作用：
stimulating a certain emotion inside of
激发内心某种情绪
you which is
你，也就是
manipulation and if I can use my tone my
操纵，如果我能利用我的语气……
words my actions to stimulate the right
言辞和行动旨在激发正义
emotion in you then you are going to
然后你就会感受到你的情绪。
move in the
搬进去
direction where I want you to go
我希望你往哪个方向走
basically so in the example of me
基本上就是这样，以我为例。
passing you the book um I used a I
把书递给你，嗯，我用了一个我
picked up the book I presented it to you
我拿起那本书，把它送给了你。
and then in a very soft tone and with a
然后，用非常柔和的语气，
assuring nod I said
我肯定地点了点头，说道
please which made it very clear to you
请告诉我，这让你非常清楚。
there was a couple of things really
确实有几件事。
going on there I guess the first is I've
我想，在那里发生的第一件事就是我已经……
gone to some effort to extend my arm and
我费了些力气才伸出手臂，
now you're going to have to leave me
现在你得离开我了。
hanging yeah or you know the longer my
挂着，是啊，或者你知道，我的时间越长越好
arms the more pain I'm getting in my arm
我的手臂越疼，手臂就越疼
from it being in the air so there's a
因为它在空中，所以存在
little bit of a you know an obligation
有点义务感，你知道的。
on your side to put me out of my my pain
站在你这边，让我摆脱痛苦
because this book is quite heavy lots of
因为这本书很重，而且很多
pages of course and if we were playing
当然还有页面，如果我们在玩游戏的话。
an actual game and I was The Giver I
那是一个真实的游戏，而我扮演的是“赐予者”。
might want to with you a little bit
可能想稍微捉弄你一下
and be like no then I I would have to
如果我回答“不”，那我就不得不……
keep going in till I found a way to get
我一直进去，直到找到办法为止。
you to say yes yeah and you try lots of
你说“是啊”，然后你尝试了很多次。
different things and the most successful
不同的事物以及最成功的
players of this game learn to listen
这款游戏的玩家学会了倾听
with like a third ear because just like
就像长了第三只耳朵一样，因为就像
please can be said in lots of different
“请”可以用很多不同的方式表达。
ways no can be said in lots of different
可以用很多不同的方式来表达“不”。
ways and if you're listening clearly the
方式，如果你仔细聆听的话……
way a person says no always contains a
一个人说“不”的方式总是包含着某种含义。
clue into how they might eventually say
线索，或许能让他们最终说出
yes it's sort of like playing hot and
是的，这有点像玩“热血”游戏。
cold which maybe you did as a kid MH
冷，也许你小时候经历过 MH
somebody would hide someone in the room
有人会把某人藏在房间里。
and you move over here and they go
你搬到这边，他们就走了
colder and then you move over here and
然后你变得更冷，接着你搬到这里来。
oh you're getting warmer so there's cues
哦，你越来越暖和了，所以这是个信号。
in how people respond to you that let
人们对你的反应方式决定了这一点。
you know if you're kind of more or less
你知道，如果你差不多是这样的话
on track and moving in the right
一切进展顺利，朝着正确的方向前进。
direction or you're not and if you're
方向，或者你不是，如果你是
not you kind of have to change Tac until
不，你得稍微改变一下战术，直到
you find that resonance that okay now I
你找到了那种共鸣，现在好了，我
understand you now we're getting
我现在明白了，我们正在获得
somewhere that's why I say like if it
这就是为什么我说“如果是这样”的原因。
works in sales it generally Works in
从事销售工作通常有效
dating what are the biggest mistakes men
约会中男人会犯的最大错误是什么？
make when they're rolling up on a woman
当他们向女人逼近时，会发出这样的声音
so you said you know they might surprise
所以你说你知道他们可能会出乎意料
them in some way they might be shut down
它们可能会以某种方式被关闭。
their personal space by getting a bit
他们通过稍微越界来侵犯他们的个人空间
too close yeah I think most of them are
太近了，是啊，我觉得他们大多数都是。
overc compensations
过度补偿
for their nervousness it's scary to
他们的紧张令人害怕
approach a girl and so there's generally
接近女孩，所以通常情况下
two things that happen one is the men
两件事同时发生，一是男人
hesitate too long yeah and then they get
犹豫太久，然后他们就会……
weird and
奇怪而
stilted like they start to think about
僵硬地，就像他们开始思考……
well what should I say I need a good
我该怎么说呢？我需要一个好的
opener like okay that that line sucks
开头就像“好吧，这句台词太烂了”。
and oh geez oh she's talking to somebody
哦，天哪，她好像在跟人说话。
now it's not a good moment they get to
现在时机不太好，他们得不到……
in their head which generally means they
他们脑子里想的，这通常意味着他们
don't approach but if they do they're
不要靠近，但如果他们靠近，他们就是
generally so like out of the moment and
通常情况下，就像脱离当下一样，
in their minds that their Vibe is just
在他们看来，他们的氛围就是
off and women reject the vibe because
关掉，女性会拒绝这种氛围，因为
they don't come off open and confident
他们表现得不够坦诚自信。
how do I get the vibe you start to
我该如何感受到你开始散发出的那种氛围？
listen you start to listen it's like
你开始听，就像……
sales man the same approach isn't going
销售员沿用同样的方法行不通了。
to work with everyone who walks in your
与走进你房间的每个人一起工作
dealership some guys they're going to
经销商，有些人要去
need the real soft touch and you need to
需要真正柔软的触感，你需要
keep a real big distance and not
保持很远的距离，而且不要
interfere with their own process because
干扰他们自己的过程，因为
they're going to sell themselves on the
他们会把自己推销出去
car other people need a lot of
其他人需要很多车
handholding a lot of guidance and it's
手把手地指导，而且是
not obvious which customers or are which
不清楚哪些客户是哪些客户。
when they first walk in the door yeah
当他们第一次走进门的时候，是的
you have to make some tentative bids and
你需要先提出一些试探性的报价，
learn to listen to their response and be
学会倾听他们的回应，并
flexibly adaptive until you find where
灵活适应，直到找到位置
they're kind of starting to open up guy
他们开始慢慢敞开心扉了。
walks into a cardal ship says hey can I
走进一艘红衣主教船，说：嘿，我可以吗？
help you he's like I don't know I'm just
他帮不了你，他说我不知道​​，我只是
looking around that was not the right
环顾四周，发现那并不正确。
thing he didn't even make iy contact
他甚至都没联系我。
he's just like leave me alone um
他就好像在说“滚开，别烦我”，嗯
but if you were to say something like I
但如果你说类似这样的话……
personally like it in blue like that's
我个人比较喜欢蓝色，就像那样。
kind of a surprising thing and you might
这有点出乎意料，你可能会
turn around it's like that's not what I
转过身来，感觉好像那不是我想要的。
expected you to say I expected you to
我以为你会说，我以为你会
kind of give me the hard
有点难搞。
cell and that created an opportunity for
细胞，这为……创造了机会
curiosity which may have led to a moment
好奇心或许促成了那一刻
of connection which could potentially
可能存在的联系
lead in the direction of an interaction
引导互动方向
which can lead to a sale like it's very
这可能会导致一笔非常划算的销售。
difficult to get a sale without the
没有……就很难完成销售
interaction so you have to put out
互动，所以你必须付出努力
tentative bids and learn to listen to
试探性出价并学会倾听
how people respond okay so the car the
人们的反应很好，所以这辆车
person selling the car would say I
卖车的人会说我
personally like it in blue potentially
我个人比较喜欢蓝色。
okay just as a way to I don't know that
好吧，只是作为一种方式，我不知道。
just came into my mind I don't I like it
我突然想到，我不喜欢这样。
it's quite but it does it evokes
它很安静，但确实能唤起某种感觉。
curiosity because then you would because
出于好奇，因为那样你就会……
then I might respond I only wear black
那我可能会回答说我只穿黑色衣服
so I need something in black but then at
所以我需要一件黑色的东西，但是后来
least you have a bridge one of the best
至少你还有一座桥，而且是最好的桥之一。
pickup lines that I used when I was
我以前用过的搭讪语
getting over my Approach anxiety in San
克服我在圣路易斯的搭讪焦虑
Francisco is i' go up and say hi hey how
弗朗西斯科，我上前打招呼，嘿，你好吗？
you doing what brings you out here
你在这里做着让你来到这里的事情。
tonight and I'd say I'm actually trying
今晚，我觉得我真的在努力。
to get over my Approach anxiety how am I
如何克服我的搭讪焦虑？
doing and that led to an like what do
这样做，然后就产生了类似“做什么”的想法。
you mean approach anxiety well I don't
你是说接近焦虑吗？嗯，我没有。
know if you know this but it's can be
不知道你是否了解这一点，但它可能是
really difficult for guys to approach
男生很难接近
women really I had no idea yeah it's a
女人真的，我完全不知道，是的，这是一个
problem I help guys with that all the
这个问题我都会帮大家解决。
time I figured I should probably get
我觉得我应该去拿
good at it myself what do you mean what
我自己就挺擅长的，你是什么意思？
do you do I kind of help people it's
你觉得我算是帮助别人吗？
like it's like it's interesting and it's
感觉挺有意思的，而且
also vulnerable in a good way because
也正因如此而显得脆弱，这很好。
it's revealing of my present moment
它揭示了我当下的状态
experience vulnerability is such a
体验脆弱性就是这样一种体验。
tricky word because it has a lot of
这是一个棘手的词，因为它有很多……
negative associations with it
它与负面联想有关
performative vulnerability well it's
性能漏洞，嗯，就是
also vulnerable means wound it's like
脆弱也意味着受伤，就像
where I could be hurt it's wound ability
我可能会受伤的地方是它的伤口能力
like why would I tell you where my
我为什么要告诉你我的
Achilles heel is I don't know if you're
我的软肋是我不知道你是否
going to be able to use that information
将会能够利用这些信息
well you know how do I know you're not
你知道我怎么知道你不是吗？
going to weaponize that further down the
之后会进一步将其武器化
road right but
路右边，但是
one more useful definition of
另一个有用的定义
vulnerability is that I am sharing with
脆弱之处在于我正在与他人分享
you my present moment emotional
你此刻的情感
experience whatever that is and that is
体验那是什么，那就是
makes it easier for women to see you
这样女性更容易看到你。
when you start to share and disclose
当你开始分享和披露时
some of your present moment emotional
你此刻的一些情绪
experience it's like using the right
体验就像使用正确的
words for a man it unlocks their
对男人来说，这些话能开启他们的心扉。
understanding and they can kind of like
理解，他们也能有点喜欢
see you more clearly because you're
因为你更能看清你
putting something out there that they
他们把一些东西公之于众
can potentially resonate with they might
可能与他们产生共鸣
not and that's okay you can just find
不，没关系，你可以自己找找。
someone else to play with right but with
找个人一起玩，对吧？但是
in the absence of that it's very
如果没有那件事，那就非常
difficult for a guy to get anything to
男人很难得到任何东西
happen and most guys they they tone down
事情发生了，大多数人都会收敛一些。
that emotion they're very they can be
他们非常能感受到那种情绪
very robotic they can be very monotone
他们非常机械，语气也很单调。
hey hey how you doing um so one way is
嘿嘿，你好吗？嗯，其中一种方法是……
guys screw this up because they get two
伙计们搞砸了，因为他们有两个
in their head and that makes them
他们脑子里想着这些，这使他们
stilted and weird the other way is they
另一种方式是生硬和怪异的。
try to overcome their nervousness by
他们试图通过以下方式克服紧张情绪
overcompensating MH they get really
过度补偿的MH他们真的
drunk they get super bold and handsy
他们喝醉后会变得非常大胆，而且喜欢动手动脚。
because they're trying to be kind of
因为他们试图表现得有点像
dominant
主导的
and I suppose that can work but uh It
我想这或许可行，但是……
generally It generally rubs wom the
一般来说，它通常会摩擦女性
wrong way one of the things I've never
错误的方式，这是我从未做过的事情之一
forgotten from when I was 18 years old
已经忘记了18岁那年的事了
and I was reading those books about um
我当时正在读那些关于……的书。
seduction and pickup Artistry is it
诱惑和搭讪的艺术是吗？
talks about how to deal with a 10 a 10
讨论如何处理10分的情况
out of 10 what they say Well it
他们说（满分10分）嗯
basically says you kind of need to be a
基本上意思是说，你得成为……
bit of an not not an in
有点混蛋，但又不是完全的混蛋
the sense of being rude or whatever but
感觉粗鲁之类的，但是
you kind of need to so say if you were a
如果你是……的话，你多少需要这么说。
10 and we're and we're at dinner I
10，我们正在吃晚饭。
didn't know who you were but there was a
我不知道你是谁，但是有一个
a group of very attractive women here
这里有一群非常漂亮的女性。
and you were the one that I wanted and
而你正是我想要的那个人。
you were the 10 I wouldn't talk to you
你是那10岁，我不会跟你说话的那个人。
right you wouldn't talk to me but the
对，你本来就不跟我说话，但是
strategy it says is to basically pay
据称，该策略基本上就是支付
attention to everybody else and then
先关注其他人，然后再关注其他人。
when the ten tries to talk to you go one
当十号试图和你说话时，就走吧。
second and then just keep talking to
其次，然后继续和……说话
everybody else and it's that small
其他人都一样，而且就这么小。
communication that I um high value that
我非常重视沟通。
um kind of would evoke their interest
嗯，这或许能引起他们的兴趣。
and curiosity why does this man
以及好奇心，为什么这个人会这样做
not maybe P like Panda to me like all
也许不是P像熊猫一样，对我来说就像所有
other men have always done what is it
其他男人总是做着什么事呢？
about him that he's got such confidence
他身上散发着一种自信。
that he will give me a slight neag you
他会稍微否定我一下。
know nines and tens are not a different
要知道九和十没有区别。
species than the fives and sixes and
比五六种物种更甚的物种
what are the women who tend to really be
哪些女性往往真正……
interested in most guys the ones who are
大多数男生都对那些……感兴趣
pursuing the ones who stick around who
追寻那些留下来的人
want those long-term
想要那些长期的
relationships for better for worse
无论好坏，彼此的关系都至关重要。
they're often the ones that the men kind
她们通常是男人们喜欢的那种人。
of kind of have this take it or leave it
有点像是，要么接受，要么放弃。
attitude towards and they're not going
他们的态度，以及他们不打算离开
out of their way which can seem like
避开他们的路，这看起来像是
they're very confident they're very
他们非常自信，他们非常
composed they're self-possessed there
他们在那里表现得很沉着冷静。
might be something special or attractive
或许是某种特别或吸引人的东西。
about this guy because he's not pursuing
关于这个人，因为他没有主动追求。
me I'm pursuing him which can reduce
我正在追求他，这可能会减少
cognitive dissonance in the direction of
认知失调的方向
increasing attraction because think
因为思考而增加吸引力
about it I don't usually go out of my
关于这件事，我通常不会外出。
way for people and yet I'm going out of
为人们开路，但我却要出去
my way for this man why am I doing that
我为什么要这样做？我为什么要用这种方式来对待这个人？
it must be because I really like this
一定是因为我真的很喜欢这个
guy right sometimes our emotions only
有时候，我们的情绪确实如此。
arise out of our Behavior people
源于我们的行为
sometimes think we have an emotion and
有时我们认为我们有某种情绪，
we act sometimes we act and then we have
我们有时会采取行动，然后我们就会……
an emotion right so getting PE it's like
一种情绪，对吧？所以，做体育锻炼就像……
it's not possible to get others to like
不可能让别人喜欢你
you more by liking them more that's one
你越喜欢他们，就越能了解他们，这是其中之一。
of the biggest errors in
最大的错误
dating and one of the best little
约会和最好的小事之一
strategies to increase interest is to
提高兴趣的策略是
ask other people to do things for you
请别人为你做事
because it takes advantage of this
因为它利用了这一点。
little cognitive hack that I just
我刚刚学到的一个小认知技巧
described you don't Stephen you don't go
描述一下，你没有，斯蒂芬，你没有去
out of your way doing favors for people
尽你所能帮助别人
if I asked you a small but reasonable
如果我问你一个虽小但合理的问题
favor and you executed it then
你当时就帮了忙，然后就执行了。
consciously or not you're going to think
无论你是否意识到，你都会想……
wow I don't usually do favors I did a
哇，我通常不帮人忙，但我这次帮了。
favor for Orion he might be a pretty
帮猎户座一个忙，他可能相当不错
decent dude like maybe there's something
他是个还不错的人，也许有什么事吧。
to this guy because give me an example
给这个人举个例子
so if I say could you could you grab
所以如果我说你能抓住吗？你能抓住吗？
that for me one second and I I point
对我来说，那一秒钟，我指着
that's one of the easiest ways to do it
这是最简单的方法之一。
sometimes it's just I've seen it in
有时候，我只是在……中看到过它
pickup where you can just say you're
在那里接单，你只需说你是
talking to somebody and be like uh you
跟别人说话的时候，会突然冒出一句“呃，你”。
know it's a little loud can we just
我知道它有点吵，我们能……
let's just step like two steps to the
让我们一步一步地来吧。
side just that two steps in complying
仅此两步即可遵守规定。
with that reasonable
如此合理的
request it elevates unconscious
请求它提升无意识
attraction it also is an opportunity to
吸引力也带来了机会
create what you might call a yes chain
建立所谓的“同意链”。
which is related to um foot in the door
这与“踏入大门”有关。
which is you're more likely to comply
也就是说，你更有可能遵守规定。
with a larger request if I first get you
如果我先联系你，我会提出更大的要求。
to consent to a number of smaller
同意若干较小的
reasonable requests first it's not the
首先，提出合理的要求，这不是……
only way but it's one way to potentially
唯一的方法，但这可能是实现目标的一种途径。
undermine resistance
削弱抵抗
and what if I'm a woman because a lot of
如果我是女性呢？因为很多……
women are struggling with the way that
女性正在努力应对以下问题：
the world has changed and this sort of
世界已经改变，而这种……
move towards dating apps and online um
转向约会应用程序和在线
dating and they don't have the the it's
约会，但他们没有那种感觉。
not socially acceptable typically for a
通常来说，这在社会上是不可接受的。
woman or it's not socially typical for a
对于女性来说，或者说对于女性来说，这不符合社会惯例
woman to roll up to a guy in a
女人开车接近一个男人
supermarket or wherever else and start
去超市或其他任何地方开始
to proposition him it's typically
向他求婚通常是
thought that they're generally bad at it
认为他们通常都不擅长这个。
I just have to say like I've had some
我只想说，我好像已经……
women approach me and they're not good
接近我的女性，她们都不太好。
maybe most guys aren't at picking women
或许大多数男人都不擅长挑选女人。
up either but some guys do get good at
两者都有可能，但有些人确实很擅长。
it m they make it like their job to
他们把它当成自己的工作一样对待
learn how to seduce or pick up women at
学习如何勾引或搭讪女性
least for a few months but most women
至少几个月，但大多数女性
when they've approached me they have
当他们接近我时，他们有
very poor
非常差
game what should a woman be thinking
游戏中女人应该想些什么
about when she approaches a man it's
当她接近一个男人时，情况是这样的……
probably best for women to
可能对女性来说最好
not roll up on men the way that men
不要像男人那样对待男人
often roll up on women I did a series
我经常骚扰女性，我做了一系列
about this which is reminding women that
关于这一点，它提醒女性：
for the vast majority of our history
在我们历史的大部分时间里
women have been the initiators they've
女性一直是她们的倡导者
just initiated indirectly with plausible
只是间接地、看似合理地开始了。
deniability so the most stereotypical
否认，所以是最典型的
example maybe you'll appreciate this
例如，也许你会喜欢这个。
given your culture is the dropping of
鉴于你们的文化是放弃
the handkerchief of the Victorian lady
维多利亚时代女士的手帕
as she's walking in the park and she
当她在公园里散步时，她
sees in the corner of her eye an
她眼角瞥见一个
attractive man that she might want to
她可能会喜欢的那种有魅力的男人
initiate a conversation with and as
发起与……的对话
she's passing by his bench without
她从他的长椅旁经过，没有
noticing the hand Chief falls out of her
注意到酋长的手从她身上掉了下来
pocket which creates an opportunity for
口袋创造了机会
the man to notice it pick it up and say
注意到它的人捡起它说
Excuse Me Miss but I believe you dropped
小姐，不好意思，但我认为您掉落了。
this oh my how absolutely clumsy of me
我的天哪，我真是太笨了。
my goodness and suddenly boom she's in a
我的天哪，突然砰的一声，她就……
conversation with a man that she chose
她与一位她选择的男人交谈
to have a conversation with and if for
和……交谈，如果……
whatever reason the guy turns out to be
无论那家伙最终被证明是出于什么原因
a total adult she could just say oh
她完全是个成年人，可以直接说“哦”。
thank you for this but I'm late for tea
谢谢你，但我喝茶要迟到了。
and she can just kind of Scamper off
然后她就可以迅速溜走了。
because she has the plausible
因为她有合理的
deniability that she didn't do this on
她否认自己没有做过这件事。
purpose
目的
so women do it with their eyes and stuff
所以女人会用眼神之类的东西来表达。
that's what I say it's like the come
我就是这么说的，就像……
hither stare and I I did it really badly
她盯着我看，我做得真糟糕。
in that episode but I was trying to
在那一集中，但我当时试图
demonstrate what that might look like
演示一下它可能是什么样子
eye contact is extremely intimate one of
眼神交流是非常亲密的交流方式之一。
the things I say in that episode that I
我在那集节目里说的那些话
don't think many women know is that if
很多女性可能不知道，如果
you and I didn't know each other and we
你我素不相识，而我们
were out at a
当时在外面
bar and I just like looked right into
酒吧，我径直往里看了一眼。
your eyes for 3 seconds I think he
你盯着我看了3秒钟，我想他
wanted to fight exactly even there this
即使在那里，我也想战斗。
nervous laughter which can potentially
紧张的笑声可能会
cover okay this is getting a little
封面好了，这有点……
tense and maybe I'm trying to deescalate
气氛紧张，也许我正在试图缓和局势。
it by smiling and showing that I'm not a
通过微笑表明我不是……
threat but absolutely unsustained
威胁，但完全没有持续性
sustained eye contact between two
两人之间持续的眼神交流
strange men is an aggressive tactic for
对陌生男子来说，这是一种咄咄逼人的策略。
more than a couple seconds it's going be
超过几秒钟就会……
like can I help you is there a problem
我能帮您什么吗？有什么问题吗？
here he just looked at you you know um
他刚才就看着你，你知道吗？
and why because it's too intimate I
为什么？因为这太私密了。
don't know who you are dude why do you
我不知道你是谁，老兄，你为什么……
think that you can get that close to me
你觉得你能离我那么近吗？
you could be on the other side of the
你可能在另一边
bar but eye contact it feels like you're
酒吧里，但眼神交流感觉就像你在……
inside me it's amazing so women can use
我体内的感觉很神奇，所以女性可以使用
eye contact to
眼神交流
their benefit where they can basically
他们的好处基本上就在于此
call the men that they want to interact
打电话给他们想互动的男士
with to them but they have to be willing
对他们来说，但他们必须愿意
to do that if they're not willing to
如果他们不愿意这样做，那就去做吧
drop the handkerchief or look them in
扔掉手帕或者看着他们
the eye I mean that's sort of like the
眼睛，我的意思是，那有点像……
minimum necessary
最低必要
Behavior where does love fit into all of
行为中，爱扮演着怎样的角色？
this and what is love then because if if
那么，爱又是什么呢？因为如果如果
we're talking about you know this being
我们正在谈论你知道的这个
a transaction relationships really being
交易关系实际上是
about transaction of value where does
关于价值交易，在哪里
love fit MH and is love just when the
爱适合MH，爱就是当
transaction of value is equal well I
交易价值相等。
think that's a very satisfying
我觉得这非常令人满意。
relationship when the transaction is
当交易存在关系时
equal like I talk about this on the
就像我之前谈到的那样
channel in good relationships the
在良好的人际关系中发挥渠道作用
transaction is invisible it's just like
交易是无形的，就像……
your needs and wants are kind of
你的需求和愿望有点像
invisibly and effortlessly being met at
悄无声息、毫不费力地被遇见
the same time my needs and wants are
与此同时，我的需求和愿望是
invisibly and effortlessly being met and
悄无声息、毫不费力地被满足
so we have the B is for continued
所以，B 代表持续。
satisfaction which might be as good as
满意度可能与
it gets when it comes to relationships
谈到人际关系，情况就是这样。
in many respects love is something that
在许多方面，爱是……
is totally different beast and it is
完全是另一种情况，而且是
very beautiful and it is very
非常漂亮，而且非常
Noble and
高贵而
transformative but there's also a lot of
具有变革性，但也有很多
misunderstandings about love so for
关于爱情的误解
example I call things that cannot be
例如，我把那些不能……的东西称为
bought or earned non-trans Goods or ntgs
购买或赚取的非交易性商品或非交易性商品
and of those ntgs the three I think most
而在这三个NTG中，我认为最……
important ones for relationship are
对一段关系来说重要的因素有
loyalty friendship and
忠诚、友谊和
love you cannot do anything to buy or
爱你，你什么也买不到，或者
earn those
赚取这些
things those are always gifts that are
那些东西总是礼物
given at the spontaneous pleasure of the
出于自发的愉悦而给予
giver and they always come with no
施予者，他们总是无私奉献。
strings attached if they are true gifts
如果是真正的礼物，那就应该附带条件。
otherwise they're just giving in the
否则他们就等于屈服了。
hopes of receiving which is a bid for
希望收到一份竞标书
transaction and a lot of things that go
交易以及很多其他事情
under the guise of loyalty friendship
以忠诚和友谊为幌子
and love are really bids for transaction
爱情和竞价实际上是交易。
mhm
嗯
so you have to be careful about that but
所以你得注意这一点。
if there's nothing that you can do to
如果你无能为力的话
buy or earn love let's start with
买爱还是赚爱？让我们从……开始吧。
friendliness because that's maybe an
友善，因为那或许是一种
easier one it's like you can't make
更简单的那个，就好像你不能做一样。
anyone be your
任何人都可以成为你的
friend like you could be the most
像你这样的朋友可能是最棒的
amicable cheerful
友善的、快乐的
easygoing guy who's always down for
性格随和，总是乐于助人
whatever and they're still going to be a
不管怎样，他们仍然会是……
lot of people who don't want to be your
很多人不想成为你的
friend in fact many of those people will
事实上，很多这样的人都会成为朋友。
choose to be friends with people who are
选择与那些
disagreeable or kind of dumb or
令人不快的，或者有点笨的，或者
difficult or stubborn it's like people
难搞或固执就像人一样
why do people choose as their friends
人们为什么会选择朋友
the people that they're friends with
他们的朋友
it's just like it wasn't like I I
就好像我以前从未经历过一样。
interviewed a bunch of different
采访了很多不同的人
candidates and I decided that you were
候选人和我一致认为你是
the most friendly guy and so I decided
他是最友善的人，所以我决定
to make you my friend here's a friend
为了和你成为朋友，我送你一个朋友
offer you know that would be that would
你知道，那会是那样的。
seem so strange to us right so the fact
对我们来说，这似乎很奇怪，对吧？
of the matter is for whatever reason and
这件事无论出于什么原因，
it's kind of missterious and
这有点神秘，
unfathomable I've decided to make you my
难以想象，我决定让你成为我的
friend and that doesn't necessarily mean
朋友，但这并不一定意味着
that you're gonna be my like you're I'm
你会像我一样成为我的。
you're gonna make me your friend right
你会让我成为你的朋友，对吧？
it doesn't necessarily go both ways
这并不一定意味着双向都适用
right but um you can't buy or earn
对，但是，嗯，你既买不到也赚不到。
friendship you can't buy or earn loyalty
友谊是买不到的，忠诚也无法赢得。
you can't buy or earn love they're given
爱是买不到也挣不到的，它是别人给予的。
at the spontaneous pleasure of The Giver
《赐予者》带来的自发愉悦
with no strings attached otherwise we
除此之外，我们没有任何附加条件
would functionally be ascribing a value
从功能上讲，就是赋予一个值
to them and we would say that these
对他们来说，我们会说这些
things are transactable so you can't
物品是可交易的，所以你不能
have it both ways another way to think
两种方式都行，另一种思考方式
about it
关于它
is people aren't always in relationships
人们并非总是处于恋爱关系中。
with people
与人
love and they certainly can love people
他们爱人，而且他们当然能够爱人。
they're not in relationships with like I
他们不像我一样和我谈恋爱。
know people who are in very intact
认识一些保存得非常完好的人。
stable marriages where there's not a lot
稳定的婚姻，其中没有太多
of love and maybe in those marriages
爱情，或许也存在于那些婚姻中
they both secretly love some EX in the
他们俩都暗恋着某个前任。
past that they couldn't get for whatever
除此之外，他们就再也得不到任何好处了。
reason so like it's certainly not enough
理由如此充分，显然远远不够。
to explain relationships on the basis of
基于以下方式解释关系
love because people rarely end up with
爱，因为人们很少最终……
the people who love them the most
最爱他们的人
so if you can be in relationships
所以如果你能谈恋爱的话
Without Love For Better or For Worse and
没有爱，无论境遇好坏
you can love people that you're not in
你可以爱上那些与你无关的人。
relationships with then at the very
与当时的关系
least we have to conclude that those two
至少我们不得不得出结论，这两个
constructs are independent of each
这些构造彼此独立。
other like when you love someone you're
其他情况，比如当你爱上某人时，你会……
in a relationship with it's kind of a
与某人建立关系有点像
happy accident it's a
美丽的意外，这是一个
coincidence maybe that's for the best
或许这只是巧合，也许这样反而是最好的。
but like there's nothing you can do to
但好像你对此无能为力
get the other person to love you it's
让对方爱上你
their decision to do it or not and if
他们是否决定这样做，以及如果
there's something you could do then we
然后你可以做点什么，我们
make love a transactable thing so it's
把性爱变成一种可以交易的东西，所以它
like pick your poison and I don't think
就像二选一，我觉得没必要。
it is I don't think it's a transactable
我认为这不是可交易的。
thing what role has pornography played
色情作品扮演了什么角色？
in all this you know you must see speak
在这一切中，你知道你必须看和说。
to a lot of men in your practice that
对你诊所里很多男性来说，
are suffering with pornography
正在遭受色情制品的困扰
addictions or that is it making us
成瘾，或者说，是它让我们变得如此吗？
harder to find relationships is it
建立恋爱关系更难了，是吗？
changing our ability to keep and hold
改变我们持有和保持的能力
relationships is it changing how we sh
人际关系是否正在改变我们相处的方式
up during sex it can like I've done some
在性爱过程中，它可能会像我做过一些事情一样。
consultations with guys who have used
向使用过的人咨询
pornography very intensely and
非常强烈地沉迷于色情作品
extensively do they tell you not always
他们会详细地告诉你，但并非总是如此。
generally when that's the issue that's
通常情况下，如果问题出在这一点上，那就是……
the issue they come to me for it's very
他们来找我咨询的问题非常
rare where it kind of comes out in the
这种情况很少见，它有点像是在……
course of things and then lots of things
一系列的事情，然后还有很多其他的事情
suddenly make sense right usually they
突然就说得通了，对吧？通常他们
come out upfront and say this is the
坦诚地说出来，这就是
reason and it's a very uh there's a lot
原因有很多，而且非常……嗯……
of Shame associated with this with
与此相关的羞耻感
addiction in general but with this
成瘾通常指成瘾，但这种成瘾尤其如此。
Addiction in particular like I do video
尤其是像我做视频那样的成瘾问题
conference calls with folks from all
与各界人士进行电话会议
over the world but people don't have to
遍布世界各地，但人们不必如此
turn their camera on if they don't want
如果他们不想打开摄像头，就让他们自己打开。
to and by far the most common topic that
迄今为止，最常见的话题是
men will turn their camera off for is
男人会因为什么原因而关闭摄像头
discusting pornography addiction like
令人作呕的色情成瘾
they don't want to be looked at they
他们不想被人注视。
don't want to be seen which can make it
不想被人看见，这可能会……
easier to actually be honest it's like
说实话其实更容易，就像
the confessional there's this dark place
忏悔室里有个黑暗的地方。
I don't have to look you in the eye and
我不需要看着你的眼睛，
share this shameful thing which might
分享这件令人羞耻的事
make it more conducive to share it get
使其更有利于分享
it out and discuss it and do something
拿出来讨论一下，然后采取行动。
about it so I can understand that
了解一下，这样我才能明白。
but it has completely changed the game
但这彻底改变了游戏规则。
of mating and dating especially if you
尤其是在交配和约会方面
operate under the assumption that in
假设在
general men attempt to exchange
将军们试图交换
resources for sexual opportunity and
性机会资源和
women attempt to exchange sexual
女性试图交换性
opportunity for
机会
resources in the context of that if both
在该背景下，如果两者兼备，则资源
parties could get what they want more
各党派更容易得到他们想要的东西
easily more safely and more cheaply in
更容易、更安全、更便宜地
other ways then it would make rational
除此之外，还有其他方法可以使其合理化。
economic sense for them to do so like
从经济角度来看，这样做对他们来说很合适。
only fans only fans is a fantastic ftic
OnlyFans OnlyFans 是一个很棒的 ftic
way for women to transact their sexual
女性进行性交易的方式
relation opportunity for resources in a
资源关系机会
safe
安全的
convenient and easy way like we'll talk
像我们这样方便简单的方式交谈
about men this is really interesting
关于男性的这一点真的很有意思。
because
因为
potentially women have always kind of
女性可能一直都有某种程度的
wanted to be with the the rich guy but
她想和那个有钱人在一起，但是
potentially for the first time in human
这可能是人类历史上第一次
history it might be easier for the
历史或许对某些人来说更容易些
average woman to get1 from a million men
普通女性从一百万男性中能得到 1 个
than to get a million dollars from one
比从一个人那里得到一百万美元更重要
like the desire for a million dollars
就像渴望一百万美元一样
hasn't gone anywhere but how you might
并没有去任何地方，但你可能会怎么做呢？
go about getting it changes given the
鉴于情况的变化，采取相应措施来获取它。
incentives and the opportunities in play
激励措施和机会
and you can moralize about women doing
你可以对女性的行为进行道德评判。
this or you can moralize about men using
或者你可以就男人使用这种行为进行道德评判。
pornography it's not going to change
色情内容不会改变。
anything like if shame worked it would
如果羞耻感真的有效，那它就会……
have worked by now I would think so I
我觉得现在应该已经奏效了。
think that rather than trying to lean
与其试图倾斜，不如考虑一下
into that social intervention maybe we
也许我们可以参与到这种社会干预中来。
can understand why it is that women's
可以理解为什么女性的
might get trapped in this way and Men
可能会陷入这种困境，而男人
might get trapped in this way because it
可能会因此陷入这种困境
does seem to be pretty gendered right
确实看起来很有性别歧视，对吧？
there's not a lot of only fans creators
OnlyFans 创作者并不多。
who are men and if it's not only fans
谁是男性？如果不仅仅是粉丝的话。
which is pretty hardcore for a lot of
这对很多人来说都相当硬核。
women it's like Instagram it's social
女性就像Instagram一样，是一种社交方式。
media that they they get trapped because
媒体让他们陷入困境，因为
they get attention they get emotional
他们获得关注，他们变得情绪化
validation they get the dopamine hit
他们通过验证获得了多巴胺刺激
from being liked from being seen that
因被人喜欢而获得关注
goes my plan B um so we use the word
我的B计划开始了，所以我们用了这个词。
trapped are you using that intentionally
被困住了，你是故意用这个词的吗？
yeah because these aren't the same it's
是的，因为它们不一样。
like I'm not you could certainly make
就像我不是你当然可以做的那样
the argument that pornography is not the
认为色情作品并非……的论点
same as an actual sexual relationship
与实际的性关系相同
I'm not arguing that it is but
我并不是说它就是这样，但是
apparently it's similar enough that a
显然它与……足够相似
lot of men can't tell the difference or
很多男人分不清这两者的区别。
at least they can tell the difference
至少他们能分辨出区别。
but it's negligible given the expenses
但考虑到开支，这笔费用可以忽略不计。
and the costs involved don't accept the
所涉及的成本无法接受
substitute kind of like eating like fake
替代品有点像吃假货
meat like I talk about that why do we
就像我谈论的那种肉一样，为什么我们
have an obesity epidemic is because
肥胖症流行的原因在于
currently there's all this processed
目前所有这些处理过程都已完成。
food stuff that seems to be somewhat
看起来像某种食物
indistinguishable from Whole Foods that
与全食超市（Whole Foods）几乎没有区别
actually nourish you especially because
实际上，它能滋养你，尤其因为
the processed food stuffs are generally
加工食品通常是
full of salts and sugars and things that
富含盐、糖和其他物质
you are programmed to want to put into
你被设定为想要投入
your body through Millennia of nutrient
你的身体经历了数千年的营养积累。
poor evolutionary conditions like these
像这样的恶劣进化条件
things resonate with male attention
事物会引起男性的注意
pornography resonates with male
色情作品能引起男性的共鸣。
attention I think I read an article
注意，我想我读过一篇文章
recently where starlink was brought to
最近，星链被带到了
some remote tribe in the Amazon and a
亚马逊地区的一些偏远部落和
month later the guys were addicted to
一个月后，这群家伙就上瘾了。
porn like they spent all day watching
他们好像整天都在看色情片一样
pornography and so that's kind of one of
色情作品，所以这算是其中之一吧。
the things I talk about in the book is
我在书中谈到的内容是：
that a lot of the things that we're
我们所做的事情很多
going through are not really moral
经历这些事其实并不道德
lapses and making it a moral issue and
失误并将其上升为道德问题
about shame is one it's it's just not
关于羞耻感，这只是其中之一，它根本不是。
going to
前往
work like generally when people are
就像人们通常那样工作
ashamed they just hide better
他们羞于启齿，只是更好地隐藏起来。
which doesn't make the problem go away
但这并不能解决问题。
it kind of makes it more
这反而让它更……
intractable if you actually want to
如果你真的想这么做，那将难以实现。
change Behavior you have to understand
改变行为，你需要理解
why people are doing it you have to kind
为什么人们会这样做，你必须友善
of do a functional analysis figure out
进行功能分析以找出
what problem this acts as a solution for
它解决了什么问题？
and then to offer reasonable alternative
然后提出合理的替代方案
solutions to that problem and what are
解决该问题的方法是什么？
the reasonable alternative solutions to
合理的替代方案
that problem I guess the the most
我想，这个问题最主要的原因就是它。
important question which I've missed
我错过了一个重要的问题
here is is it a problem pornography yeah
这里，色情作品是个问题吗？是的。
is the like if if the world
如果世界就像那样
became a only fans Marketplace as it
成为 OnlyFans 市场，因为它
relates to relationships and sex where
涉及人际关系和性
men are getting their you know their
男人们正在获得他们的，你知道他们的
sexual whatever they want their sexual
他们想要性方面的任何东西
attention from only fans and women are
OnlyFans 和女性的关注
selling that is that a problem if men
卖这个东西如果男人……那就是个问题吗？
are you know jerking off all day at home
你是不是整天在家自慰？
behind their computer screens and women
她们躲在电脑屏幕后面，还有女人
are in the other side of the computer
位于电脑的另一侧
screen selling images of their feet to
屏幕销售他们脚部的照片
men is that is that a problem
男人就是这样，这是个问题吗？
depends on how you look at it right so
这取决于你怎么看待这个问题，对吧？
I'm of the mind
我心怀善念
that the game will go on the game will
比赛将继续进行。
go on long after you and I are gone I
即使你我都已不在人世，我的生命依然会继续下去。
don't think that this whatever we're
别以为这就是我们所处的这个环境
passing through spells the end of
穿过这里就意味着结束
civilization as we know it the end of
我们所知的文明的终结
sexual relationships things will
性关系的事情会
continue to change and evolve and both
持续变化和发展，两者
sides will adapt and the goal of the
双方都会做出调整，而目标是……
game is to play for as long as possible
游戏的目标是尽可能长时间地进行下去。
okay but better question then is it a
好的，但更好的问题是，它是一个
problem on the individual level I think
我认为这是个人层面的问题。
can be so the man that comes to you with
可以这样，那个来找你的人
this is a problem mhm what are the
这是一个问题，嗯，是什么？
symptoms of that problem going to be in
这个问题的症状将会出现
his life he's never had a
他的一生中从未有过
relationship but he wants one yeah he
恋爱关系，但他想要一段恋爱关系，是的，他
still lives in his parents' house this
他现在仍然住在父母家。
is really important because you have to
这非常重要，因为你必须
understand that sex is not just about
要明白，性不仅仅是……
sex there's something called sublimation
性方面，有一种叫做升华的东西。
have you heard this term before I have
你以前听过这个词吗？我听过。
but I don't know it I think it comes
但我不知道，我觉得它会来的。
also from
也来自
psychoanalysis and it's the idea that
精神分析及其理念是：
certain impulses inside of us are real
我们内心的某些冲动是真实的。
they're powerful and yet they're
它们很强大，但它们
socially
社会
unacceptable the libido the desire for
不可接受的性欲，对……的渴望
sex is never going to go away because
性永远不会消失，因为
it's connected to the life force itself
它与生命力本身相连。
through sex new life gets created if the
通过性行为，如果……，就能创造新的生命。
libido were actually domesticated it
性欲实际上已被驯化
would be very bad for Humanity that's
这对人类来说将是非常糟糕的。
why sex is always kind of like this wild
为什么性总是像这样狂野
west this untamable Wilderness that
向西，这片难以驯服的荒野
exists even the in the heart of the most
即使在最深处也存在
repressive societies on the planet like
地球上像这样的压迫性社会
it cannot be tamed and we shouldn't try
它无法驯服，我们不应该尝试。
to tame it too much right so that said
驯服得太过火了，对吧？所以说……
we can't give free reign to our sexual
我们不能放任自己的性欲。
impulses all the time life would be
生活中处处充满冲动，生活将会是
chaos right so what folks generally
混乱，所以人们通常会怎么做？
learn to do is to Channel or sublimate
学会如何引导或升华
that sexual energy into other pro-social
这种性能量会转化为其他亲社会行为
activities or behaviors socially
社交活动或行为
acceptable behaviors exactly starting a
可接受的行为，确切地说，是从
company or building roads or writing a
公司或修建道路或写作
book see the thing that's why I'm an
这本书让我明白了为什么我是一个
entrepreneur because I was sublimating
因为我当时正在升华，所以我成为了企业家
my sexual ures potentially probably and
我的性尿液可能和
what what I'm getting at is that if you
我的意思是，如果你
if you give men the opportunity to exist
如果你给男人存在的机会
in a perpetually sexually satisfied
在持续的性满足中
state which is what freely distributed
国家，也就是自由分配的
and accessible pornography does then you
那么，方便获取的色情内容就会出现。
take away that power source that serves
移除那个供能的电源
for pro-social action ah it's not just
对于亲社会行为而言，啊，这不仅仅是
that these men aren't going to be having
这些人不会有
sex with real women they're not going to
和真正的女人发生性关系，她们不会
have the energy and the drive to take
有精力和动力去……
risks like applying for that job or
申请那份工作之类的风险
doing something where they might
做一些他们可能会做的事情
fail like the consequences to a
失败的后果就像……
diminished libido redound throughout
性欲减退贯穿始终
civilization civilization is built on
文明建立在……之上
the repression of the
对……的镇压
libido so you want horny men that can't
性欲旺盛，所以你想要的是那种性欲旺盛却无法满足的男人。
horny men are really useful because
好色的男人其实很有用，因为
horny men will do all kinds of
好色的男人会做各种各样的事
incredible things to satisfy that urge
令人难以置信的事情满足了这种渴望
it's actually pro-socially useful to
实际上，这样做对社会有益。
keep men in a horny
让男人保持性欲旺盛
state but think about it it's like if if
状态，但仔细想想，就像如果如果
I'm if I'm not hungry why would I assume
如果我不饿，我为什么要假设……
the risks and costs of
风险和成本
hunting and so if I'm doped up on weed
狩猎，所以如果我吸食了大麻的话
and I'm using porn and I'm just in this
我在看色情片，我就身处其中。
like totally relaxed anesthetized State
就像完全放松的麻醉状态
then why would I even move let alone do
那我为什么要搬家，更别提做什么了？
anything worth doing with my life
我生命中任何值得做的事情
and men in that trap are aware of this
身陷囹圄的人都明白这一点。
and they're ambivalent just like most
他们和大多数人一样，态度矛盾。
addictions they know the alcohol is
他们知道自己对酒精上瘾了。
killing them but they also can't stop
杀死他们，但他们也无法阻止
drinking like there's something really
喝得好像真的有什么事发生一样
deep and dark about that addiction same
关于那种成瘾，既深刻又黑暗。
thing with
和
porn they're ambivalent they want to
他们对色情片的态度很矛盾，他们想要……
stop but they often don't and they need
但他们往往不会停下来，而且他们需要
help they certainly don't need shame and
帮助他们，他们当然不需要羞耻感，而且
judgment I was thinking playing through
我一直在思考，通过游戏来判断。
the the guy that calls you and then you
那个给你打电话的人，然后你
know he hears you say this I don't know
我知道他听见了你说这些话，我不知道
if if this is what you'd say or not but
如果你会这么说的话，或者不会的话，但是
if he arrives at that conclusion that
如果他得出这样的结论：
everything you said is correct that
你说的都对。
watching pornography is basically taking
观看色情片基本上就是一种……
away his life force energy which is
他的生命力被夺走了。
making him unproductive and unmotivated
这使他变得效率低下且缺乏动力。
and he's not going to the gym because he
他不去健身房是因为他
can just jerk off watching only fans
可以一边看OnlyFans一边撸管
whatever how do how do you get him to
不管怎样，你该如何让他……
change his behavior It's Tricky there's
改变他的行为，这很棘手。
lots of things that you can do I learned
我学到了很多你可以做的事情。
a lot of those things when I was working
我工作的时候做了很多这样的事情
in addiction for a couple of years
吸毒成瘾几年了
however all of those things are Prelude
然而，所有这些都是序曲
to not doing the thing anymore
不再做这件事了
yeah one thing I learned from working
是的，我从工作中学到的一件事是……
with addicts is that Insight is not
对于成瘾者来说，洞察力并非如此。
enough to change people I worked with
足以改变我共事过的人
some folks who were very heavily
有些人非常重
therapized they had been through all
他们接受过治疗，经历过这一切
kinds of treatment individual therapy
治疗类型 个体治疗
rehab they knew about their family of
他们知道自己的家庭情况，正在接受康复治疗。
origin they understand about their own
他们了解自己的起源
intas psychic processes that lead them
引导他们的心理过程
towards relapse they're actually very
他们实际上非常容易复发。
self-aware from from a psychotherapeutic
自我意识来自心理治疗
perspective and they still use and I
视角，他们仍然在使用，而我
also worked with folks who were not so
也曾与一些不太……的人共事。
self-aware but we're like yeah I decided
虽然有自知之明，但我们还是会说：“是啊，我决定了。”
that alcohol kind of made me not feel so
酒精让我感觉没那么……
good so I decided I just shouldn't drink
很好，所以我决定干脆不喝酒了。
anymore and they those people got better
不再如此，那些人的情况有所好转。
and the Really self-aware insightful
以及真正具有自我意识和洞察力的人
guys often got lost in their own
男人们常常沉浸在自己的世界里。
machinations and they kept relapsing so
他们耍尽手段，结果却屡屡复发。
Insight is sometimes useful but it's
洞察力有时很有用，但它
certainly insufficient to actually
当然不足以真正
changing Behavior to actually change
改变行为才能真正改变
Behavior you have to do the thing like
你必须像那样行事
the only way to stop drinking is not to
戒酒的唯一方法就是不喝酒
put the booze in your mouth anymore the
别再把酒放进嘴里了。
only way to stop using pornography is to
戒除色情制品的唯一方法是
stop using pornography there's no other
停止使用色情制品，没有其他办法了。
way about that now when you stop a
现在，当你停下来的时候，大概就是这样。
behavior lots of things are going to
行为方面，很多事情都会发生
come up and so one thing that you can do
上来，所以你可以做的一件事
is plan ahead for those
提前做好计划
contingencies I used the term before one
我之前用过这个术语来描述各种突发情况。
of the most useful things with
最有用的东西
addictions of all kinds is to talk about
谈论各种成瘾问题
functional analysis what do
函数分析是什么
this process this Behavior this
这个过程，这种行为
substance what does it actually doing
物质究竟有什么作用？
what problem is it
是什么问题？
solving like I was uh I was addicted to
解决问题就像我上瘾了一样
cigarettes when I was younger and
我年轻的时候抽烟
nicotine is a really hard one to
尼古丁真的很难戒掉。
quit and I probably quit eight or nine
我辞职了，大概辞职了八九次。
times before I finally kicked it for for
在我最终把它踢出去之前，已经过了好几次了
good I hope right and one thing that
我希望一切都好，还有一件事……
helped me was to understand well when
对我有帮助的是很好地理解了何时
did I usually reach for the pack and
我通常会伸手去拿背包吗？
some of the biggest triggers for me was
对我来说，一些最大的触发因素是
when I was
当我
bored and I just needed a little bit of
无聊，我只需要一点点……
I don't know something to do some sort
我不知道该做些什么。
of stimul maybe I it made me it gave me
刺激或许让我产生了这种感觉，它给了我
the opportunity to go outside and take a
有机会到户外走走
break from what I was doing change a
暂时放下手头的事情，改变一下。
scenery okay or I needed some sort of
风景还可以吗？或者我需要某种东西？
reward I did something good I deserve a
我做了好事，我应该得到奖励。
cigarette here right now people need
现在这里有人需要香烟
ways to alleviate their boredom and they
他们寻找缓解无聊的方法，并且
need ways to reward their good behavior
需要一些方法来奖励他们的良好行为
they just need to find ways to do that
他们只需要找到实现这一目标的方法。
that doesn't sabotage their growth and
但这并不会阻碍他们的成长，而且
create more problems in the long term
从长远来看，这会造成更多问题。
than they solve which is what cigarettes
然后他们解决了香烟的问题。
I think do for people including myself
我认为这样做对包括我自己在内的所有人都有益。
and once I understood that I was
一旦我明白了这一点，我
basically reaching towards the pack when
基本上是向群体伸出手
I was bored or I needed a reward I found
我当时很无聊，或者我需要一些奖励，于是我找到了
other ways that authentically alleviated
其他真正缓解的方法
boredom or were rewarding that didn't
无聊或者有回报，但并非如此
create more problems than they solved
它们制造的问题比解决的问题还多。
now that wasn't easy but that helped
那并不容易，但确实有所帮助。
because in the absence of those things I
因为如果没有那些东西，我
would feel bored and I just have to sit
我会觉得无聊，只能坐着。
with it or I'd feel reward I'd feel
有了它，我就会感到满足，我会感到
proud and I wouldn't be able to reward
骄傲，我无法给予奖励
myself in any kind of a way which
我自己以任何方式
generally led to relapse
通常会导致复发
so you have to understand why men might
所以你必须理解为什么男人可能会
be using pornography and often it's
经常使用色情内容
loneliness it's
孤独，就是
boredom so are you saying the antidote
无聊，所以你的意思是解药
would be the antithesis I it would be
将是它的反义词。
connection and something to do
联系和一些事情做
absolutely
绝对地
yeah go get a job go get some friends
是啊，去找份工作，交些朋友吧。
and you got to stop um you got to stop
你必须停下来，你必须停下来
at first and sometimes it's just about
起初是这样，有时也只是这样。
getting through the next 24 hours don't
熬过接下来的24小时并不会……
think about you're never gonna watch
想想你永远不会看
another movie again just make the
又拍了一部电影。
decision not to use today no matter how
无论如何，今天决定不使用
bad it gets you're just not going to use
情况糟糕到你根本不会用了。
today and if you still want to use
今天，如果你仍然想使用
tomorrow you can use tomorrow do you
明天你可以用明天的时间，对吗？
think pornography is a net negative for
认为色情制品总体上是负面的
society probably yeah I mean pornography
社会大概是吧，我是指色情作品
has always existed there's like drawings
一直都存在，就像图画一样。
on Cave walls of women with with big
洞穴墙壁上描绘着身材高大的女性形象
boobs right
右侧乳房
so we've seen that in cultural artifacts
所以我们在文化制品中已经看到了这一点。
from all kinds of civilizations
来自各种文明
throughout time and place what makes
无论在何时何地，是什么造就了……
pornography really dangerous today is
如今色情制品真的很危险。
just the scale on which it's being able
只是它能够达到的规模而已。
it's distributed it's free and it's
它是分布式的，它是免费的，而且它是
readily available at any moment as long
只要随时可用
as you have a internet connection it's
只要你有网络连接，它就是
crazy I was I was saying to a friend the
我当时疯了，我对朋友说……
other day I was like you just go on
前几天我就跟你说，你就继续吧
Twitter and I saw Cara swier who is the
我在推特上看到了卡拉·斯维尔，她是……
journalist podcaster in America I saw
我看到美国一位记者兼播客主持人
her do a tweet the other day she's
她前几天发了一条推特。
saying I'm leaving Twitter I've been
我说我要离开推特了，我一直
here since 2007 I believe she said she
我相信她说她从2007年就住在这里了
because I'm leaving it because it's
因为我要离开，因为……
become like a porn hellscape porn really
变得像色情地狱一样，真的色情
on Twitter oh my God yeah you could
在推特上，哦我的天哪，是的，你可以
scroll down Twitter feed you will e
向下滚动 Twitter 信息流，你会看到
regardless of who you follow because
无论你关注谁，因为
they I think what's happened since um
我认为自从……以来发生的事情
the buyout is they've tried to make it
他们试图促成收购。
more addictive which means you're
更容易上瘾，这意味着你
getting more viral content into your
在你的博客中增加更多病毒式传播的内容
feed and more content that's has a high
信息流和更多高价值内容
dwell time are the amount of time you
停留时间是指您……的时间量
spend looking at it so that stuff's
花时间仔细查看，这样那些东西就……
coming into your feed more regardless of
无论如何，更多内容会出现在你的信息流中
whether you follow those accounts or not
无论你是否关注这些账号
and there'll be a lot more graphic
而且会有更多图像。
imagery um like that in your feeds these
就像你信息流里的那些图片
days and I was explaining this to my
几天后，我一直在向我的
friend so I said what look at my Twitter
朋友，所以我说看看我的推特
feed I scroll down I scroll down I
我向下滚动 我向下滚动
scroll down I scroll down and you you go
向下滚动，我向下滚动，你也向下滚动。
down tempos and it's a famous story that
慢节奏，这是一个著名的故事
actually just broke in the UK it's a
实际上它刚刚在英国崩溃了。
female prison guard having sex with a
女狱警与一名男子发生性关系
inmate and it happened in one of our
一名囚犯，这件事发生在我们其中一所监狱。
prison UK prisons and and that's in the
英国监狱，而且那是在……
middle of my feed it's a 4-minute video
我的推送中间有一个4分钟的视频。
of this sexual act you know this and you
你知道这种性行为，而且你
go like if I was susceptible to and all
就好像我很容易受到伤害一样
men are susceptible to I am a
男性容易受到“我是……”的影响
susceptible to addiction but if I was if
我容易上瘾，但如果我是……
I was someone that had just got away
我曾是一个侥幸逃脱的人
from my porn addiction seeing that
从我的色情成瘾来看
you know well it's the same thing with
你知道，这和……是一样的。
alcohol it's like it's everywhere at
酒精似乎无处不在。
least everywhere in America and a lot of
至少在美国各地都是如此，而且很多地方
Alcoholics on some level correctly
在某种程度上，酗酒者正确地
despair it's like I have to choose
绝望，就像我必须做出选择一样。
between my social life and my addiction
在我的社交生活和我的毒瘾之间
yeah so true and it can be very
是的，确实如此，而且这可能非常
difficult to start to live a sober
开始过清醒的生活很难
lifestyle it's almost socially
生活方式几乎就是社交
unacceptable not to drink isn't it in
不喝酒是不可接受的，不是吗？
some context I it just makes other
一些背景信息，它只是使其他
people uncomfortable because it calls
人们感到不舒服，因为它呼唤
their own use of that substance into
他们自己使用该物质
question I think people who are really
我认为这个问题是那些真正……的人提出的。
intentional and cognizant of their use
有意且意识到其用途
it doesn't make them uncomfortable when
这不会让他们感到不舒服
somebody doesn't drink what would you
有人不喝酒，你会怎么办？
say then so if if if you were to give
那么，如果你要给的话……
very Topline advice to both a man in
给男人的最重要的建议
that that's 35 years old and struggling
那人已经35岁了，还在苦苦挣扎。
to get into a relationship and a woman
进入一段恋爱关系和一个女人
that's 35 and struggling to get into a
他35岁了，还在努力找工作。
relationship if you could only speak to
如果你只能和某人交谈，你们的关系会是怎样的呢？
them for just 30 seconds to give them
只需给他们30秒钟，就能让他们……
advice what would you say to each
你会对每个人说些什么？
wow and you got to be honest here and
哇，你得实话实说。
unpolitically correct because I know cuz
我知道这不符合政治正确，因为
I think the thing you'd probably say if
我想你可能会说的话是……
the cameras weren't pointing at you is
摄像头没对着你
probably the most important thing no I
或许最重要的事，不，我
just need more information it's like why
我需要更多信息，比如为什么。
is that 35-year-old struggling is he
那个35岁的苦苦挣扎的人是吗？
because he's just socially awkward and
因为他只是社交能力比较差。
he he he has his less the rest of his
呵呵，他剩下的部分就少了。
life kind of on track like he's a decent
生活基本步入正轨，他是个不错的人。
dude he's got a decent paying job and
老兄，他有一份收入不错的工作，
him him I think the the advice I would
我认为我会给他的建议是……
give to him is to sort of date like it's
给他的就是像约会一样。
your
你的
job now lots of people think that they
现在很多人都认为他们有工作
just want a
只想要一个
loving secure
爱与安全
and peaceful relationship and they just
他们关系和平，他们只是
want those three things but that's
我想要那三样东西，但仅此而已。
actually an enormous ask that's like
实际上，这是一个非常大的要求，就像……
wanting a job that's high paying low
想要一份高薪低收入的工作
stress and you're passionate about it's
压力很大，而且你对它充满热情
very difficult to get all three of just
很难同时得到这三样东西。
those things right most people that you
那些事情对大多数人来说都是如此。
know do not have all three of those
我知道自己并不拥有这三样东西。
things at their work most relationships
他们工作中最重要的人际关系
are not those three things if you want
如果你想要的不是这三件事，那就不是这三件事。
one of those jobs they're out there but
这是市面上众多工作机会之一，但
they're kind of the needle in the hay
他们就像大海捞针一样。
stack it is a numbers game especially as
堆叠游戏本质上是一个数字游戏，尤其当
a man as a male in general you
作为一个男人，你
disseminate lots of pollen lots of seed
散播大量花粉和种子
because most of them are going to lead
因为他们中的大多数将会领导
nowhere they're going to be evolutionary
它们无处可去，进化也无从谈起。
or relationship dead ends and so if you
或者关系走到了尽头，所以如果你
really want a job and you're serious
你真心想要这份工作，而且是认真的。
about it you need to make getting a job
关于这一点，你需要努力找工作。
your job and you need to send out you
你的工作需要你派人出去。
can't just say I tried once or twice and
不能只说我尝试过一两次，
it didn't work out man it's like you
事情没成，兄弟，就像你一样。
might have to send out
可能需要寄出去
200 resumés you might have to take some
你可能要投递200份简历。
coaching classes to learn how to
参加辅导课程学习如何
interview better you might have to do
面试表现更好，你可能需要这样做
some research into the company and the
对该公司进行了一些调查
kinds of questions they ask and to learn
他们提出的问题类型以及学习
about their culture so you can
了解他们的文化，这样你就可以
demonstrate goodness of fit like make
证明其适用性良好，例如
getting a job your job and then
找到一份工作，然后
reproduce at scale don't just think it's
大规模复制，不要仅仅认为它……
going to take care of
去处理
itself or that you're a victim of
本身，或者你是受害者
circumstance I don't think most guys
这种情况，我觉得大多数男人都不会这样。
think it's going to take care of itself
我觉得它会自行解决。
I think most the Trap that trap is
我认为大多数陷阱都是……
something that women can fall in
女性可能会陷入的境地
it's like they want the meat cute and
他们好像想要把肉做得可爱又……
it's going to happen when it's going to
该发生的时候自然会发生。
happen and you know if it's meant to be
事情发生了，你知道这是否是命中注定。
then it's meant to be and if he didn't
那就是命中注定，如果他没有
if he didn't try enough and he left then
如果他没有尽力就离开了
I guess that wasn't the one anyway like
我猜那肯定不是我要找的那一个。
well what were you doing were you
你当时在干什么？
providing value were you doing anything
你是否在提供价值？你做了什么？
to keep him in that relationship it's
为了让他继续维持这段关系……
that's that's something that a lot of
那是很多人……
women fall prey to in my opinion most
在我看来，女性最容易成为大多数犯罪的受害者。
guys especially by the time they're 35
尤其是到了35岁左右的男性。
like all lands in your lap as a
就像什么好事都没发生一样，落到你头上。
35-year old man you know haven't you
你认识那个35岁的男人，对吧？
learned that by now like if you want
现在我已经明白了，如果你想的话。
anything in life you kind of have to go
生活中任何事你都必须去做。
out and get it make it happen so
出去把它弄到手，让它发生。
assuming that women are going to be any
假设女性会成为任何
different would be absurd and you have
不同的说法是荒谬的，而且你拥有
to get over that rejection you have to
要克服被拒绝的痛苦，你必须
get over the pain treat it like a
克服痛苦，把它当作……
scientist
科学家
do do the AB testing and put yourself
做AB测试，把自己放进去。
out there at a mass scale which is
大规模地存在于外界，这便是
uncomfortable and expensive proposition
令人不适且代价高昂的提议
but hopefully in three or four months
但希望三四个月后就能实现。
you can accomplish what you would
你可以实现你想要的一切
otherwise spread out over three or four
否则会分散到三到四个地方
years and you can move on with the
几年后，你就可以继续前进了。
business of whatever you want that
你想做什么生意都行。
relationship to actually do you want to
与你实际想要的关系
diminish the actual time you spent you
减少你实际花费的时间
spend in the sexual Marketplace because
在性交易市场消费
the longer you spend as a guy the more
你作为男性的时间越长，就越……
rejection you're going to feel and the
你会感受到拒绝，以及
more inertia will set
更大的惯性将使
in it feels like we're going through a
感觉就像我们正在经历一场
interesting transitional moment in the
这是一个有趣的过渡时刻
world of dating and relationships sure
约会和恋爱的世界
you talk about that a lot the sort of
你经常谈到那种……
the transition period we're going
我们即将进入过渡期
through with things like obviously birth
完成诸如分娩之类的事情，这显然是件大事。
control but more recently things like
控制，但最近诸如
artificial intelligence which are really
人工智能，它们确实
going to put a spanner in the proverbial
准备给这句谚语添堵
works of dating and relationships well
约会和恋爱关系方面的作品
yeah it's the same trap as porn for men
是的，这和男性色情片的陷阱是一样的。
like with the Advent of virtual reality
就像虚拟现实的出现一样
Robotics and artificial intelligence
机器人和人工智能
like if it's hard for men to tell the
比如，如果男人很难分辨……
difference on some level between an
在某种程度上，两者之间存在差异
actual sexual encounter in pornography
色情作品中的真实性行为
now now can you imagine where it's going
现在，你能想象它要去哪里吗？
to be in like five years gosh and it's
五年后就到了，天哪，而且是
going to be a a significant trap imagine
这将是一个巨大的陷阱，想象一下
20 is I mean we'll be in a Blade Runner
20 的意思是，我们会置身于《银翼杀手》的世界。
situation where you have holographic
这种情况，你拥有全息投影
girlfriends who tell you exactly what
会告诉你一切的女朋友
you want toar here and you can change
你想在这里翻页，你可以更改
their appearance at will I mean I don't
他们的出现随心所欲，我的意思是，我不这么认为。
know but like that's not too far-fetched
我知道，但这并非完全牵强。
doesn't sound like the worst thing I
听起来好像不是最糟糕的事
mean because people are
意思是，因为人们是
unsatisfying like people are
令人不满，就像人们一样
disappointing people are real
令人失望的人是真实存在的
and that can be tough like all
这可能像所有事情一样艰难。
relationships require some degree of
人际关系需要一定程度的
settling to some to some extent that's
在某种程度上，这算是解决了。
not very sexy that's not very satisfying
不太性感，也不太令人满意。
and I think that when we're when we're a
我认为，当我们……
wash and optionality or at least a
洗涤和可选性，或者至少是
parent optionality it becomes harder and
父母的选择权变得更加困难，而且
harder to settle for something that is
更难接受这样的东西
less than perfect that's something I
不够完美，这是我的一点。
talk about a lot also it's
谈论很多事情也是
like the meat market the dating scene
就像肉市和约会场景一样
has changed so much like it used to be
变化太大了，跟以前很像了。
that you as a guy could do fairly well
作为男生，你完全可以做得相当不错。
if you were the biggest fish in a
如果你是一条最大的鱼
relatively small pond right there are no
那里有个相对较小的池塘，没有
ponds anymore dude we're all swimming in
伙计，现在都不是池塘了，我们都在里面游泳。
one gigantic
一个巨大的
ocean the fact of the matter is is that
事实是，海洋……
guy is competing for the girl next door
男生正在和邻家女孩竞争
with every other man on the
和其他所有男人一样
planet and every woman is competing for
星球，每个女人都在竞争
the most eligible bachelor in their
他们中最理想的单身汉
little Community with against every
小社区反对一切
other woman on the
另一个女人
planet it's so easy for people to
地球对人们来说是如此容易
connect with each other through social
通过社交媒体相互联系
media and that's why on some level the
媒体，所以在某种程度上……
best dating in the world is not a dating
世界上最好的约会并非约会
app it's
它是应用程序
Instagram are you hopeful sure the game
Instagram 你对游戏抱有希望吗？
will go on people will find a way to
还会继续，人们总会找到办法的。
make it work there's always opportunity
抓住机会，总有机会。
maybe you know this but there were more
或许你已经知道了，但还有更多。
new millionaires created in 1929 in the
1929年诞生的新百万富翁
stock market crash than in any other
股市崩盘比任何其他时期都更加严重
moment in American history like there is
美国历史上的这一刻，就像……
a way to thrive and succeed in almost
几乎在所有领域都能蓬勃发展并取得成功的方法
any game and under almost any
任何游戏，几乎在任何
circumstances but you have to be
有些情况，但你必须……
flexible and you have to be able to spot
灵活，而且你必须能够发现问题。
the opportunity which often means that
这个机会通常意味着
you have to buy when other people are
当其他人都在购物时，你却不得不买。
selling which is very difficult to
销售非常困难
do in general just in terms of like
一般来说，就类似的事情而言
Modern Survival the individual should be
现代生存，个人应该……
very cautious about moving in the
搬家方面非常谨慎。
direction of the
方向
majority like most people's lives are
大多数人的生活就像大多数人的生活一样。
not awesome so why move in the direction
这并不理想，所以为什么要朝着这个方向发展呢？
that most people are moving if anything
大多数人都在搬家，如果说有什么变化的话。
that could be a reliable indicator that
这可能是一个可靠的指标，表明
they're might be something of interest
它们或许会很有趣。
in a different direction as an
朝着不同的方向发展
entrepreneur I'm always looking for ways
作为一名企业家，我一直在寻找各种方法
to connect and to create and that's why
连接与创造，这就是原因
I decided to launch the conversation
我决定发起这场对话。
cards I turned to Shopify who also
我转向了 Shopify，他们也提供卡片服务。
sponsored this podcast and Shopify made
赞助了本播客，Shopify 也参与其中。
it so easy to set up an online store and
建立网上商店非常容易，
reach all of you no matter where you are
无论你们身在何处，都能联系到你们。
in the world I remember the challenges
在世界上，我记得那些挑战
we faced when we first launched the D
我们在首次推出D时就面临着这个问题。
conversation cards managing inventory
对话卡片管理库存
ensuring a seamless checkout process and
确保结账流程顺畅无阻
reaching our audience Shopify step did
触达我们的受众 Shopify 步骤完成
and made everything so straightforward
把一切都安排得如此简单明了
and efficient it was like having an
效率很高，就像拥有一个
entire team of experts by our side
我们整个专家团队都在我们身边。
allowing us to focus on creating content
让我们能够专注于内容创作
and connecting with you what I love
和你分享我所爱的一切
about Shopify is no matter how big you
关于 Shopify，无论你规模有多大
intend to grow your business they give
他们打算发展你的业务
you everything you need to take control
你将拥有掌控一切所需的一切。
and take your business to the next level
并将您的业务提升到一个新的水平。
and to say thank you for listening to
并感谢大家的聆听。
this podcast we're giving you a trial
本播客我们提供免费试用。
which is just $1 a month and you can
每月只需​​ 1 美元，你就可以
sign up by going to shopify.com Bartlet
请访问 shopify.com 注册 Bartlet
the link is in the description below
链接在下方描述中。
when you're trying to build something
当你试图构建某物时
the problem that we all face is we need
我们共同面临的问题是我们需要
talent and skills that we don't have
我们所缺乏的才能和技能
ourselves and we can waste so much time
我们自己，我们可能会浪费很多时间
trying to learn a new skill when really
试图学习一项新技能，而实际上
what we should be doing is using a
我们应该做的是使用
platform like fiverr.com where you have
像 fiverr.com 这样的平台，你可以在那里……
Global access to reviewed tried and
全球获取经过审查和尝试的信息
tested worldclass Talent at your
经过考验的世界一流人才随时为您服务
fingertips that you can access in a
您可以通过指尖轻松访问
flexible and affordable way fiver for me
对我来说，Fiverr 是一种灵活且经济实惠的方式。
when I was starting out in business was
我刚开始创业的时候是
a real unlock it was a bit of a hack
这真是一次彻底的解锁，有点像黑客攻击。
because I used to think that the only
因为我以前认为只有
way for me to add skills to my project
这是我为项目增添技能的一种方式
was by hiring full-time staff and
是通过雇用全职员工来实现的，
bringing them into the office fiver.com
把它们带到办公室 fiver.com
changes that and if you're in that
情况就不同了，如果你身处其中的话。
position now where there's a skill
现在这个职位需要一项技能
you're missing for a project that
你缺席了一个项目。
matters to you here's what you have to
如果你关心这些，以下是你必须做的：
do visit fiverr.com diary to learn more
请访问 fiverr.com 日记了解更多信息。
and here's the great thing if it doesn't
如果它不这样做，那太好了
go well Fiverr offer a pretty amazing
Fiverr 提供的服务非常棒
money back guarantee so what are you
退款保证，所以你到底在说什么？
waiting for you know I'm thinking a lot
等你，你知道我一直在想很多事。
about the um the video I saw on your
关于我之前在你网站上看到的那个视频。
YouTube channel called how to be a man
YouTube频道名为“如何成为男人”
yeah that's one of the more popular ones
是的，这是比较受欢迎的一个。
H it's interesting because a lot of
这很有趣，因为很多
women come up to me um that have young
有些年轻女性走过来跟我说话。
that are raising young men and they
他们正在培养年轻男性，而且他们
they'll ask me about this particular
他们会问我关于这个方面的问题。
subject they'll say because there's so
他们会说，这个话题是因为有很多……
many different performative influencers
许多不同的表演型网红
out there that are doing this sort of
那些做这种事情的人
performative masculinity what should I
表演性男子气概我应该怎么做
say to my son makes a good man in in
告诉我的儿子，做一个好男人需要付出怎样的努力
2024 because a lot of the things that
2024年，因为很多事情
sort of some narratives are suggesting
有些叙述似乎暗示着
make a good man are quite feminine
优秀的男人往往很有女性气质。
traits typically
特征通常
but those aren't necessarily always Co
但这些不一定总是合作
um conducive with being attractive so if
嗯，有利于吸引人，所以如果
I was to throw this to you and say how
我本该把这个扔给你，然后告诉你……
do I be a man what would your answer be
如果我是个男人，你的答案会是什么？
I think there's lots of ways that you
我认为有很多方法可以……
can be a man right and I don't think we
可以是个男人，对吧？我不认为我们
should be bogged down in those
应该深陷其中
performative aspects of masculinity okay
男性气质的表演性方面是可以接受的。
but the way I talk about it in the video
但我视频里谈论这件事的方式……
is the way to be a man fundamentally is
做男人的根本之道是
to have a spine and a pair of
有脊椎和一对
balls and both Things Are important and
球和两者都很重要
if you have those two things then in my
如果你拥有这两样东西，那么在我的
opinion you're a man no matter what you
不管怎样，你都是个男人。
look like or how you act and I think
你的外表或行为举止，以及我认为
that kind of cuts to the heart of what
那直接触及了问题的核心。
has even historically been the core of
从历史上看，它甚至一直是核心
masculinity one of them is having a
男性气质之一是拥有
spine which is the willingness to stand
脊梁，即站立的意愿
up like a spine is what actually allows
像脊柱一样挺立才是真正允许的。
you to stand erect and a man generally
你要站直，一个男人通常
needs to have something that he stands
他需要有某种立场。
for because life is very very difficult
因为生活非常非常艰难
in particular the moment you stand up
尤其是你站起来的那一刻
you cast a shadow which is a symbolic
你投下的影子具有象征意义。
way of saying as soon as you stand for
意思是，一旦你站起来
something you will attract resistance to
你这样做会招致阻力。
that something no matter what it is you
不管那是什么，你
stand for there is no there's nothing
表示“没有”，意思是“什么都没有”。
that is so unambiguously right and good
这绝对是正确且合理的。
that it does not cast a shadow except
它除了……之外，不会投下阴影。
pure light let's put it that way only
纯粹的光，就这么说吧。
light does not cast a shadow right and
光线不会投射阴影，对吧？
we are not pure beings of light right so
我们并非纯粹的光明存在，对吧？
we need to be able to stand up and to
我们需要能够站起来，并且
rise above the field of
升起于田野之上
undifferentiated humanity
未分化的人类
because there's things that need to be
因为有些事情是必须做的
done there's loads that need to be
完成，还有很多事情需要做
lifted there are fires that need to be
解除封锁后，还有一些火灾需要扑灭。
put out and the spine is what is also
展开后，脊柱也是……
the conduit of the nerves that allow
允许神经通过的通道
Locomotion allows movement through
运动能力允许通过
reality movement through the world and
现实世界在世界上的运动和
that's generally what's necessary there
通常情况下，那里就需要这样做。
are so many problems like sometimes guys
有时候问题太多了，比如男生
come to me and like well what should I
来找我，问问我该怎么办
do with my life just like look
我的人生就这么他妈的算了
around Man start with what is very
围绕着人类，从非常
obviously a problem in your life fix
显然，你生活中遇到了一个问题，需要解决。
that and once you fix that
一旦你解决了这个问题
then you can begin to broaden your scope
然后你就可以开始扩大你的范围了。
with respect to the problems you tend to
就你倾向于遇到的问题而言
identify don't try to solve humanties
识别问题，不要试图解决人性问题
problems right now when your life is not
现在的问题在于，你的生活并非如此。
in the state where it needs to be like
在它需要成为的那种状态下
focus on yourself first put your own
首先关注自己，把自己的事情放在首位。
mask on before you assist others on the
在帮助他人之前，请先戴好口罩。
airplane and then once you get things in
飞机，然后等你把东西都搬进去之后……
order and things are generally working
秩序井然，一切运转正常。
you can begin to broaden your scope and
你可以开始拓宽视野，
that's really important because
这真的很重要，因为
one person who does that can benefit
这样做的人可以受益
well now they can benefit millions of
现在他们可以从中受益数百万人。
people through the internet and social
人们通过互联网和社交媒体
media it's incredible it's an
媒体真是太不可思议了，这是一个
opportunity that has never existed on
前所未有的机会
the face of this planet and they can do
地球的面貌，他们能做到
it from the privacy of their own living
从他们自己生活的私密空间里获取信息
rooms it's
房间是
amazing so that's important but you also
太棒了，这很重要，但你也
need a pair which is to be able to have
需要一双能够拥有
the willingness
意愿
to deal with the consequences of
应对其后果
standing up and casting a shadow if you
站起来并投下影子，如果你
stand up and the moment you meet with
站起来，在你与……见面的那一刻
any kind of resistance or push back or
任何形式的抵抗或反抗
antagonism or criticism which you
你表现出的敌意或批评
absolutely will
绝对会
receive there was you shouldn't have
收到时你不应该有
stood up to begin with like that's just
一开始就站起来，就像那样
going to hurt it's going to teach you
会很痛苦，但会教会你很多。
the lesson that it's better not to stand
这个教训告诉我们，最好不要站着。
up it's better just to kind of blend in
最好还是尽量融入人群。
it's better to push all that stuff down
最好把那些东西都压下去。
because looks what happens when you try
因为看看你尝试之后会发生什么。
well yeah well you need to have
嗯，是的，你需要有
some push back to be able to deal with
一些阻力需要应对
whatever comes your way as a consequence
无论由此产生什么后果，你都会面临。
of standing up anybody who stands up
任何站起来的人都会受到谴责
will cast a shadow and part of that
会投下阴影，而那一部分
Shadow is the projected Envy of others
阴影是他人嫉妒的投射。
who for whatever reason as yet lack the
由于某种原因，他们目前还缺乏
courage to stand up themselves it's so
他们有勇气站出来，这真是太难得了。
much easier to attack those for standing
攻击那些站着的人要容易得多。
up than it is to stand up and run the
比站起来跑步要容易得多
risk of those attacks
这些攻击的风险
yourself right and especially with the
你自己是对的，尤其是对
Internet it's so much easier to do that
互联网让这一切变得容易得多。
these days you can hide your face your
如今你可以隐藏你的脸
name and and just take pot shots at
命名并随意攻击
anyone and anyone um everyone and
任何人，嗯，每个人，
anyone ously is part of the reason men
任何人都是男人存在的原因之一。
end up having these sort of midlife
最终会经历这种中年危机
crises that we've talked about because
我们讨论过的危机是因为
they stop standing up and they stop
他们停止站立，然后停了下来
having Ables because I've heard you talk
我有能力，因为我听你说过。
about
关于
selfishness and that men aren't selfish
自私和男人不自私
enough I think selfishness is a good
我认为自私是件好事
thing to be especially in relationships
在人际关系中，这一点尤为重要
at my stage of life I think that 90% of
在我这个人生阶段，我认为90%的人
successful relationships is selection
成功的人际关系是一种选择。
I'm not a big fan of compromise to my
我不太喜欢妥协。
mind compromise is two people not
妥协是指两个人之间的沟通不畅。
getting what they want I think it's
我认为他们如愿以偿了。
better to be
最好是
pretty selfish and explicit about your
你相当自私，而且毫不掩饰自己的私心。
selfishness and to find someone who
自私，以及找到一个
doesn't mind it who can work with that
不介意的人可以和他一起工作。
or even enjoys it and thrives in those
甚至乐在其中，并在其中如鱼得水。
conditions but there's always going to
条件是，但总会有……
be compromise
妥协
now something you you'd rather I'd be
现在，你宁愿我成为那样的人
I'd be cautious around compromise
我会谨慎对待妥协。
because generally it does create this
因为通常情况下，它确实会造成这种情况。
sense of obligation and debt like I'm
感觉自己像个负有责任的人，好像欠了债似的。
going to give up something that I want
我要放弃我想要的东西
to make you happy and so I'm going to
为了让你开心，所以我打算
you to sacrifice your happiness at some
你为了某些事情牺牲了自己的幸福。
future date because of something I want
因为我想要的东西，所以要定在某个未来的日子。
to do but if you're not unwilling to
要这样做，但如果你不不愿意的话
compromise in terms of what you're
在你所做的事情上做出妥协
looking for um you're probably going to
正在寻找……嗯，你可能要去……
be looking forever no well there's other
永远寻找，没有，还有其他的
things that you can do you can clarify
你可以做的事情，你可以澄清
your selection criteria okay and
您的选择标准可以。
generally the fewer criteria you have
一般来说，标准越少越好。
the more successful you will be like
你越成功，你就会越像
only go into the sexual Marketplace
只进入性交易市场
wanting just a few things okay so no
只想要几样东西，好吧，没问题。
like I'm not dating him he's got a
好像我没跟他约会似的，他有……
velcro wallet oh like the yeah I mean
魔术贴钱包，哦，就像那个，我是说……
it's like some women will disqualify
就好像有些女性会被取消资格一样。
really decent male partners for a trifle
非常不错的男性伴侣，仅此而已
and they often do that when they're
他们经常这样做，当他们……
young and a wash an optionality because
年轻，而且洗涤是一种选择，因为
why not what's your selection
为什么不呢？你的选择是什么？
criteria okay so I used to have much
好的，我以前有很多标准。
higher selection criteria same and one
更高的选择标准相同且一
of the mindsets that it's going to sound
听起来会是这样的心态
weird but one of the mindsets that I've
这很奇怪，但却是我的一种思维方式。
worked against and has led to a lot more
适得其反，反而导致了更多问题。
satisfying relationships is that I have
令人满意的关系就是我拥有的。
tried not to go to the sexual
尽量避免发生性行为
Marketplace looking for my equal or
市场正在寻找与我地位相当或
someone who can meet me at my
能来我家和我见面的人
level in the past I would go there and I
过去我曾去过那里，而且
would like I want to talk about quantum
我想谈谈量子力学。
mechanics and Shakespeare and literature
力学、莎士比亚和文学
and go Wilderness backpacking and I also
然后去野外背包旅行，我也是
do these mindfulness Retreats and I'm
参加这些正念静修营，我
interested in Enlightenment and
对启蒙运动感兴趣
spiritual discipline and I want a woman
灵修，我想要一个女人
who's interested in all of those things
谁会对所有这些都感兴趣
and and I also want to be attracted to
而且我也想被……吸引
her too so it's like
她也是，所以就像
and is expensive every time you say and
而且每次你​​说“和”都很贵
probabilistically you're less likely to
从概率上讲，你不太可能
get what you want which redounds to
得到你想要的，这最终会导致
actual expenses in terms of time money
实际支出（以时间或金钱衡量）
opportunity in the sexual Marketplace so
性市场中的机会
you should be very cautious about what
你应该非常谨慎地对待……
you say and
你说，
to and I remember I was having some
我记得我当时正在吃一些
trouble meeting women that met all of my
很难遇到符合我所有要求的女性
extrapolated criteria and I still had
推断标准，我仍然有
I'm sure plenty of unconscious criteria
我相信有很多无意识的标准。
that I was exacting on them as well um
我对他们的要求也很严格。
and I brought this to a mentor and he
我把这件事告诉了我的导师，他
listened patiently to me and he
他耐心地听我说话，他
basically when I was done said Orion why
基本上，当我讲完之后，我说的是猎户座为什么
the would you want to talk to a
你他妈的想跟谁说话？
woman about quantum mechanics like you
像你这样懂量子力学的女人
do not need a woman to do that like if
不需要女人来做这件事，就像……
you really want to do that that's
你真的想那样做吗？
something that's really important to you
对你来说真正重要的东西
I guess that's your right but you just
我想那是你的权利，但你只是
need someone who's interested in quantum
我们需要一位对量子力学感兴趣的人。
mechanics to do that with that could be
用这种方法实现这一点的机制可能是
a man it doesn't have to be a woman and
可以是男人，不一定是女人。
I was like oh that's that's right and so
我当时就想，哦，对，就是这样。
what I did is I I looked at all the
我所做的就是，我查看了所有……
things that I was going to the sexual
我当时正要去性方面的事情
Marketplace to find and I thought could
市场里可以找到，我想可以
I get this need met
我的需求得到了满足。
in other kind of relationship with other
与其他人的另一种关系
person on the planet besides a woman in
除了女人之外，地球上还有谁？
a sexual relationship and the vast
性关系和广阔
majority of those things I could say yes
大多数事情我都可以回答“是”。
to and so I made a commitment to get
所以，我下定决心要得到
those needs met elsewhere because it's
这些需求在其他地方得到了满足，因为
as a man it's generally easier and
作为男人，这通常更容易一些。
cheaper to get those needs met elsewhere
在其他地方满足这些需求会更便宜。
than in sexual relationships with women
比与女性发生性关系更甚
and that was also great because it also
那也很棒，因为它也
forced me to cultivate and maintain my
迫使我培养和保持我的
nonsexual relationships both with men
与男性的非性关系
and women right which put less pressure
女性权利会带来较小的压力
on my female partner to be everything
我的女性伴侣需要成为一切
and anything to me so you know what was
对我来说，任何事都一样，所以你知道那是什么。
left was all of the things that either
剩下的就是所有那些东西了。
either wouldn't or couldn't get met in
要么不愿要么不能在……
any other kind of relationship which
任何其他类型的关系
first and foremost was sex MH it's just
首先，最重要的是性，仅此而已。
how it is a straight guy it's what it
他就是个直男，就是这样。
that's what I go for in a sexual
这就是我在性方面所追求的。
relationship the second criteria is that
第二个标准是：
she needed to be sufficiently attractive
她需要足够有吸引力。
to me in the sense that I knew
对我而言，就我所知而言，我知道
that if I were to walk into most rooms
如果我走进大多数房间……
and want secretly to be with that guy's
并且暗地里想和那个男人在一起
girl that it wasn't going to work with
那个女孩觉得这行不通
the woman that I was with MH that's not
和我在一起的那个女人，MH，不是
very virtuous to admit but it's probably
承认这一点固然很好，但可能
better for me to acknowledge that and
我最好承认这一点。
work with that than to pretend that that
与其假装那样，不如接受那样。
doesn't exist because it's probably not
不存在，因为它可能根本不存在。
going to go away so she needed there
她要离开，所以她需要待在那里。
needed to be lots of sex she needed to
她需要很多性生活
be sufficiently attractive to me and I
对我来说足够有吸引力，而且
like that let's say soft femininity that
比如说，那种柔美的女性气质。
comes out of women in the context of a
在女性的语境下，
close intimate relationship that you
你与他人之间亲密的关系
can't get from a platonic or
无法从柏拉图式的关系中获得
professional female friend or colleague
专业女性朋友或同事
so those are the three things that I I
所以，这就是我要说的三件事。
went looking for um with the fourth
和第四个人一起去找他
criteria that she couldn't
她无法达到的标准
be so disagreeable that it was going to
令人非常不愉快，以至于
create more problems than are solved by
制造的问题比解决的问题更多
the three criteria being met and this
三个条件都已满足，并且
was great because I knew what I was
这很棒，因为我知道自己是什么。
going to a relationship for I wasn't
我当时并没有打算谈恋爱。
bringing a lot of need or expectation it
它带来了很多需求或期望。
was harder for me to be disappointed by
对我来说，很难感到失望。
women and it also allowed me to
女性，而且它也让我能够
entertain the possibility of satisfying
考虑满足的可能性
relationship with lots of different
与许多不同事物的关系
kinds of women like outside of those
像那些之外的女性类型
criteria she could be anyone from any
她符合的条件可以是任何人。
kind of Walk of Life and um that's great
有点像人生旅程，嗯，那很棒。
because you kind of want to have your
因为你多少想要拥有你的
applicant pool as as wide as possible in
尽可能扩大申请人范围
the initial phases of a selection
选择的初始阶段
process yeah I I can I can relate in
是的，我能理解。
many ways I um I think my earlier years
很多方面我嗯我认为我早年
I thought I wanted to date another
我以为我想和另一个人约会。
entrepreneur but I think that would have
企业家，但我认为那会……
absolutely been absolutely hell when I
当我……的时候，那简直是人间地狱。
say entrepreneur someone that was like
比如说，企业家，像……
just obsessed with their career but then
他们当时只是痴迷于自己的事业，但后来
where does that leave space for a
这样一来，哪里还有空间留给……
relationship and also I I thought I
关系，而且，我认为我
wanted to date someone that believed the
想和相信……的人约会
things I believed I'm quite logical I
我以前相信的事情，我相当理性。
need evidence to believe the things I
我需要证据才能相信我所做的事情。
believed turns out I found the opposite
我原以为如此，结果却发现恰恰相反。
and it's the best thing ever because
这是有史以来最好的事情，因为
she basically is everything I'm not and
她基本上拥有我所不具备的一切特质，
I find that really curious so she's very
我觉得这真的很奇怪，所以她非常
spiritual she takes life at a certain
她以某种精神方式看待生活。
Pace she's very in tune with herself
她非常了解自己，节奏也很快。
she's got a shrine at home which she's
她在家里设了一个神龛，她在那里……
got like her crystals and stuff on it
她把水晶之类的东西都放在上面了。
and I don't believe any of those things
我一个也不相信。
but the good part is that she doesn't
但好消息是她没有
care if I believe it and that's what
我信不信，这才是重点。
makes it work because I can just listen
之所以能奏效，是因为我只需要听。
I can look over and there's no pressure
我可以往那边看，没有任何压力。
to do some Shakra meditation or whatever
做些脉轮冥想之类的
and that's where it works that's great
这就是它发挥作用的地方，太棒了！
and it sounds like you really learned a
听起来你真的学到了很多东西。
lot of lessons yeah yeah you know and
很多教训，是啊，你知道的。
one of the things that's really
其中一件真正重要的事情
important is if you want to love you
重要的是你是否想爱你
have to accept your partner yeah like
必须接受你的伴侣，是的，就像
wanting them to be better whatever that
希望他们变得更好，无论如何
means is kind of a subtle form of
意思是某种微妙的……形式
disrespect because it's basically
这是不尊重，因为它基本上就是
communicating that you're not good
表达你不好
enough as you are
你这样就足够了
yeah so like and people have their
是的，所以就像，人们有他们的
preferences some things are so much
有些事情的偏好非常重要。
easier to accept than others and that
比其他方式更容易接受，而且
will differ from person to person so for
因人而异，所以……
whatever reason you're dealing with
无论你遇到什么原因
somebody who you honestly don't feel
一个你真心感觉不到的人
like you can accept like if this never
就像你可以接受，就像这从来都不是
changed it would degrade Your Capacity
更改后会降低您的容量
to participate enthusiastically in this
积极参与此项活动
relationship just find somebody else to
这段感情只是为了找别人而存在的。
have a relationship with don't them
和他们保持关系，但不要和他们发生性关系。
up by trying to change them no because
试图改变它们并不能解决问题，因为
part of the fun of loving is that
恋爱的乐趣之一就在于此
they're different and that you do kind
它们各不相同，而且你确实很友善。
of eventually want to create this safe
最终想要创造这种安全环境
context for the people to be themselves
为人们提供做自己的环境
because you can only love to the depth
因为你只能爱到极致。
of your knowledge you can only love to
你拥有的知识，你只能热爱它。
the depth of your understanding which is
你理解的深度，即
why to bring it back around it's
为什么要把它重新提起呢？
important to slowly dis Point your
慢慢地让你的注意力分散很重要。
partner from the marketing and the
来自市场营销和合作伙伴
attractiveness that initially bring
最初带来的吸引力
people out on the date so so you're not
大家都在约会，所以你不是
just performing all the time you do need
只需要一直保持这种状态就行了
to do that slowly and to actually show
慢慢来，并且真正地展示出来
the other person who you are so you can
了解对方，你才能成为他/她。
be seen which increases the likelihood
被看到会增加可能性
that you can be loved you cannot love
你可以被爱，但你不能爱别人。
something that you do not understand
你不明白的事情
that's just
那只是
Superstition all right what is the the
迷信，好吧，那是什么？
most important thing from your book the
你书中最重要的内容是
value of others understanding the
他人理解的价值
economic model of relation ships to get
建立关系的经济模型以获得
and keep more of what you want in the
把更多你想要的东西留在身边。
sexual Marketplace what is the most
性交易市场最火爆的是什么？
important thing in this book that we
这本书中很重要的一点是，我们
haven't talked about I think the most
我觉得我们还没谈到最重要的事
important thing is that people is really
重要的是，人们真的
understanding that people want things
明白人们想要东西
from other people and that if you want
来自其他人，如果你想的话
to be rich in relationships then you
要想在人际关系中变得富有，那么你
need to cultivate the things that people
需要培养人们所拥有的东西
want so that you can give them to those
想要这样你就可以把它们送给那些
things like the epilogue of that book is
比如那本书的后记就是
a parable from the life of Jesus about
耶稣生平中的一个寓言
the coin of Caesar and I think about
凯撒的硬币，我想到了
this in terms of relationship it's like
就关系而言，这就像是……
it's like render onto Caesar what is
这就像把凯撒的形象渲染到凯撒身上一样。
Caesar's like people need and want
凯撒喜欢人们需要和想要的东西
things from each other give them what
彼此之间的事物赋予他们什么
they need and want and you will have a
他们需要和想要，而你将拥有
satisfying relationship people don't
人们并不追求令人满意的关系。
want to admit that it's so okay can I
我想承认这完全没问题，可以吗？
talk about this for a second this is so
稍微谈谈这个，这真是太……
important I'll answer that indirectly
我会间接回答这个问题。
first using an analogy and then directly
首先用类比，然后直接
indirectly let's talk about professional
让我们间接地谈谈专业方面的问题。
relationships like what makes a
人际关系，例如是什么造就了
professional relationship a professional
专业关系专业人士
relationship the transaction in the what
交易关系是什么
I want here's what I'll give you yeah a
我想要这个，我会给你的，是的。
professional relationship yeah like
专业关系，是的，就像
what's the one thing that you get from a
你从中获得的最重要的一点是什么？
professional relationship that you don't
你没有的职业关系
get anywhere
去任何地方
else I'm not trying to trick you I think
否则，我觉得我不是想骗你。
you know this one well there's many
你很熟悉这个，有很多这样的。
things I get from a professional
我从专业人士那里得到的东西
relationship so like me and Jack we're
关系就像我和杰克一样
in a professional relationship we're
在专业关系中，我们
friends is what I like to think but
我喜欢这样想，但其实我们是朋友。
we're in a professional relationship so
我们之间是职业关系，所以
what do I get from Jack I mean he's just
我能从杰克那里得到什么？我的意思是，他只是
here because he likes you no no no no no
他来这儿是因为他喜欢你，不不不不不
why is he here um he's getting a lot out
他为什么在这里？嗯，他有很多话要说。
of it for himself is that it Jack are
对他自己而言，杰克是
you just here because you're getting a
你来这里只是因为你得到了一个
lot of stuff out of this he he loves it
他从中得到了很多东西，他很喜欢。
Jack you love it here tell
杰克，你喜欢这里吗？告诉我
[Laughter]
[笑声]
him ah Jack gets it what makes a
他啊，杰克明白了，是什么造就了
professional relationship professional
专业关系专业人士
is the transfer of money J Jack shouted
是转账吗？J Jack 大喊道
money by the way for everybody Jack just
顺便说一句，杰克对每个人都有好处。
shouted money from the back I was saying
我正说着，后面有人喊着要钱。
friendship he loves it he shouted money
他热爱友谊，他大声喊着钱
no no does that make Jack a mercenary is
不不，那难道就意味着杰克是雇佣兵吗？
he just here because he's getting paid
他来这儿只是因为有工资而已。
let's hope not but here's here's the
但愿不会，但情况就是这样。
thing maybe you're aware of this
或许你已经意识到这一点了。
especially once things started to come
尤其是当事情开始发生的时候
back online after the shutdowns from
断网后恢复在线
covid there was a a hiring problem like
新冠疫情期间出现了招聘难题。
a lot of people didn't want to work and
很多人不想工作，
the companies were kind of scratching
这些公司有点儿抓狂。
their head and they were thinking well I
他们低下头，心想：嗯……
don't understand we offer a really
不明白我们提供的真的
compelling Mission we are a really
我们肩负着一项令人振奋的使命，这真是一项意义非凡的使命。
inclusive family-like environment we
我们营造包容如家庭般的环境
really believe in the development of our
我们真心相信自身的发展。
employees we offer bean bag chairs and
我们为员工提供豆袋椅和
pingpong tables I don't understand why
我不明白为什么乒乓球桌
anyone want to work not work for us well
有人想在我们这里工作却不想好好工作吗？
is anybody in the dating the
有人在约会吗？
professional arena is like well what do
职业领域就像是，好吧，该怎么办？
you pay like maybe don't buy bean bags
你付的钱可能就买不起豆袋椅了
maybe pay your employees more like
或许可以给你的员工涨点工资
everybody who's looking for a job would
所有正在找工作的人都会
just say the reason why you have trouble
只需说明你遇到困难的原因即可。
hiring is you're paying $30 an hour and
招聘时薪是每小时 30 美元。
you require a master's
你需要硕士学位
degree the issue is that for everybody's
问题在于，对于每个人来说，这都是一个问题。
dignity we can't be too explicit about
尊严，我们怎么强调都不为过。
the transaction of money even in our
即使在我们这里，金钱交易也是存在的。
professional
专业的
relationships he's here because of money
他来这里是因为金钱关系。
right but if you just like pulled out a
对，但如果你只是掏出一个
w of cash and was like Jack what are you
手里拿着现金，然后就像杰克一样，你在干什么？
going to do for this today buddy you
今天我要做的就是这个，兄弟。
know will you jump over here it's like
你知道你会跳过来吗？就像这样
he he'll eventually have to choose
他最终必须做出选择
between his self-respect and his
在他的自尊和他之间
financial goals right and eventually
财务目标正确且最终
like many people he'll choose his
像许多人一样，他会选择他的
self-respect because he's going to feel
因为他会感到自尊。
undignified for what he has to do to get
为了得到这一切，他不得不做有辱尊严的事情。
that money and so to protect people's
这笔钱，以及为了保护人民的……
dignity we cover the professional
尊严，我们涵盖专业
interaction with a lot of
与大量废话打交道
with a lot of mission and inclusivity
充满使命感和包容性
and all these other things that
以及其他所有这些东西
generally don't solve as many problems
通常解决不了那么多问题
as paying people
作为付费人员
more like paying people more doesn't
更像是给人们涨工资并不会……
solve every problem from an employees
解决员工遇到的每一个问题
perspective but it solves a lot of
从某种角度来看，它解决了很多问题。
problems from an employees
员工带来的该死的问题
perspective right and to be fair there
视角正确，公平地说，
are plenty of high-paying jobs like in
有很多高薪工作，例如……
medicine Venture Capital that have
拥有医药风险投资的
terrible cultures like to be a medical
糟糕的文化喜欢成为医疗
doctor you have to go through the
医生，你必须经历这个过程
residency process 120 hours where you're
住院医师培训过程需要120个小时，地点在你所在的地方
working for a dollar an hour you're not
你不是那种时薪一美元的人。
sleeping for 3 days straight it's tough
连续睡三天三夜真难熬。
top to your law firms Venture Capital
为您的律师事务所风险投资提供顶级服务
they're like if you can't take it buddy
他们会说，如果你承受不了，伙计。
that's okay don't swim with the sharks
没关系，别和鲨鱼一起游泳。
we pay you enough I don't want to hear
我们付给你的钱够多了，我不想听
any complaining and show me the results
别抱怨了，把结果给我看看。
so it's like when you pay people more
这就好比你给人们更高的工资一样。
they're willing to put up with not
他们愿意忍受不
having those other things okay the issue
其他那些事情没问题
is when a lot of good meaning but
是有很多美好寓意的时候，但是
soft-headed people take the
头脑简单的人会相信胡说八道。
seriously and they think oh yeah I hear
说真的，他们会想，哦，是啊，我听说了。
a lot culture is important we'll give
文化很重要，我们会给予
people culture and they think that
人们的文化，他们认为
that's going to be a substitute for
那将是一个替代品
giving people money in a professional
以专业人士的身份给人们钱
relationship and that's not true okay
关系，那不是真的，好吗？
you buy that 100% great so now we'll
你买的那个100%好，所以现在我们……
answer the relationship problem
回答关系问题
directly one of the rules about
直接遵循以下规则之一
relationships is you cannot be too
人际关系就是你不能太……
explicit with a transaction because then
明确地通过交易进行交易，因为那样
it will feel like prostitution okay and
感觉就像卖淫一样，好吧。
no one wants to feel that way man are a
没有人想有那种感觉，男人都是……
woman and it's been it offends the
女人，而且这冒犯了……
Dignity of the individuals involved and
相关人员的尊严和
so we cover it with a lot of
所以我们用很多东西覆盖它
the core of relationships is
人际关系的核心是胡扯
getting your needs met from another
从他人那里获得需求满足
person if you don't give people more of
如果你不给人们更多……
what they want or need they will be
他们想要或需要的，他们就会是
dissatisfied if you give people more of
如果你给人们更多，他们会不满意
what they want and need you will be able
你将能够满足他们的需求。
to dispense with a lot of the
剔除很多废话
that Society tells you relationships are
社会告诉你，人际关系是
actually about in the same way that
实际上，方式大致相同。
paying people more companies to dispense
支付更多费用给人们，让更多公司分发
with the around how companies
以及围绕公司运作的那些胡说八道
are supposed to
应该
be that is most people that I know would
我认识的大多数人都会这样。
rather take a high-paying job and have
宁愿接受一份高薪工作，并且拥有
fewer of these other fluffy things
少放些其他蓬松的东西
around it than vice
围绕着它比副
versa by the same token most people are
反之亦然，同样地，大多数人
going to be satisfied if they get their
如果他们得到他们想要的，他们就会感到满意
needs and desires want in a met in a
需求和欲望想要在一个地方得到满足
relationship if you want a satisfying
如果你想要一段令人满意的关系
relationship meet the needs and wants of
关系满足了……的需求和愿望
your partner and then you w't need to do
你的伴侣，然后你就不需要这样做了。
all the then you don't need to
那么你就不需要那些废话了。
do the what is the in
做那些废话，废话到底是什么？
the context of really give me some
真的给我一些
examples like Valentine's Day or oh
例如情人节或哦
there's so many different forms of the
有很多不同的形式
especially from the context of
胡说八道，尤其是在以下背景下：
a psychotherapeutic perspective um the
从心理治疗的角度来看
issue is that you have to understand
问题在于你必须理解
what your love languages are or you have
你的爱的语言是什么？或者你有
to understand I'm an inj and you are an
要明白我是伤者，你是伤者
entp and we want thing it's like we have
ENTP，我们想要的东西就像我们拥有的一样。
to accommodate other people's
为了迁就他人
personalities we have to learn to
我们必须学会的性格
communicate we have to learn to
沟通是我们必须学会的。
compromise we have to just love more you
我们必须做出妥协，那就是更加爱你。
have to find God and go to church you're
你必须找到上帝，去教堂。
playing out you're role playing the
扮演角色
people in your practice right sure right
你诊所里的人对吧？对吧？
and it's like you don't have to do any
就好像你什么都不用做一样
of those things like especially if a lot
尤其是一些类似的事情，如果很多的话。
of soft-headed but good-hearted people
心地善良但头脑简单的人
except that is true it's like
除了那句胡说八道是真的之外，就像……
oh yeah communication is important well
哦，沟通很重要。
I'll just learn how to communicate
我得学会如何沟通。
better with my partner yeah you could be
和我的伴侣在一起更好，是的，你也可以。
the best Communicator in the world but
世界上最好的沟通者，但是
if you're not giving your partner what
如果你没有给你的伴侣什么
she needs and wants it's going to be a
她需要并且想要这将是一个
high conflict difficulty relationship
高冲突困难关系
and if you give her what she needs and
如果你给她她需要的东西，
wants you don't have to communicate with
想要你不必与人沟通
her at all if you don't want to like
如果你不想喜欢她，那就完全不要理她。
I've gotten to the point where I think
我已经到了这种地步：
it's possible to have a completely
有可能完全
satisfactory relationship with someone
与某人保持令人满意的关系
that you don't even speak their
你甚至都不跟他们说话
language because a lot of what makes
语言，因为很多东西都构成了语言。
relationships work is the discharg of
人际关系工作是释放
need and want and a lot of communication
需求、欲望以及大量的沟通
can be accomplished non-verbally so I
可以通过非语言方式完成，所以我
guess the conclusion here if I was to
如果让我来猜，我会得出什么结论？
guess is that we need to understand what
我想我们需要了解的是什么
we need but also we need to understand
我们需要，但我们也需要理解
what we actually offer yeah if you're
我们实际提供的服务是，如果您是
having trouble in the dating Market
在约会市场遇到困难
there's really two possibilities one is
实际上有两种可能性，一种是……
you're being too picky you want too many
你太挑剔了，你想要太多了。
things and or your value proposition is
事物和/或你的价值主张是
dubious that what you hope to get isn't
令人怀疑的是，你所希望得到的并非你所期望的。
commensurate with what you will give in
与你愿意付出的相称
return people don't like hearing that
回头客不喜欢听到这些话
people don't like hearing that how would
人们不喜欢听到这样的话。
you say that in a simpler way if you
如果你用更简单的方式来表达，
want more you have to be prep prep to
想要更多，你必须做好准备。
give more and the problem is people want
付出更多，问题是人们想要更多
a lot of things and they don't have a
很多东西，但他们没有
lot to offer you said it you said it
有很多东西可以提供，你说过了，你说过了。
you're the one that said it I didn't say
是你说的，我没说。
it you said the last part um but it is
你说最后一部分……嗯，但是是
true that the more that you want the
确实，你越想要
more you have to be prepared to give and
你必须做好付出的准备，而且
that's
那就是
fair yeah no it makes perfect sense I
没错，这完全说得通。
mean it's like simple mathematics it is
意思是说，它就像简单的数学一样。
um we have a closing tradition on this
嗯，我们有个关于这个的结束传统。
podcast where the last guest leaves a
播客节目中，最后一位嘉宾离开了
question for the next guest not knowing
下一位客人不知道这个问题
who they're leaving it for the question
他们把这个问题留给了谁。
that has been left for you oh how
那是留给你的，哦，多么美好啊！
interesting
有趣的
is there something you wanted to do in
你有什么想做的事情吗？
your life that you didn't do because you
你因为……而没有过上你本该拥有的人生。
were
是
afraid sure yeah there have been things
害怕？当然，确实发生过一些事。
that I haven't done because of
我没有做这件事是因为……
fear I think on the like I didn't go
恐怕我没去。
skydiving for instance but I don't know
例如跳伞，但我不知道
if that's really what she's this person
如果她真是那样的人的话
is talking about um and I am confident
正在谈论嗯，我很有信心
in saying that I have since overcome my
说我已经克服了我的
fear and all those important
恐惧以及所有那些重要的
hesitations um one of the hardest things
犹豫不决是最难克服的事情之一。
to do is to overcome the fear
要做的就是克服恐惧
of an important
一个重要的
estrangement in a often because of the
疏远往往是由于……
TR of the kind of superficial
表面型的TR
and Casual nature of relationships these
以及这种随意的关系性质
days it's often family and um family
日子里，通常是家人，嗯，家人
relationships can be very difficult to
人际关系可能非常困难
navigate because we come with a whole
因为我们带着一整套设备而来，所以能够顺利导航。
host of expectations about how mothers
人们对母亲有很多期望
are supposed to act and fathers and
应该采取行动，父亲们也应该如此。
brothers etc etc and sometimes people
兄弟等等，有时还有人
can hold on to
可以坚持
grudges a very long time in
怨恨会持续很长时间
families and there's those grudges can
家庭中也存在着那些怨恨。
also be maintained through the fear of
也可能通过恐惧来维持
being the first person to forgive and
第一个原谅别人的人
the first person to extend an olive
第一个递橄榄的人
branch both sides generally feel like
双方都感觉像
they've been wronged
他们受到了不公正的对待。
and so both sides are functionally
因此，双方在功能上都是
waiting for the other person to act
等待对方采取行动
first and what I found is that's one of
首先，我发现这是其中之一
the secrets of forgiveness it's like
宽恕的秘密就像
four you give it first it doesn't
第四，你先给它，它不会。
necessarily mean the other person will
未必意味着对方会
forgive you as well but one of the most
我也原谅你，但其中最……
important things that I've done is being
我做过的重要事情是……
willing to overcome that fear of
愿意克服这种恐惧
offering the
提供
forgiveness and not having that be
宽恕，以及没有宽恕这件事
reciprocated and that was a fear that
相互回应，而这正是我所担心的。
kept me
让我留了下来
paralyzed in some of my relationships in
在某些人际关系中，我陷入了瘫痪状态。
the past that I think was really helpful
我认为过去那些真正有帮助的事情
and important for me to overcome and how
对我来说，克服困难以及如何克服困难都非常重要。
has that benefited you that
那对你有好处吗？
forgiveness well it helped me to get rid
宽恕确实帮助我摆脱了困境。
of anger in my heart man it's like
我心里充满了愤怒，就像……
people have hurt me people I'm sure have
有人伤害过我，我确信有人伤害过我。
hurt you and it's very difficult to go
伤害了你，而且很难离开。
through life and to not be hurt there's
人生在世，为了不受伤，有……
all kinds of things to bump into both
各种各样的事情都可能遇到。
figuratively and literally
比喻意义上和字面意义上
and I think that without
我认为如果没有
forgiveness a person's heart just fills
宽恕能使人的心中充满爱意。
up with anger and resentment over time I
随着时间的推移，我的愤怒和怨恨与日俱增。
think of forgiveness as an emotional
将宽恕视为一种情感
survival strategy it's something that I
生存策略是我需要考虑的事情。
did to save my own life to save my own
为了保住自己的性命
heart doesn't technically involve
心脏严格来说并不涉及
another person it's a relinquishing of
对另一个人来说，这是一种放弃
hatred and resentment and anger because
仇恨、怨恨和愤怒，因为
I don't want to feel that way anymore
我不想再有那种感觉了
and the more that you feel those things
你越能感受到这些事情。
the more that your feeling apparatus is
你的感觉器官越……
clouded and it's harder to sense any
天色阴沉，很难察觉到任何东西。
other kind of emotional information or
其他类型的情感信息或
energy and so it can kind of be a
能量，所以它可以是一种
self-fulfilling prophecy for a lot of
对很多人来说，这都是自我实现的预言。
people who have been hurt they go around
那些受伤的人四处走动
getting hurt even
即使受伤
more so I think that was something that
我觉得更重要的是，那件事是……
I was afraid to do was to was to really
我害怕做的，就是真的
look at the anger inside and I kept it
看看我内心的愤怒，我把它藏了起来。
inside for longer than I probably needed
我在里面待的时间可能比我需要的要长。
to and to kind of clean up my heart and
为了，也为了某种程度上净化我的心灵，
to clean up my
清理我的
relationships you you referenced earlier
你之前提到的那些关系
Dr Orion terban you referenced earlier
您之前提到的Orion Terban博士
that you know in this day and age you
你知道，在这个时代，你
can clean up your life you can clean up
你可以清理你的生活，你可以清理
your your heart your soul and your
你的心，你的灵魂，还有你的
environment and then you can help
环境，然后你就可以提供帮助了。
millions of others which is a unique
还有数百万其他人，这真是独一无二。
opportunity that's been presented to us
我们面临的机遇
in 2024 with the power of the internet
2024年，借助互联网的力量
um and that's exactly what you're doing
嗯，你现在做的正是如此。
in every sense of the word it sounds to
从各个意义上来说，它听起来都像是
me like you have been on a journey
我和你一样，都经历了一段旅程。
yourself and you've arrived at a place
你自己，你已经到达了一个地方
where you're helping millions and
你正在帮助数百万人，
millions of people people through not
数百万人通过
just the book that I have in front of me
就是我面前的这本书。
here today which is essential reading
今天这里要介绍的是必​​读内容。
for anybody who wants a really different
对于任何想要真正与众不同的人来说
quite
相当
honest um challenging perspective on
坦率地说，这很有挑战性。
what's actually going on with
到底发生了什么？
relationships and love and all these
人际关系、爱情以及所有这一切
interpersonal dynamics that most people
大多数人的人际关系动态
are afraid to talk about out loud but
他们不敢大声谈论，但是
also through your YouTube channel which
也可以通过你的 YouTube 频道
has been an absolute Smash Hit and I was
这部作品绝对大获成功，而我……
on there earlier on watching many of
之前在那里看过很多视频
your videos and the way that you deliver
你的视频以及你的表达方式
your message is both based on science
你的信息既基于科学，又基于科学。
and facts and solid data but also based
以及事实和可靠数据，但也基于
on the experience that has come out of
从这段经历中……
your practice of many many men and that
你与许多男人交往的做法，以及
blend of um insights I thinke presents a
我认为，这融合了多种见解，呈现出一种……
really important unique perspective on
对……而言，这是一个非常重要且独特的视角。
these issues so I thank you for all of
这些问题，所以我非常感谢你们。
the wonderful work that you're doing
你所做的工作非常出色
because it's certainly helping so many
因为它确实帮助了很多人。
people and it's a very essential voice
人们的声音至关重要。
and you're a remarkable Communicator as
而且你是一位杰出的沟通者
well so I think um sometimes it's not
所以我觉得，有时候并非如此。
necessarily what we're saying it's how
不一定是我们说的，而是方式
we're saying it and you say it in a
我们这么说，你也这么说。
really impactful um honest dare I say
真的很有影响力，嗯，说实话，我敢这么说吗？
vulnerable way so thank you for the work
以这种脆弱的方式，所以感谢你的工作
that you do Dr Orion it's terrible that
奥赖恩博士，你这样做太糟糕了。
was High Praise man thank you that wow I
真是太棒了，谢谢你，哇！
I do hope that I'm on net positive I
我希望我的最终结果是积极的。
don't always get it right I am trying my
我并不总是能做对，我正在努力
best and learning as I go uh this was a
尽力而为，边做边学，嗯，这是……
wonderful conversation thank you so much
非常棒的谈话，非常感谢！
thank you Stephen
谢谢你，斯蒂芬
[Music]
[音乐]
oh
哦